Chapter 1403: Change and Situation

A huge space fortress floated in the universe, surrounded by wormhole hyperdrive base stations. From time to time, wormholes opened and closed, and fleet after fleet flew out.

The Siebert Fortress was located in the Carter Star Cluster at the border of the Flickering World. It was the headquarters of the Galactic Alliance Army in the Flickering World.

In order to fight against the World Tree Civilization, the three Universal Civilizations formed the Galactic Alliance Army during the preparation period and combined the forces of the explored universe. They also divided the explored universe's various Star Fields into numbered military regions and modified them to varying degrees.

Over the past ten years, the Flickering World had been completely transformed. The five border Star Clusters were now only left with countless defensive lines and strongholds.

Not only the Flickering World which represented the first military region but even the Star Fields in the central region were also prepared for war.

After all, the situation of the World Tree invading the territory was different from the interception war. During the interception war, there was a large area behind them, so there was a limit to their worries. However, past the Flickering World was the territory, so there was no way to retreat. They had to guard against it, and the pressure was completely different.

At this moment, in the conference room on the top floor of the Siebert Fortress, countless people were gathered with solemn expressions. Not only were there the various commanders of the Galactic Alliance Army, but there were also some Beyond Grade A Association upper echelons.

A 3D star map of the Flickering World appeared on the table.

"According to the report from the frontline, the World Tree's vanguard army is not far from the Flickering World border. It is estimated that they will arrive at the outermost defense circle in ten days. The various troops are already prepared for battle. What do you all think?"

Simon operated the star map as he spoke. He enlarged the area at the border and marked the areas that were most likely to be attacked by the World Tree.

Although the World Tree only had one set of coordinates, it would not take just one route. It would split into many vanguard teams and advance in different directions, eventually invading the Flickering World from those directions. However, the three Universal Civilizations had already expected this situation and had turned the Flickering World into a metal barrel.

"We've been preparing for this day for more than ten years. Just fight."

"That's right. What needs to be prepared and discussed has been done for more than ten years. Now, it's time to test our results."

"The World Tree's current actions have not deviated from our predetermined situation. We just have to act according to the strategy. When they really attack, we will adjust accordingly."

Many of the officers spoke, their fighting spirit overflowing.

Simon nodded and turned to look at Han Xiao. "Your Excellency Black Star, what do you think?"

Han Xiao supported his face with his palm and said, "We have strengthened our defense and cleared the resources, the World Tree can't snowball for the time being, so they won't keep advancing blindly. They'll most likely build a bridgehead base in the border area and stabilize the jump point, ready to fight a long battle with us."

Compared to ten years ago, his appearance had not changed at all. With his extraordinary lifespan, this bit of time could not even leave a mark on him.

"That's right," Simon agreed.

"So, this is a test of endurance. A battle of attrition is inevitable. Let's see who can endure it. Let's see if we die first or if we find the World Tree's main body first," Han Xiao shrugged.

Currently, the revival mechanism of the World Tree was still unsolvable. Han Xiao felt that the Transcendent Grade should have the power to attack the Information Form, but he could not unlock it. He could only attribute it to some prerequisites that had yet to be fulfilled.

In the past few years, the secondary dimension expeditionary army had made some progress. Although they did not find the World Tree's main body, they had figured out the World Tree's territory in the secondary dimension and had met the other party's garrison many times.

Fortunately, with the protection of Harrison's halo, they did not expose their coordinates and were safe. However, their actions were finally discovered by the World Tree Civilization. Currently, batches of Blessed Races were searching for the expedition army of the three Universal Civilizations in the secondary dimension.

However, this was unavoidable. The World Tree's main body was protected by countless Blessed Race members and it was heavily guarded. The closer the expedition army got to the main body, the easier it was to trigger the alert. It was basically impossible to find the main body of the World Tree without alerting any guards. It was the same in his previous life. The team that actively searched for the main body of the World Tree was chased all over the world by the Blessed Race. In the end, it was Harrison's luck that had exploded, and he passed through the security net and found the main body.

"When does the Beyond Grade A Association plan to participate in the battle?" Simon asked.

"They can participate in the battle at any time, excluding me." Han Xiao narrowed his eyes. "I won't make a move before the World Tree sends out the Tree King again."

His advancement to the Transcendent Grade was still a secret to the World Tree. He wanted to use this opportunity to launch a surprise attack and seal another Tree King. If he rashly appeared to fight a small army, he would most likely scare the Tree Kings so much that they would not dare to appear.

Before luring out the Tree King, he did not want his cannon to hit the mosquitoes.

No one had any objections. After some discussion, they quickly finished the meeting and went offline to prepare.

Han Xiao turned off the remote projection and looked back at the square of the training base. In front of him was a dense crowd. All the trainees were gathered there, looking at him.

"As all of you know, the World Tree is about to invade. The training will end today. It's time for you to use what you've learned."

As Han Xiao spoke, he scanned the crowd.

After more than ten years of high-pressure training and his guidance, a new batch of Beyond Grade As had been born. There were more than forty of them. Other than the exploration era, there had never been a time in history where Beyond Grade As were born so frequently.

Almost half of the members of the Black Star Army were there. Jotina successfully advanced, Nero also advanced to Beyond Grade A half a year ago, and even Lagi successfully advanced.

Karlot had also advanced to Beyond Grade A early on, but Han Xiao did not allow him to appear. He was still undergoing special training, accumulating insights, and trying to trigger [Everlasting Martial Path] again to quickly reach his peak combat strength.

The trainees were in an uproar for a while. Suddenly, as though they had made an agreement, they all bowed toward Han Xiao.

Regardless of whether they had advanced to the Beyond Grade A realm or not, everyone had a solemn expression on their faces as they said in unison,

"Thank you, Your Excellency Black Star, for teaching us for the past ten years. We will remember to engrave kindness in our hearts!"

No matter what Black Star's motive was, at least they knew how much they had benefited in the past ten years. Their gratitude toward Han Xiao was sincere.

Han Xiao accepted it calmly and waved his hand. "Report to the army."

Everyone bowed again and boarded the spaceships that were already prepared. The spaceships turned into streams of light and disappeared from everyone's sight.

At this moment, Kasuyi walked up from behind and sighed.

"I wonder how many of these Calamity Grade seeds will survive till the next time we meet."

"We've already given them the chance. You can't blame others for not being able to obtain the Sanctum entrance ticket in more than ten years."

Han Xiao shook his head.

Kasuyi nodded. "It's time for us to report. Remember to bring Aurora back. If we can't see her, we won't feel confident."

"Got it."

Han Xiao nodded and watched the Beyond Grade A Association members leave.

In comparison, the Beyond Grade As were not too nervous. With Black Star's Sanctum Revival, their lives were guaranteed.

After more than ten years of training, many Beyond Grade As had made some improvements. Han Xiao sparred with them from time to time, and he also obtained some abilities from some of them.

After sending everyone away, Han Xiao changed into King and teleported to the Soul Terminal.

The moment he arrived—Hila, Aurora, and Feidin, who were in seclusion—sensed him.

"You're here?"

Hila stopped absorbing the soul fragments, and an indescribable aura emanated from her body.

"You've improved a lot over the years." Han Xiao looked at her with a satisfied expression.

Soul Terminal was the training ground for Hila and Feidin. After ten years of seclusion, Hila had already stepped into the peak Beyond Grade A realm, and her strength had increased tremendously.

Feidin had absorbed an unknown amount of soul energy through the Soul Swapper, and he had also steadily reached the level of an upper-tier Beyond Grade A.

As for Aurora, she was unable to use the resources of the Soul Terminal, but she had received special training from Hila, and her abilities had also improved. Although she was not as strong as the two freaks—Hila and Feidin, she was still quite good.

"You're here to take us back, right? It's about time for the World Tree to arrive." Hila's eyes flashed with a fighting spirit, "I can finally fight the Tree King."

Han Xiao ignored this battle maniac and turned to Aurora. "You're our core member. Are you ready?"

"Don't worry, I won't fail this time!"

Aurora clenched her fists with determination.

Although she still remembered that dream, she had already sworn not to fall for it again.

Han Xiao smiled and rubbed her head before looking at Feidin.

"You're already an upper-tier Beyond Grade A Super. Using this power to activate the Soul Swapper is enough to cause a large area of damage to the members of the World Tree. You have a lot of freedom in this."

The Soul Swapper was a mass killing machine, and its power was not inferior to psionic waves. It was also a treasured military tool, and when it was inconvenient for him to attack, Feidin would be able to replace him to deal large area damage to the fleet.

"I understand." Feidin rubbed the surface of the Soul Swapper and nodded.

Although he did not like killing, he would not show mercy to invaders like the World Tree.

Han Xiao then changed into another King and teleported to the Underworld. He immediately saw Evans, and EsGod, who was teaching him combat skills.

As soon as he saw Han Xiao, Evans immediately stopped practicing and walked up to him.

Han Xiao cut to the chase and said, "The World Tree is coming. Come with me."

"Okay." Evans nodded.

EsGod walked over with his hands behind his back and said, "Don't die on the battlefield. I'm still waiting for you to fulfill my dream. Although the Sanctum Revival is good, as long as you die once, your ability will be lost, and you will never be able to reach the Transcendent Grade. Don't blame me for giving up on you when that happens."

"Don't worry, Teacher. I won't die so easily."

Evans replied with confidence.

As the saying goes, having a senior is like having a treasure. EsGod had roamed the universe for many years, and he was extremely experienced. With his wholehearted guidance, Evans had already accumulated a lot of combat skills.

When he first advanced and obtained the [Energy Control] Esper Ability, Evans was at most an ordinary person with a firearm in his hands. Now that he had received EsGod's teachings, he was like a soldier who had completed all the special force's elite classes and was proficient in all weapons. His combat ability had increased many times.

After more than ten years of interaction, Evans already saw EsGod as his teacher. Although EsGod did not admit it, he did not reject this title.

"Follow me."

Han Xiao raised his brows and left with Evans without saying anything.

EsGod watched as the two of them disappeared, and a faint smile appeared on his face.

The three Universal Civilizations intensely prepared for battle. Ten days passed in the blink of an eye, and the World Tree Vanguard Army finally arrived at the border of the Flickering World.

Just as the Military Strategy Department had expected, the World Tree invaded from different directions, but they were all within the range of the defense circle. Battles broke out in many areas at the same time.

In all the battlefields, the individual strengths on both sides restrained themselves. The Beyond Grade As of the three Universal Civilizations had only probed a few times, but the World Tree Civilization had never sent any Beyond Grade As to fight.

Having learned from the Heart Tree King's case, the World Tree was extremely wary of Black Star and did not use any Beyond Grade As for the first wave of attacks.

In this first battle that occurred after a gap of ten years, the three Universal Civilizations, which had been preparing for a long time, successfully gave the World Tree Army a head-on blow. They did not allow the World Tree to step into their territory, and both sides were in a stalemate at the Flickering World border.

However, even after winning once, the three Universal Civilizations did not feel any joy, because this was only the first wave of probing attacks. The World Tree did not use much of its strength, and the situation was still dire.

Just as Han Xiao had said, the World Tree was prepared for a battle of attrition. The first thing it did was to build a large number of bridgeheads outside the Flickering World border.

Because of the World Tree's continuous advancement, the jump points were all under their control. The three Universal Civilizations were currently unable to replicate the spatial anchoring orbits which were used during the interception war, and they could not chase away the enemy. They could only defend their territory and endure the waves of attacks from the World Tree. Going forward, this would be the situation of the war, and it was also a situation that the three Universal Civilizations had long been prepared for.

Chapter 1404: Confrontation

The intense battle between the World Tree Army and the Galactic Alliance Army lasted for two months, but the World Tree was still unable to break into the Flickering World territory. Although they had broken through the Galactic Alliance Army's defenses several times, the defense circle that the three Universal Civilizations had used more than ten years to build, was far more complete than the temporary intercepting circle. The support network was extremely dense, like an extremely dense elastic net.

The deeper they sank, the stronger the rebound would be, and they would not be able to stand on their own. All the World Tree troops that had attacked the Flickering World were either beaten back or wiped out. Their best record did not even reach three days, not even passing through the Star System at the border.

The border battle reports of the Flickering World were constantly sent back to the Central Galaxy, spreading throughout the galactic society. Countless galactic residents had been in fear for more than ten years, and now that the enemies had truly invaded their territory, many of them were even more afraid. However, because the Galactic Alliance Army had always kept the enemies out of their territory, their outstanding performance gave some confidence to the galactic residents.

Siebert Fortress. Many Beyond Grade As were on standby here for two months.

"Heh, didn't the World Tree like to use its individual strength against us? Why are they so cowardly now? They are getting rusty."

In the lounge, Sun Hunter stepped on the table and said with disdain.

"Probably because they're afraid of Black Star. He captured a tree king ten years ago, so it must have hurt them," Kant smiled.

In the past two months, no matter how they provoked or enticed them, the World Tree did not send out their individual strengths to fight, calmly watching the Beyond Grade As of the three Universal Civilizations create trouble on the battlefield.

The Beyond Grade As were a little helpless. No matter how strong their fighting spirit was, there was nothing they could do if the others did not respond. They had even used their physical bodies to tempt the World Tree expert, but the World Tree experts still refused to come out.

"You're thinking too much. The World Tree isn't that afraid of me. They should be observing the number of individual strengths we have. They won't give up on their Exchange tactic so easily. They're probably going to attack soon."

Han Xiao played with Ames' hair and replied casually.

He had been on standby with the others, waiting to catch a big fish.

In the past few days, the three Universal Civilizations had hidden the true size of their individual strength. Most of the new Beyond Grade As did not come out. Hila, Feidin, Evans, and the other powerful Beyond Grade As with special abilities or huge progress did not participate. At the same time, the Beyond Grade As who had 'died' during the last battle did not appear, allowing them to remain 'dead' in the eyes of the World Tree.

In the Holy Accord organization that was not yet revealed to others, there were still dozens of Revivors who were prepared to participate in the battle. The individual strengths displayed in front of the World Tree were just the tip of the iceberg. It was to make the World Tree think that the Exchange tactic was effective and fall into the trap.

After more than ten years of searching, Oathkeeper had accumulated quite a few Sanctum keys, but Han Xiao had never used them. He kept them as a strategic reserve.

Buzz—

While everyone was chatting, the alarm suddenly sounded. The World Tree launched another attack on the outermost defense circle.

Everyone paused. Before they could move, a remote projection of an officer suddenly appeared in the room.

"Everyone, the Beyond Grade As of the World Tree have finally appeared. Please arrive at the battlefield as soon as possible."

Hearing this, Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

"It's finally here… Is there any sign of the Tree King this time?"

"Yes!"

"Who?"

"Two. They are the Subduing Tree King and the Lord's Avatar of the Fortitude Tree King."

Kasuyi could not help but laugh and interrupted, "With the lesson from last time, the World Tree would not dare to let the Tree King go out alone. However, the arrangement this time is similar to the last. I'm afraid they feel that as long as they are careful, they will not fall for the same trick as the Heart Tree King."

This time, a new Beyond Grade A asked curiously,

"The Tree King has already appeared. Does Your Excellency Black Star want to fight?"

"It's only Subduing Tree King… Forget it, I'll leave it to you guys."

Han Xiao stroked his chin, pondered, and clicked his tongue.

He hoped to catch a big fish. At the very least, it should be Fortitude Tree King. It would be best if it was the Ancestral Tree King. It did not seem worth it to expose his strength for a mere Subduing Tree King… He just disliked the Subduing Tree King, a Pugilist, because his abilities were too simple and he was not as important as the other Tree Kings.

Furthermore, there were plenty of Beyond Grade As in the Beyond Grade A Association, so there was no need for him to do anything. As long as they killed Subduing Tree King, he would not be able to revive in the short term. That should lure out the Ancestral Tree King and the Secret Tree King. They would be the better prey in Han Xiao's eyes.

Hila's eyes lit up, as though she was afraid that someone would snatch her opponent. "Leave this guy to me!"

Han Xiao raised his brows and dampened her enthusiasm mercilessly, "Although your improvement is not small, you are still far from killing a Tree King."

"You won't know till you try it." Hila's eyes flashed coldly.

"Alright, as long as you don't let him escape." Han Xiao curled his lips.

Originally, Wuornos was the most stable in dealing with the Tree King, but this guy had not left the Temple of Ten Thousand Gods for more than ten years, and he still had no intention of joining the battle. However, now that there was the eldest brother in the Underworld, they did not lack powerful experts.

Han Xiao noticed that Evans' hands were trembling slightly, and he could not help but feel strange. "Are you afraid?"

"This is my first time on the battlefield, and it's such a galactic war. I'm indeed a little afraid," Evans said calmly.

Lagi mumbled, "What's the use of being afraid? Could it be that I won't die in battle if I am afraid? I didn't expect to die so soon after becoming a Beyond Grade A for just a few years. Sigh, someone like me really doesn't have the right to enjoy life…"

"Shut up."

Han Xiao interrupted him.

If not for the fact that you have some combat power, I would have locked you in Amber today!

At this moment, on the border.

The enormous World Tree fleet was attacking the defensive perimeter, and the fleet of the Galactic Alliance Army cooperated with the various strongholds to counterattack. Countless terrifying rays of light shuttled back and forth in the vast battlefield of the universe, forming a bright but fatal rain of light that shot into each other's formation, turning the spaceships into fireworks in space.

This was not the first time the two sides had fought, and the battle situation quickly heated up. The troops moved under the command of various military artificial intelligences. From a macro perspective, it looked like they were only shooting at each other on a large scale, but in fact, both sides were adjusting their tactics and carrying out minor operations.

On the battlefield, a group of Beyond Grade As of the World Tree were observing from afar under the protection of their starships.

The Subduing Tree King placed his hands behind his back and scanned the formation of the Galactic Alliance Army with his sharp eyes.

Not long after, the Beyond Grade As of the three Universal Civilizations also arrived on the battlefield one after another. The two sides faced each other from afar. Because only a portion of them had appeared, their numbers did not seem as large as the World Tree's.

This batch of Beyond Grade As that had appeared was mainly those who had participated in the interception battle. The others were hiding in the dark and watching.

Seeing this, the Subduing Tree King narrowed his eyes and nodded.

"Humph, many of their experts died last time. They're not our match this time."

In the past two months, he had been observing the situation of the three Universal Civilizations' Beyond Grade As. Most of them were old enemies. Although there were a few new faces, their numbers were limited. They were probably new Beyond Grade As.

He did not find this strange. The World Tree also had been nurturing Supers for more than ten years, and it had also given birth to some new Holy Tree Emissaries and ancestral spirits. The size of their individual strength had also increased.

A portion of the enemy's individual strength had died in the battle more than ten years ago, and the dead of their World Tree had all been resurrected. The battle strength of both sides fluctuated, and the Subduing Tree King was quite confident.

However, the Heart Tree King had already fallen. As a Pugilist, it was very difficult for him to instantly kill the enemy's healer. He had tried it the last time, and he had fallen into Black Star's trap. Thus, he did not plan to repeat the same mistake. The gathering of the World Tree's powerhouses this time was just a test, and they did not have any intention of carrying out the Exchange tactic immediately.

Sweeping his gaze across the enemies, the Subduing Tree King suddenly realized that there was no trace of Black Star.

"That guy actually didn't come out? No, he must have hidden himself to ambush us."

The Subduing Tree King became alert.

The only person he was worried about was Black Star. The Heart Tree King had been sealed, and he did not want to follow in his footsteps. He was secretly on guard, afraid that Han Xiao would jump out and stab him.

As the saying goes, when enemies meet, their eyes will burn with hatred. The Beyond Grade As on both sides rushed toward each other without saying anything and immediately started fighting on the battlefield, forming a large area of chaos.

The Tree King activated his liberation mode, and his body glowed with green light. He had originally wanted to force Black Star out, but he did not expect to be stopped by a red-haired woman.

"Your opponent is me."

Hila stood in front of the Subduing Tree King with a cold expression, her eyes filled with killing intent.

The Subduing Tree King's eyes flickered. He had an impression of Hila.

"It's you? Hmm, your self-healing ability is not bad, but you think you can stop me with your strength?"

Other than Black Star, the Subduing Tree King was not afraid of anyone. Thinking of Hila's performance on the battlefield more than ten years ago, he did not even put her in his eyes.

Hila did not have the habit of shooting her mouth off. Hearing this, she let out a cold snort, and a powerful aura burst out from her.

The Subduing Tree King suddenly felt threatened, and his expression changed. He looked at Hila with shock.

'She has become so strong?'

Without a doubt, this red-haired woman had already stepped into the peak Beyond Grade A level, and her energy fluctuations were at the upper level of the peak Beyond Grade As. It had only been ten years since they last met, but she had already improved so much!

The Subduing Tree King's expression turned grave. Although there was still a gap between the two of them, he had to admit that this woman in front of him was qualified to fight him.

He sensed the battle situation of his comrades and realized that the enemy Beyond Grade As were far stronger than the World Tree's Beyond Grade As. Although they had lost in terms of numbers, they were not at a disadvantage.

"How did they train ‽" The Subduing Tree King was shocked.

In just ten short years, they had made such an obvious improvement. How could Beyond Grade As increase their combat strength so easily? Could it be that the enemy's territory was filled with geniuses ‽

Chapter 1405: Hila's New Form

Without waiting for the Subduing Tree King to make a move, Hila had already attacked. A red light flashed in her eyes, and the death energy that had formed into an ocean shot out. It contained an aura of destruction, sealing all of the Tree King's dodging angles.

Suppressing the shock in his heart, the Subduing Tree King flashed with green light, and his powerful Pugilist flames burst out like a supernova. A thick green light wave burst out and the approaching death energy froze in midair and shattered one after another. However, more death energy surged down and filled up the gap almost instantly.

After being strengthened by the power of the undead, the corrosion was many times stronger. Although the Subduing Tree King's protective flames blocked the death energy, there was still a portion of the death energy that stuck on it, constantly wearing down the thickness of the pugilist flames. The pugilist flames quickly lost their vitality, turning into stars before disappearing into the universe.

"This ability has the attacking properties of impact, erosion, decrease in activity, spirit, and so on. Furthermore, it seems to have some sort of superimposed killing technique. If my body is hit, it won't be good…"

With a thought in his mind, the Subduing Tree King channeled more energy into his protective shield. He also used his authority as a Tree King to summon the World Tree Root. It spun rapidly like a tornado, shattering the incoming death energy.

Without stopping, he bent his knees and stomped hard. A shockwave exploded behind him, and he shot out like a cannonball, turning him into a stream of light as he charged straight towards Hila.

"Come!"

Hila's eyes turned fierce, and a wave of red-black energy suddenly surged out from her body before quickly rolling back, covering her body, layer by layer. In an instant, it became solid and the death energy seemed to have solidified, turning her into a five to six-meter-tall red-black giant.

At the same time, dense and complicated silver-gray lines covered the little giant's body, looking rather mysterious.

The outline of the giant's body was exactly the same as Hila's, but there were no facial features on its face, only a pair of eyes burning with white light.

The next moment, the green meteor slammed into the abdomen of the little giant and flew out with her. Like a red and green ray, it penetrated dozens of starships, leaving a path filled with fireworks.

Dong dong dong~

Green fist shadows descended from the sky and landed on the giant like a storm. However, her red and black body was extremely tough, and there were no signs of it being shattered.

Suddenly, the multitude of fist shadows disappeared. Everyone saw that the giant had caught the Subduing Tree King's fist with both of its hands.

Bang!

The powerful force created a flowing ripple on the surface of the giant's body, spreading from his palm to his back, and then out from his body. A green energy shockwave spread out in the universe behind it, shattering hundreds of battleships.

"A Pugilist is invincible in close combat? I don't believe it!"

With a strong will to fight, the red and black giant suddenly smashed its head on the top of the Subduing Tree King's head, shaking the two of them. With a loud clank, the iron-headed baby received a 'friendly greeting'.

Immediately after, the giant let go of the Tree King and clenched his fist. In the blink of an eye, countless red flashes appeared, and hundreds of fist imprints burning with red flames appeared on the Tree King's protective shield. A huge force burst out and instantly sent him flying.

In this form, Hila had actually managed to defeat the Subduing Tree King in close combat!

"…..Interesting."

The Subduing Tree King that was sent flying immediately stopped and rubbed his head. The rest of his body was unharmed, and he was surprised by Hila's close combat skills.

After the previous fight, he realized that this giant's physique was extremely tough and strong. If not for the lack of Pugilist flames, he would have thought that he was fighting a peak Beyond Grade A Pugilist.

"Again!"

Hila waved her hands, full of fighting spirit.

Although her ability was good at attacking from mid to long distances, she still preferred engaging in fierce close combat.

After so many years of persistence in challenging Black Star, being pressed down on the ground time and time again, Hila had already gotten the thrill of being tortured. Not only did she like to get beaten up, but she also liked to beat others up just like Black Star did. In the past ten years, Aurora had suffered quite a few punches from her.

Because the Power Of The Dead contained the ability inheritance of her previous owner, Nerkese, Hila did not need to focus on developing her abilities to understand the usage of many Esper Abilities. After stepping into the peak Beyond Grade A realm, she had unlocked many new abilities, and transforming into a red and black giant was one of them.

Hila's control of death energy was usually focused on the outside of her body. Now that she could condense and compress it in her body, she could transform herself into another form, called 'Reaper Liberation'. This was one of the main battle methods of Nerkese.

This skill had many transformation stages, and the further one went, the stronger they became. However, each stronger stage required a sufficiently high energy level to unlock. The final requirement for unlocking the ultimate stage, 'God of the Dead' required an Energy Rank of more than 90,000 Ona. Hila had yet to meet the requirement, and she had only unlocked the 'Departed Soul' stage. It was the miniature red and black giant that she had currently transformed into.

After entering the 'Reaper Liberation' state, her body and the Underworld Dimension would fuse to a higher level, and she would be able to activate a new talent. The more Hero Spirits there were in the Underworld as well as the higher their quality, the more enhancements to her strength she would receive. The effect was similar to the [Proof of Leadership], which was also one of the reasons for Hila's huge increase in combat strength.

At the same time, because the body after transformation was made up of highly condensed death energy, the characteristics of the original ability still existed. Even if physical attacks were used, they would still have the ability to cause Death's Erosion, damaging and corroding the soul. Furthermore, just touching her body would cause the life force of an outsider to be lost.

The two of them looked at each other in midair, and the next moment, both of them moved at the same time. The red and green figures clashed once again, and their fists landed on flesh. The aftershock of their fists shot out and disrupted the battlefield.

"Tsk tsk, so scary."

Han Xiao stayed in the base, clicking his tongue as he watched the battle.

He had experienced this form of Hila before and her close combat ability was indeed very strong. Combined with her recovery ability, she was extremely tanky, and her combat strength stood firmly in the first tier.

However, in his eyes, even with this move, Hila was still far from being able to defeat the battle form of the Tree King. Before he advanced, even if he could win against the Subduing Tree King alone, he would not be able to do anything to him in a short period of time. Hila's strength was far weaker than before he advanced, so it was impossible for her to defeat the Tree King alone.

However, with her disgusting tankiness, she would not be beaten into a meat patty even by the Subduing Tree King anytime soon.

Han Xiao no longer looked at the two of them and looked at the other battlefields.

The Fortitude Tree King and Herberlon were old enemies, and their eyes were filled with hatred. The two Mechanical Deities' huge bodies rolled across the battlefield and shattered starships.

Other than the two of them, there were also quite a few Mechanical Deities on the battlefield. Due to the size of their bodies, they were all the most conspicuous people within the Beyond Grade A battlefield.

As for Milizaus, after successfully "losing weight", he had already escaped the fate of being a target. At this time, he was chasing after a World Tree Army leader and throwing magic spells. His improvement was huge, fully showing the benefits of getting to know an ancestor.

The rest, such as Manison, Kasuyi, and the others, found their opponents and fought non-stop. Furthermore, golden light would shoot out from the battlefield from time to time. That was Aurora healing people with precision. Her control was much more skillful than ten years ago, and her success rate was higher. It could be seen that the special training was quite effective.

After a few rounds of Sanctums' resuscitation, the three Universal Civilizations had a lot more experts in the first tier. However, the ten executives of the World Tree, the high-level Holy Tree Emissary, the thirteen ancestral spirits, and the army commanders were not to be trifled with. However, not all of the first-tier experts had entered the battlefield. The World Tree did not allow all the experts to participate in this probing attack, and the three Universal Civilizations had also hidden a batch of Revivors and new Beyond Grade As. Although the three Universal Civilizations had a disadvantage in terms of numbers, their strength had increased, so they did not suffer any losses and were temporarily in a stalemate.

"Feidin is going to attack, right?"

Han Xiao looked at Feidin, who was hiding in the fleet, and narrowed his eyes.

Although the souls of all the enemies were bound to the World Tree, causing the Soul Swapper to only be able to destroy them and not transfer the souls out, it was still very powerful.

As expected, after watching for a while, Feidin finally took out the Soul Swapper and activated this Universal Treasure.

The next moment, the souls of the crew members within the surrounding World Tree Spaceships were torn into pieces, and they died on the spot.

Tens of thousands of World Tree battleships faced such a situation, and the damage was still spreading further.

"Hmm? What's going on?"

The Subduing Tree King's expression changed, as he sensed this abnormality from the Mind Sharing.

The strange thing about the Soul Swapper was that it did not leave a trace. In the eyes of the Subduing Tree King, large batches of the World Tree crew had died without any warning. They could not find the source of the attack, but it was definitely the enemy's doing.

Although they did not know what special weapons the enemy had used, it was not a coincidence that the sudden deaths were gathered in one area. The World Tree fleet immediately began to adjust and avoid this area.

Although this was a stupid method, it was indeed effective. The Soul Swapper did not have an unlimited range. Although it could cover the entire planet, under the scale of the galactic battlefield, this range was relatively small. Of course, Feidin was not a fixed cannon. As long as he swam around the battlefield, he would be able to kill more enemies.

The Subduing Tree King naturally did not know about this. After observing the sudden death of the soldiers, he then looked at the current battle between Beyond Grade As, with a heavy mood.

"It's about time to retreat."

Although Black Star, who was the most difficult to deal with, had yet to appear, the Tree King had already decided to retreat.

He had thought that this probing attack would allow him to gain the upper hand in terms of individual strength and did not expect the situation to turn so bad. This civilization that was viewed as prey was extremely tenacious. It seemed like even if he managed to land on their territory, he would not be able to defeat them easily.

This time, he was not the main attacker. If the situation was good, the Subduing Tree King would not mind sacrificing himself. However, the current situation was not as he had expected. He felt that there was no need to continue fighting.

The Tree King's eyes narrowed, and his energy exploded. His fist glowed with the green light in the shape of a cross, and with lightning speed, it slammed into Hila's abdomen.

Bang!

A halo of impact appeared!

The two of them were originally locked in a fierce battle, but this heavy punch suddenly broke the stalemate, and Hila was sent flying. At the same time, the World Tree Root beside the Subduing Tree King threw Hila further away, smashing a row of starships like a meteor.

The Subduing Tree King did not chase after her. Instead, he turned around and retreated. The other World Tree experts received the order and retreated simultaneously, leaving only the Lord's Avatar of the Fortitude Tree King and the other Mechanic experts behind.

Although he was now unable to kill Hila, the difference in strength between them was not so easy to bridge. If he wanted to leave, Hila would not be able to stop him.

"Chase!"

Kasuyi shouted in the mental network, and the people still on the battlefield chased after him.

Hila finally managed to stop herself, and when she looked up, she realized that the Subduing Tree King was already far away. She immediately chased after him, but the distance between them was increasing instead of decreasing.

She could not help but release her mental waves to shout:

"Don't run! Keep fighting!"

The Subduing Tree King turned a deaf ear to her words and ignored her completely. He shuttled back and forth between the battles among the two fleets, getting closer and closer to his own formation, leaving her with only his back view.

At this moment, Dillon, who had already materialized, suddenly appeared on the battlefield. He looked at the figure of the Tree King from afar and sneered.

"Are you kidding me? How can you call yourself a King like this? You're just a piece of trash that ran away. You don't even deserve to be the most useless Pugilist."

As soon as he finished speaking…

The Subduing Tree King momentum suddenly decreased, and a look of shock appeared on his face.

What's going on… It's just a simple taunt. With my personality, I actually stopped for no reason and wanted to beat this guy up?!

Could this be some kind of mental control similar to that of the Voice Spirits?!

Chapter 1406: Dylan: I Am a Pro in Pulling Aggro

"What are you doing?"

The Fortitude Tree King, who was wrestling with Herberlon at the back, immediately noticed the abnormality of the Subduing Tree King and was shocked.

What the hell? Are you seriously stopping ‽

Originally, many of the World Tree powerhouses had retreated at the same time and formed a battlefront to support each other, effectively blocking the pursuit of the enemy group. However, the moment the Subduing Tree King stopped, he was instantly at the back and left the team, exposing himself to the enemy Beyond Grade As.

"I…"

The Subduing Tree King trembled as though he had just woken up from a dream. He suppressed the urge to turn around and took a deep look at Dylan before hurriedly following the rest.

However, before he could speed up, Dylan raised his brows.

"What are you looking at? What, you want to hit me? Do you have the guts?"

The Subduing Tree King paused, clenched his teeth, and continued to accelerate.

Seeing this, Dylan laughed and said with a judgmental tone, "That's right. Keep running. A Pugilist who doesn't even have this bit of courage doesn't have the right to even look at me."

The Subduing Tree King subconsciously stopped once again. He was shocked and furious… Usually, he would not be affected by such verbal conflict, but for some reason, when these words came out of this person's mouth, he could not control his emotions.

Anger surged through his brain, and the Subduing Tree King suppressed it. Just as he was about to take another step forward, Dylan's sarcastic voice sounded again.

"You really stopped? You can't even stand two sentences? Ha, you don't even have this little patience. You're indeed a Pugilist. Other than 'stupid', there's no other word suitable for you."

It was as if an invisible hand had grabbed onto his body, and the Subduing Tree King froze. He wanted to continue retreating, but he could not move his legs no matter how hard he tried. A demonic murmur echoed in his heart.

"Kill him… kill him… kill him…"

The Subduing Tree King's expression changed drastically. His expression was twisted, as though he was fighting with himself.

All of a sudden, the Fortitude Tree King's roar sounded in his mind.

"Are you f*cking leaving or not ‽"

The Fortitude Tree King could not take it anymore. He did not know what had gotten into the Subduing Tree King, but he was running intermittently. It was as if he was suffering from kidney damage, and he was getting left behind.

"There's something strange about that guy. His words can anger me…" The Subduing Tree King's tone was gloomy.

"Can't you block his mental transmission ‽"

The Fortitude Tree King roared in rage.

He even had to remind him of such a simple matter. He was indeed a pugilist!

The Subduing Tree King was stunned for a moment before coming to a realization.

That's right, I can still block him. Why didn't I react just now ‽ I must have lost my mind because of the anger!

He convinced himself. He was not willing to admit that although he was angered to the point of wanting to beat someone up, there seemed to be a magic in Dylan's words that made him want to listen to the scoldings more…

He quickly solidified the mental barrier and blocked the outside mental fluctuations. At this moment, the Subduing Tree King finally felt that the world was peaceful.

He suppressed the inexplicable reluctance in his heart and continued to run.

"Go back and support the Subduing Tree King!"

The Fortitude Tree King took over the command. He suppressed his anger and ordered the World Tree powerhouses to turn around and receive the Subduing Tree King.

The battlefield was ever-changing. Although the Subduing Tree King had only been delayed for a short while, he had distanced himself from the retreating troops and was completely alone.

Originally, the many World Tree experts had already run far away, and they were able to shake off the Beyond Grade A pursuers of the three Universal Civilizations with a small number of casualties. However, because the Subduing Tree King was being held back by taunts, they had no choice but to turn back and reinforce him. They fell back into the swamp, and their retreat formation was completely messed up.

The Fortitude Tree King had no choice. If he did not send these World Tree experts to support, the lone Subduing Tree King would most likely die on the spot.

Black Star had yet to make a move and could launch a sneak attack at any time. He was afraid that the Subduing Tree King would share the same fate and be sealed like the Heart Tree King, causing another Tree King Crown to disappear.

In addition, the Fortitude Tree King did not want the tool, the Subduing Tree King, to die in battle and go into hibernation. That would mean that he would have to take charge of the overall situation, how would he be able to idle away then? He would rather let the other World Tree experts die to save the Subduing Tree King.

The World Tree's retreat was interrupted, and the Beyond Grade As of both sides fought again.

On the other side, Sun Hunter flew past Dylan and laughed.

"Nicely done. Your mind game is quite good. You've pinned him down!"

"What mind game? I just want to scold him."

Dylan had a look of disdain on his face, and his gaze toward the Subduing Tree King held some anger.

Hearing this, the Beyond Grade As flying around looked at him strangely.

Scolding the enemy is nothing. If it was a private chat, it would have been fine. However, you are scolding openly, and we can clearly hear you attacking all Pugilists. If you were not playing a mind game, then doesn't your scolding involve our Pugilists as well?

At this moment, Sierron flew past them and said with a displeased expression, "Don't involve us Pugilists even if you want to insult the enemy."

Dylan glanced at him and said matter-of-factly, "You're also trash."

"…Don't stop me, I'm going to kill him now!"

Sierron was furious.

"Mission is more important. Ignore him." Sun Hunter quickly grabbed Sierron's finger and dragged him away without much effort.

The current Dylan had already completely adapted to the identity of the Underworld Hero Spirit, and he no longer had any scruples when speaking. The Beyond Grade As were no longer willing to lower themselves to his level. After all, what was the point in bickering with a dead person?

...

On the battlefield, the Subduing Tree King retreated as he fought. His attacks were filled with rage, and the power of his attacks increased.

Hila caught up once again. The red and black giant's fists continued to punch, and its arms pulled back and forth like rubber.

However, the current Subduing Tree King did not have any interest in being in a stalemate with her. Every move he made exploded with all his strength, and they all landed on Hila's body.

After a few rounds, Hila was beaten up badly and she was at a disadvantage.

Although she was also good at close combat in this form, there was still a gap between her and the Subduing Tree King, who was going all out. After all, the Pugilist class still had some meaning…

Bang!

The fist, shining with the green light of the cross, landed deeply on the red-black giant's body, and the surging Pugilist flames entered the giant's body.

The next moment, a green light suddenly lit up in the red-black giant's body. It expanded in the blink of an eye and dyed its entire body a dazzling green color. It exploded from the inside out!

Like a balloon exploding, the highly concentrated death energy that formed the body directly exploded, turning into red light fragments that filled the sky, and Hila's body was exposed.

Before Hila could retreat, the Subduing Tree King grabbed her neck and slammed his other hand into Hila's face, sending blood and broken bones flying.

"Powerful!"

With a flash of golden light, Hila's heavily injured face instantly recovered. The pain did not affect her movements at all. She condensed her death energy and was about to deal damage to the Subduing Tree King.

However, the Subduing Tree King understood her intentions. He raised his leg and kicked her heavily on her abdomen, interrupting her movements. He kicked her body until it folded and flew backward. Her spine was already broken by the huge penetrative force.

"Cough cough cough—"

Hila spat out a mouthful of blood, controlled her muscles to adjust the position of her spine, connected the broken nerves and blood vessels, and absorbed a trace of life energy from her Soul Connection with Aurora, allowing her injuries to recover quickly.

The form of 'Reaper Liberation' was destroyed, and it was still on cooldown. Although Hila did not intend to admit defeat, she had no choice but to face the reality that she could not defeat the Subduing Tree King and analyzed the current situation.

"Although I can still continue fighting the Subduing Tree King, I can't hold him back. This will allow him to escape…"

Hila's eyes were still filled with the desire to fight, but she was afraid of ruining Han Xiao's goal, so she could only suppress it.

"Does it hurt?"

Seeing that she did not continue to charge forward, the Subduing Tree King narrowed his eyes and did not pursue her.

Although he was left alone due to his carelessness, causing a large group of Beyond Grade As from the three Universal Civilizations to surround him, the many World Tree Supers returned in time and broke through the encirclement that had yet to take shape, dragging the situation back into a chaotic battle. Therefore, the Subduing Tree King was still in a good situation and was not surrounded.

The Subduing Tree King observed the situation and felt much more relaxed. Although Hila was not easy to deal with, she could not stop him at all. With his ability, as long as there was no Beyond Grade A like Black Star to hold him back, the chances of him escaping were still very high.

The retreat was stopped because of him, but he was still safe. The negative outcome was only sacrificing more of his comrades… Although it was a bit of a loss, as long as he, the Tree King, returned, these losses could still be accepted. After all, his hibernation would be much longer than the average World Tree expert.

"I didn't think that a simple probe would be so dangerous. I can't act casually next time."

The Subduing Tree King did not chase after Hila but retreated.

However, at this moment, a strong sense of danger suddenly appeared, as though a large hand had grabbed onto his heart.

The Subduing Tree King's expression changed slightly as he looked toward the source of the sensation.

A figure appeared beside Hila out of thin air. He did not look special on the outside and looked very ordinary. His expression was calm, but he exuded an evil and crazy aura that could not be hidden.

EsGod tilted his head and looked at the World Tree Roots beside the Subduing Tree King. He smiled and sighed.

"How many years has it been? I've finally seen this thing with my own eyes… Heh, if I hadn't seen it, I might not have been imprisoned for nearly a hundred years."

The Subduing Tree King frowned. He felt a strong threat from this stranger.

He had already blocked the mental fluctuations of outsiders, so he had no idea what EsGod was talking about. He turned around and ran without hesitation.

This unfamiliar Beyond Grade A that had suddenly appeared was not a simple character, and it would be difficult to determine the victor in a short time. If he was dragged here, it would be dangerous. Thus, the Subduing Tree King did not want to continue fighting.

However, before he could fly far, the smiling EsGod had already teleported in front of him.

The Subduing Tree King's eyes darkened, and a powerful flame condensed in his fist. He aimed at EsGod, planning to use the shockwave to force EsGod back.

A green Pugilist beam shot out with enough power to destroy an entire planet. However, EsGod only raised his hand casually and activated his Esper Ability, refracting the beam of light which then shattered a large number of starships like a laser.

"Esper?"

The Subduing Tree King's eyes flashed, but he did not plan to stop. He quickly closed the distance between them and punched out with his fist.

Bang!

The fist landed on EsGod's chest without any resistance, but all the power disappeared without a trace.

The Subduing Tree King's expression changed. Just as he was about to retract his fist, EsGod slapped him back. Green light gushed out and reflected the power of the Subduing Tree King's previous attack.

Boom!

A huge shockwave exploded in an instant, and the Subduing Tree King was sent flying.

He immediately stopped moving and looked at EsGod in shock. He removed his mental shield and could not help but ask,

"What ability is this?"

"Guess."

EsGod smiled.

Even with the support of his Esper Ability, he would still be injured if he took such a blow head-on. In the past, he would have to worry about the burden on his body, so he did not dare to do this. He rarely fought head-on. Now, his body was only temporary, and he did not have to care about any consequences at all.

EsGod had a rare feeling of having nothing to worry about. He hooked his finger at the Tree King.

"Come, let me see the ability of a Tree King."

"…Your ability is not bad. You can absorb my power and reflect it back, but you don't have the right to show off in front of me."

The Subduing Tree King quickly calmed down and looked at EsGod coldly.

In this short exchange, he had already realized how difficult EsGod was to deal with. He thought that EsGod's Esper Ability was to reflect attacks and that he was good at defense. He must be stalling him, he thought.

However, EsGod smiled.

"Is that so?"

Buzz!

The next moment, sixty to seventy doppelgangers separated from EsGod's main body. Each doppelganger had a different ability, and they all released the aura of a Beyond Grade A, instantly attracting the attention of everyone present.

"This is…"

Alarm bells rang in the Subduing Tree King's heart, and his expression changed drastically.

He had originally thought that this unknown expert would only be difficult to deal with and would only be able to stall him at most. The true danger came from the siege of the other Beyond Grade As… but at this moment, the sense of danger EsGod gave him was almost similar to Black Star's.

"So this civilization actually has such strong experts hidden…"

The Subduing Tree King's heart was heavy as he waited. Facing such an opponent, he did not dare to think about escaping.

The next second, EsGod and all his doppelgangers attacked at the same time. Various Esper Abilities formed a perfect combination.

In a direct confrontation, EsGod might not be the strongest among the Beyond Grade As, but due to his unparalleled abilities, he could be considered the peak among Beyond Grade As in techniques!

"Crap!"

An endless sense of oppression assaulted him, and the Subduing Tree King suddenly opened his eyes wide. He realized that he could not find any flaws, and he could not help but be shocked.

This powerful enemy in front of me has strength that exceeds my expectations. It seems like he has the strength to kill me alone ‽

Chapter 1407: Subduing Tree King: This Is All a Conspiracy, You Can't Fool Me!

A battle between the two erupted.

Dozens of doppelgangers with different Esper Abilities worked together seamlessly. As soon as they clashed, EsGod suppressed the Subduing Tree King. The combination of various Esper Abilities and combo attacks was dazzling, and the Subduing Tree King could not find his bearings.

When EsGod had just summoned his doppelgangers, the attention of all the Beyond Grade As on both sides had been drawn over. Seeing how miserable the Subduing Tree King was, everyone could not help but have strange looks on their faces.

"What a strong Esper. With so many Beyond Grade A doppelgangers assisting him in battle, although the Subduing Tree King king has the advantage in terms of frontal explosive power, all his actions are disrupted by the large number of doppelgangers. He isn't able to fight back at all and is completely passive…"

While wrestling with Herberlon, the Fortitude Tree King observed the battle situation on the Subduing Tree King's side. The more he watched, the more fearful he became.

The Subduing Tree King was being held back by a large number of EsGod doppelgangers and could not take control of the situation. He was like a weak teenager who was forced into an alley by a group of strong men. He was getting further and further away from the main force.

This powerful enemy did not have the overwhelming strength as Black Star did, but the Fortitude Tree King felt that he was equally difficult to deal with. If a Super with only one ability faced such an opponent, and the strength of the two parties did not have an insurmountable gap, then the Super would be at a natural disadvantage. A Pugilist who only knew how to hammer people was an example.

'Luckily, I'm a Mechanic…'

This thought appeared in the mind of the Fortitude Tree King.

On the other side, the Beyond Grade As of the three Universal Civilizations looked at EsGod with shock.

"EsGod is truly terrifying without any restraints. His true combat capability is so strong…"

Many people were shocked.

Most people knew EsGod's name, and many had fought him personally. However, EsGod's current combat strength was much stronger than they had imagined. He had never been this strong before.

"Looks like the Underworld suits him very well."

Manison's eyes flickered, and his tone was complicated.

EsGod had been imprisoned for close to a hundred years and wasted so many years. However, he was like a fish in water the moment he entered the Underworld. His stubbornness was gone, and his combat strength increased tremendously. While Manison had been training hard for so many years, due to Black Star's persistent attacks, his combat strength had actually regressed and was not as good as when he was at his peak. As one fell and another rose, he realized that he did not have the confidence to deal with the current EsGod.

This comparison made Manison feel sad for himself.

Seeing the battle between the two of them, everyone quickly took action after being shocked. The World Tree experts tried to provide support, and the morale of the three Universal Civilizations was greatly boosted. They became even more obstructive and did not allow the enemy to leave the team battle to help.

For the time being, the two of them could not be bothered with the actions of their teammates and focused on the battle.

...

The green meteor crashed through the battlefield, but it was like a bug that had fallen into a spider's web. All of its attacks were neutralized by EsGod's doppelgangers using all kinds of strange defensive Esper Abilities. The Subduing Tree King could not break out of EsGod's encirclement at all and could only be dragged along.

The Subduing Tree King launched another series of close-range attacks, but the fists glowing with green light easily passed through EsGod's body and did not hit anything.

Before he could do anything else, an EsGod doppelganger suddenly appeared from the side and floated over like smoke, turning into a curse and attaching itself to his body. His body suddenly became sore, and he could not even use half of his strength.

Before the Subduing Tree King could get rid of the negative status, the EsGod doppelgangers around him released different types of energy attacks.

Some shot out high-energy lasers from their eyes, some shot out 'X' shaped silver beams from their hands, some spun electromagnetic field lightning chains, and some pushed out dark red energy waves from their hands.

Bang! Bang! Bang!

Multicolored energy bombarded the Subduing Tree King's body. The light in the field expanded and exploded, causing the Subduing Tree King to tumble and fly backward.

Before he could fly far, the Subduing Tree King felt something tighten around his waist. It turned out that an EsGod's doppelganger was already waiting for him on the way and had grabbed him by the waist.

His reaction was fast, and he used a powerful elbow strike to hit the EsGod doppelganger's head. However, he did not manage to push the EsGod doppelganger back. The EsGod doppelganger's head suddenly became blurry, as if there was a high-frequency vibration, and all the kinetic energy was absorbed.

The next moment, this EsGod doppelganger pushed his hip, and the kinetic energy rebounded, not missing anything and rushing into the Subduing Tree King's body.

"Get lost!"

The Tree King's expression was twisted, his aura erupted and broke free from the control. He threw this EsGod doppelganger away.

However, before he could take any further action, more than ten mental attacks from different Esper Abilities suddenly exploded in his brain. Blood immediately spurted out from the Subduing Tree King's mouth and nose, and his soul was injured. A large number of mental debuffs appeared, making him dizzy.

He endured the pain and was just about to use the World Tree Roots to help him out when he realized that the World Tree Roots were already pinned down by another group of EsGod doppelgangers using space, force field, and other Esper Abilities.

"How many Esper Abilities do you have ‽"

The Subduing Tree King was completely shocked.

After fighting for such a long time, this opponent had already used more than a hundred Esper Abilities. Attack, defense, control, evasion… All sorts of abilities were present, like a bottomless abyss. There was simply no limit!

Since the start of the battle, EsGod had never used any big moves to inflict heavy injuries on him. However, this method was like eating away at his life, continuously inflicting light injuries on him time and time again. It was extremely disgusting.

"I never counted."

EsGod's tone was calm as he continued to attack.

His Esper Abilities were endless and could be said to be omnipotent. He completely controlled the tempo of the battle and did not give the Subduing Tree King any time to catch his breath. The lethality was secondary, but the strongest aspect was the almost perfect chain of control, almost playing the Subduing Tree King in his palms.

While enduring the concentrated attacks, the Subduing Tree King observed the situation with difficulty. Seeing that the main force was getting further and further away, his heart could not help but turn cold.

"My teammates are being held back, and it will be very difficult for them to rush over to support me. If I continue to fight him like this, my condition will continue to deteriorate, and the chances of me being able to escape will become increasingly slim…"

The Subduing Tree King's expression changed, and he suddenly had a flash of insight.

That's right, Black Star has yet to appear. How can he not participate in the battle? He must be secretly waiting for me!

'The Heart Tree King was tricked. Black Star knows that the other tree kings will be more vigilant, so he is hiding for the time being and pretending not to participate in the battle. He wants to make me lower my guard. When this Esper depletes my strength to a certain extent, he will suddenly attack and seal me as well!'

At this moment, the Subduing Tree King felt his mind clearing up.

That must be it. This is a trap!

'That was close. If I am not decisive enough, I will fall for his trick… I can't fall for his trick!'

He believed that he had seen through Black Star's plan and made up his mind.

EsGod did not know anything about the Subduing Tree King's mental state. Just as he was about to order his doppelgangers to launch another wave of attacks, a frightening energy was suddenly released from the Subduing Tree King's body.

"Hmm? This feeling is…"

EsGod's eyes narrowed, and he retreated without hesitation.

The Subduing Tree King had a fierce expression on his face, and his body suddenly emitted a bright light.

"I'd rather self-destruct than let you guys succeed!"

Bang!

His entire body exploded, and an intense energy shockwave spread out. The EsGod doppelgangers around were all sent flying, and the World Tree Roots turned into light fragments and disappeared.

The Subduing Tree King had always thought of himself as a rational Pugilist. His choice now was based on his own interests.

He was being held back by EsGod, and Black Star was watching him from the dark. His chances of escaping were slim, so he decided to self-destruct before his condition fell to a dangerous state.

On one hand, it would cause the enemy's sneak attack to fail, and on the other hand, his teammates did not have to come to support, thus minimizing losses.

Two birds with one stone!

Just one word, amazing!

Swoosh!

EsGod's figure flashed, avoiding the shockwave of the self-destruction.

He had finally met an opponent he wanted to fight to his heart's content, but he did not expect his opponent to explode just like that.

In his opinion, although the Subduing Tree King was at a disadvantage, he was still a Tree King level combatant. Even if he had the advantage, it would be extremely difficult to kill the other party. The current situation was far from the time to self-destruct…

"Forget it, at least the target is settled."

EsGod suddenly shook his head and laughed.

The situation of the battle was ever-changing. If the Subduing Tree King fought to the end, he might still have a chance to escape. However, since he decided to self-destruct now, there was no need to worry about any accidents.

Black Star's order was to kill this guy. Now that his opponent had killed himself, he would be saving his energy.

On the other side, the Fortitude Tree King sensed the self-destruction of the Subduing Tree King and was shocked.

He felt that although the situation was not good, there was still a chance. Why did he give up the hope of survival? He could still be saved…

The Fortitude Tree King immediately received the Subduing Tree King's mental fluctuations and understood what had happened.

"So, he did this because he was worried about being ambushed by the enemy…"

The Fortitude Tree King was speechless.

Due to the revival mechanism, this method of self-destructing to prevent the enemy from capturing them was very common for the World Tree members. The last time, the Subduing Tree King had died by self-destructing, but it was surprisingly similar this time as well…

The Fortitude Tree King did not know if he should say that the Subduing Tree King was decisive or a stupid teammate for falling in the same place twice.

With just one probing, they had lost a Tree King. He felt exhausted.

"Sigh, I can't say that it's a bad thing. He did die a little quickly, but it guaranteed that he won't be sealed like the Heart Tree King."

The Fortitude Tree King sighed in his heart. He could only think on the bright side… At least, the Subduing Tree King's sacrifice was not completely worthless. He managed to probe out the enemy's cards.

This unknown Esper who was not inferior to Black Star and that large-scale instant killing device that did not leave any traces must be the enemy's trump cards.

With this information, his side would be able to prepare in advance the next time they fought… He had finally gained some benefits from this battle. He felt that the Subduing Tree King's death was not a big loss.

It was a pity that this errand boy was gone. He could not slack off anymore.

With this in mind, the Fortitude Tree King no longer had any thoughts of fighting. He suppressed the annoyance in his heart and immediately ordered a retreat.

"Let's go!"

The World Tree experts stopped fighting and retreated. After paying a price, they finally returned to the main formation and were protected by the fleet again.

The Beyond Grade As of the three Universal Civilizations did not pursue after seeing this and retreated into the defense circle.

Seeing this, the expressions of the leaders of the three Universal Civilizations who were watching from afar relaxed, and they were secretly surprised.

Even before Black Star made a move, a portion of the Beyond Grade As had already given the World Tree experts a head-on blow, causing the enemies to suffer. In their eyes, this was undoubtedly the result of Black Star's training over the past ten years.

"Although Black Star is unpredictable, he is still reliable in this field."

"There shouldn't be anyone in the entire Galactic Society who knows how to cultivate Supers better than him. Black Star has contributed a lot to such a huge improvement. His ten years of hard work has given us an advantage in terms of individual strength."

The three of them were somewhat relieved.

...

At the same time.

In the base, Han Xiao raised his brows when he saw the Subduing Tree King explode into the most beautiful fireworks.

"He chose to self-destruct at this time… Could it be that he's afraid that I'll ambush him? Ha, isn't he being too smart for his own good? Among the Pugilists, your stupidity is quite unique."

Han Xiao could not help but laugh.

He did not plan to make a move, but he did not expect this inaction to scare the Subduing Tree King so much that he gave up his life… It could only be said that he had left quite a shadow in the World Tree's heart.

This time, without his help, the other teammates had caused the World Tree to suffer a loss. Without a doubt, they had improved tremendously, and Hila and the others could even hold their own. He was very satisfied.

Most importantly, a portion of the Revivors and new Beyond Grade As held back their urges until the end of the battle and did not appear to join the battle. This meant that the Holy Accord's Revivors were still not exposed, which was a good thing for Han Xiao.

The World Tree's attack was obviously just a test, while his side only revealed the tip of the iceberg and did not reveal all their cards. They killed the Subduing Tree King while holding back some of their trump cards. Sending this annoying guy back home to rest was quite worth it!

As such, the World Tree did not receive any more intelligence, and it still maintained the incorrect judgment of the Exchange tactic being effective.

Han Xiao rubbed his chin and smiled.

"It seems like you guys don't even have the right to enjoy this gift that I've prepared… That's good too. I'll give this surprise to you guys when you send out a powerful Tree King."

Chapter 1408: Fishing and Response

While Han Xiao was thinking, the individual forces of both sides had already retreated from the battlefield, but the fleets were still exchanging fire. The densely packed particle beams crisscrossed, shattering the shields and armor of countless battleships. All kinds of large war weapons took turns and the border defense circle blocked the World Tree vanguard team outside the territory with extreme firepower.

After beating the World Tree experts away, the Beyond Grade As temporarily retreated to the Siebert Fortress to rest. They returned to the resting room in high spirits and greeted Han Xiao who was watching the battle.

"Well done, everyone. This is a great victory!"

Han Xiao nodded with approval.

"Haha, I used to think that the World Tree experts were difficult to deal with, but now I feel they're just so-so." Sun Hunter jumped onto the table and laughed like a hero.

"Of course, you guys did not waste your time for nothing the past ten years. I've seen all your progress." Han Xiao smiled.

Hearing this, everyone could not help but smile. They were in a good mood.

When facing the enemy again, everyone realized that they had relaxed quite a bit. The enemy's improvement was limited, but their own improvement was huge. This was undoubtedly the result of His Excellency Black Star's ten years of special training.

The Beyond Grade As deeply experienced the growth brought by the special training and their gratitude toward Han Xiao grew deeper. They looked at Han Xiao with admiration and respect.

More than ten years ago, the World Tree had given them a lot of psychological pressure, and they felt that the World Tree was extremely difficult to deal with after a few exchanges. However, with Black Star as their confidence, they no longer had any psychological trauma.

After more than ten years of fermenting, Han Xiao had gained more respect. Because there was an intrinsic difference between a Transcendent and the Beyond Grade As, he had subtly improved the attitudes of many Beyond Grade As toward him. The way the Beyond Grade As viewed him now was similar to how Calamity Grades respected and supported the Beyond Grade As. The concept of superiors and subordinates was more deeply rooted in the hearts of the people and most Beyond Grade As had already accepted the changes in their relationship.

"It's all thanks to Aurora that we were able to achieve such a great victory," Beyoni said with admiration.

Hearing this, everyone started bootlicking.

There were no casualties in this victory and it was naturally Aurora's contribution that forced the World Tree experts back. Her healing power was stronger and more accurate than ten years ago and many Beyond Grade As were eager to suck up to her.

"It's alright. I just did my job."

Aurora was used to being humble, expressing her fear of being the MVP. At the same time, she secretly glanced at Han Xiao, anticipating his praise.

Han Xiao did not see the look in her eyes. He smiled and said, "Speaking of contributions, EsGod's killing this time… cough, forcing the Subduing Tree King to die is also a great contribution."

Everyone was stunned and turned to look at the calm EsGod.

Although EsGod had performed a meritorious deed, he had a grudge with many of the people present. Now that they were fighting side by side, everyone had a complicated impression of him.

EsGod glanced at Han Xiao. "If the Subduing Tree King was not afraid of your ambush, he would not have self-destructed so easily. Tree Kings indeed live up to their name. He's not that easy to deal with."

Hmm… although you're humble, when I think about how you played with the Subduing Tree King, I feel like you're posturing…

Han Xiao thought to himself and waved his hand. "You still contributed."

EsGod smiled and did not continue.

What was the use of contributions? He would not be allowed to revive. He did not care if he made any contributions. It was just a mission from the Underworld.

At this moment, Kasuyi rubbed his chin and said, "It's a pity that the Subduing Tree King self-destructed too decisively, causing the enemy to retreat in time. We did not cause more casualties to the enemy, and we only managed to kill about ten enemy Beyond Grade As. Among them, only the Subduing Tree King was a powerful individual."

"This isn't a big problem. It might be a good thing if we look at it from another perspective." Han Xiao waved his hand and smiled. "Think about it, since the Subduing Tree King died in battle, the ones in charge of the overall situation will have to be changed. If we had heavily injured their Beyond Grade As in this wave, then even if the next Tree King wants to fight, he probably won't have enough force. Now that we have left the World Tree with a relatively intact high-level strength, the new Tree King will have the chips to fight again in a short period."

"There's such an explanation?" Kasuyi was surprised.

"What's so strange about that? My goal is to seal a sufficiently powerful Tree King. If they shrink back, how am I going to attack? I hoped you guys wouldn't seriously injure the enemy this time. This is called baiting the big fish. Killing the Subduing Tree King is enough for now."

Han Xiao nodded.

Hearing this, one of the revivors laughed and said, "Haha, it's a good thing we didn't join the battle this time, or we would have ruined your plan."

"Of course, we can't just reveal all our trump cards in just a probing battle. We will catch them off guard next time."

Han Xiao smiled.

The Revivors and some of the new Beyond Grade As originally felt that it was a pity that they did not make a move this time, but they were relieved now and focused on the big picture.

They gathered together and analyzed the results of the battle for a while before dispersing to do their own things. From time to time, they would look up at the live broadcast of the battle. At this moment, they had the upper hand, so there was no need for them to attack again.

Han Xiao chatted with Ames and browsed through the deployment of the Galactic Alliance Army. Suddenly, he felt a squeeze beside him. Jotina walked over and sat beside him.

Han Xiao turned around and saw Jotina staring at him with a burning gaze, as though she wanted to swallow him alive.

"What are you doing now?" Han Xiao raised his brows.

"I want to stay by your side." Jotina licked her lips.

"Then sit properly. Don't come close."

Han Xiao was helpless.

He knew that Jotina had always been craving for his body and had rejected her many times. However, she had never given up and kept pestering him.

In the past, Jotina would restrain herself because of the huge gap between them, but ever since she became a Beyond Grade A, she became more and more unrestrained. Especially when everyone was on standby at the frontlines, this woman kept harassing him.

"No, I want to lean on you." Jotina did not hide anything and hugged his arm boldly.

Han Xiao had no choice but to pull his arm out. However, Jotina leaned her head on his chest and wrapped her arms around his waist.

"Don't you think this is the wrong time? Can't you be mindful of your image?"

Han Xiao's mouth twitched. After all, Jotina was a Beyond Grade A who was willing to stay in the army, so it was not convenient for him to beat her up.

"It's alright, you guys continue." The Beyond Grade As glanced over, not surprised at all. They were already used to it.

"…Do you think I'm air?"

Ames looked at the two of them and could not take it anymore.

It would have been fine if Jotina had sat on Han Xiao's other side, but this woman had snatched her seat and pushed her to the side. Wasn't this a provocation?

"This is your exclusive seat? Can't I sit here?" Jotina looked back at her with hostility.

Ames could not be bothered with her. This was not the first time Jotina had targeted her, and she was speechless.

She crossed her arms and looked at Han Xiao. "You look very comfortable."

"Of course not."

Han Xiao shook his head and pushed Jotina away. He then sat down on the other side of Ames and dragged Lagi to his side.

Seeing this, Jotina snorted and did not move closer. She turned around and sat at the side, glaring at him.

Ames patted Han Xiao's chest and said with a smile that was not a smile, "You're very popular now. Many people want to snatch you away from me. Are you going to have a new lover one day?"

Han Xiao stroked his chin and pretended to tease. "I think that the reason why people are coveting me is because there are gaps in our relationship. If we form a family and have offspring, others will know better and give up."

"…We'll see."

Ames leaned her head on Han Xiao's shoulder and replied softly.

Their relationship had long been made public, and this was not the first time Black Star had brought up the topic of having offspring. However, if she simply did not want to have children, how troublesome would that be? It was just that after more than ten years, Ames' tone had also changed from firm rejection to hesitation. The 'threat' from Jotina made her waver more and more.

Han Xiao did not insist.

In the past few years, he had tried to cultivate his descendants with his life energy and bioengineering. However, he realized that there were many flaws in the life-form created by such gene cultivation. They could not inherit the three inherited talents and could not achieve the expected effect. Thus, his plan to quickly expand the race could only be put on hold.

Since he could not use the Mechanic method, he could only rely on fertilization.

Beep beep!

At this moment, his communicator rang.

Han Xiao took it out and took a look. It was a message from the person in charge of the secondary dimension expedition outpost.

The content was simple, but it made Han Xiao's pupils contract.

"Your Excellency Black Star, the Abnormal Creature Egg that you told me to pay attention to has shown changes. Please come quickly."

More than ten years ago, Han Xiao had reached a consensus with the Realmless King. He had borrowed part of the territory and transformed it into the outpost of the secondary dimension expeditionary army of the three Universal Civilizations. They had worked together for a long time.

The so-called Abnormal Creature Egg was the Pivotal Snake Egg. Han Xiao had specially instructed the person in charge of the expedition outpost to monitor it. It had not changed much in the past ten years and this was the first time something had happened.

"I have something to do, so I'll be leaving for a while. Kasuyi will temporarily give the orders on my behalf."

Han Xiao stood up without hesitation and left after changing into the King.

...

On the other side, World Tree Base, Tree King Palace.

Fortitude Tree King was seated on the throne, two rays of light appeared on the other two empty seats, quickly turning into the figures of the Ancestral Tree King and Secret Tree King.

As soon as he regained his physical body, the Secret Tree King said impatiently,

"How are you guys fighting? Why is the Subduing Tree King dead again?"

"Just a small accident."

The Fortitude Tree King had always been at odds with him.

The Secret Tree King snorted. "Accident? Heh, don't make excuses for your incompetence. Look at your results. You participated in the battle twice and lost the Heart Tree King and the Subduing Tree King respectively. You're simply embarrassing us."

"It's different this time. The enemy has revealed a new trump card. The reason the Subduing Tree King self-destructed so decisively is because of the Heart Tree King's case," the Fortitude Tree King retorted.

"As a Tree King, he died so easily. I don't think he deserves the Tree King Crown. It would be better if we change to someone else," the Secret Tree King mocked.

"Alright, stop arguing. There's no problem with the Subduing Tree King's choice. At least he was not sealed by the enemy…"

At this time, the Ancestral Tree King raised his hand and stopped the two of them from arguing.

Although his tone was calm, he was actually feeling depressed. The Subduing Tree King had died too quickly. He had practically self-destructed the moment he left the base. If not for the fact that replacing a Tree King was more troublesome, he really wanted to dismiss the Subduing Tree King.

Hearing this, the Fortitude Tree King did not argue and continued, "The Subduing Tree King's sacrifice is worth it. He has probed out a new strong enemy for us…"

He shared the battle details with the two of them, emphasizing EsGod's strength.

The Ancestral Tree King narrowed his eyes and said,

"To think that the enemy still has such a strong opponent… Including Herberlon, there are already three people who have the strength of a Tree King. There's no lack of people among the other Supers who can fight against a Tree King. Their individual strengths are too developed, and we might not have the advantage."

"It's mainly because the experts from the other races are unable to take action. Otherwise, it would be much easier." The Fortitude Tree King was helpless.

Black Star's existence had directly crippled a large group of their foreign experts, and they did not have all the high-level combatants that could enter the battlefield. Otherwise, they would not have been so passive.

The Ancestral Tree King nodded. "Yes, that's true. Our only advantage right now is the endless revivals. However, the opponent's recovery-type Esper is not simple. Although the Exchange tactic is effective, it's not easy to use it… Comparatively, recovering on the spot is considered immediate combat power for them, but we're only using it after the battle. It won't help much in a head-on battle, so we're at a disadvantage."

"Then what should we do?"

"Hmm, our advantage is that the cost of trial and error is close to zero. We can try a few more times like today, so we don't have to care too much about the casualties. As long as we can obtain more information about the enemy, it will be worth it."

The Ancestral Tree King said.

The Fortitude Tree King coughed and said, "However, ordinary probing won't make the enemy feel pressured. I think it's better for us to attack together."

The Ancestral Tree King did not doubt him. He thought for a while and said, "You're right. Today, two Tree Kings were at a disadvantage. It seems like only the three of us together can force out the enemy's strength. It would be best if we can kill that Esper."

"I think the descent of the Tree God is more reliable…" the Fortitude Tree King suggested.

The Ancestral Tree King frowned slightly and shook his head. "The Heart Tree King's Tree King Crown is gone. Even if we use the Tree God's Descent, it won't be complete. Furthermore… I don't like that feeling."

If it was not necessary, he would not be willing to use the Tree God's Descent. This was not a comfortable thing.

The Fortitude Tree King agreed and changed the topic.

"By the way, the enemy has built a defensive circle at the border, and it seems like they destroyed quite a few Star Clusters. What do you plan to do?"

The Ancestral Tree King did not mind and casually said,

"That's normal. Since they know our advantage, they will naturally make such a choice… Think of a way to steal their intel and confirm the enemy's territory. It's best to obtain the coordinates of the other Star Fields and have our troops jump over to open up a new battlefront, avoiding their border defense circle.

Also, they seem to be looking for the main body of the mother tree. I don't know where they got this information from, but we need to search for their traces in the secondary dimension. Also, find a way to confirm the entrance of the enemy civilization into the secondary dimension and open up the secondary dimension battlefront."

Now was not the time to stop the war. Since they were near the enemy's territory, there were more options to attack. Compared to attacking the Flickering World's defense circle, the Ancestral Tree King was more inclined to gathering intelligence and opening up more battlefronts to amplify the World Tree's advantage.

"Understood."

The Fortitude Tree King nodded vigorously.

He had deliberately emphasized how difficult it was to deal with the enemy so that he could pull the other two Kings into the team. This way, he would not have to worry alone. Perfect!

Chapter 1409: Special Sense, Birth of a Pivotal Snake

While the three tree kings were discussing, they suddenly paused at the same time and fell silent. They all sensed a message from the mother tree's consciousness.

A strange light flashed across the Ancestral Tree King's eyes as he slowly said,

"Mother tree sensed that another natural enemy has appeared and told us to kill it."

"Is it that strange creature again? It's actually not extinct." The Secret Tree King was a little interested.

The Ancestral Tree Dynasty nodded. "Hmm, the secondary dimension is suitable for you. Go and lead our kindred to resolve this matter. Try to find its location before the natural enemy enters adulthood."

"I'll try my best." The Secret Tree King did not comment further.

This was not the first time the World Tree had discovered a natural enemy. In the early years of the civilization, there were records of natural enemies invading.

The restraining relationship between the two sides came from the abnormal entanglement at the information state level. There was a two-way connection, so the World Tree Civilization had always paid attention to the existence of natural enemies.

The World Tree's ability to sense its natural enemy was divided into two phases. When the natural enemy was in its infancy, the World Tree would only know of its existence and would not be able to sense its exact location. As the natural enemy gradually matured, the sense towards it would also become stronger. When any natural enemy entered adulthood, the World Tree would be able to track their location accurately to kill them, eliminating a large number of natural enemies.

However, the World Tree could only sense its natural enemy after it was born, and it could not discover the embryo that the natural enemy had given birth to. Therefore, it had never been able to kill all of them. In the end, there were still some that managed to slip through the net, so it could only settle for the next best thing — taking the initiative to kill the infants.

In fact, the World Tree had always been focused on expanding in the secondary dimension, and part of the reason was that it was dedicated to exterminating its natural enemy. Once it sensed something, it would immediately inform the Tree Kings to kill the younglings of its natural enemy as soon as possible and not allow its natural enemy to enter adulthood. This was a very high priority, and only the Tree Kings knew of the details.

The Fortitude Tree King could not help but ask, "What about the frontline war?"

"Let's first eliminate the mother tree's natural enemy. It seems like our operation will have to be postponed." The Ancestral Tree King glanced at him, thought for a moment, and added, "Don't forget to water the Subduing Tree King."

...

Secondary Dimension World, expeditionary army outpost.

A huge ring-shaped teleportation gate was suspended in the dimensional space. This was the gate that the three Universal Civilizations used to enter and exit from the main universe. There were many secondary dimension fortresses around it, and groups of exploration teams came and went.

With a flash of light, Han Xiao's figure appeared on the special transportation platform.

The person in charge of the outpost was already waiting there. He immediately came forward.

"Your Excellency Black Star, you're finally here."

"How's the situation now?" Han Xiao looked at him and asked.

"That embryo's absorption rate of dimension energy suddenly increased by a million times. I don't know if it's good or bad. You should go take a look yourself. I've already prepared the vehicle for you."

"Alright… By the way, how did the Realmless King react?"

"He went there a step earlier. He should be observing the changes in the embryo at a close distance."

"Alright, I'll go too."

Han Xiao nodded.

After more than ten years of development, the secondary dimension that the Realmless King had lent out had already been modified by the three Universal Civilizations. Currently, the three Universal Civilizations were using this outpost as a springboard to greatly increase the expeditionary army's strength.

Furthermore, the three Universal Civilizations used their tradition of being hooligans to convince the Realmless King to take out more territories for them to build their bases. Currently, this area had already become a 'shallow dimension', where the three Universal Civilizations could enter and leave to and from the main universe directly.

Even if the Realmless King was unwilling to provoke the World Tree, he was now tied to the same war chariot by the three Universal Civilizations.

Han Xiao sat on the carrier, set the coordinates of the dimension, and started the engine. The heavy particle thruster spewed out raging flames and quickly turned into an invisible tail stream. The conventional engine transitioned to the dimensional shuttle engine, accelerated to the critical point, and disappeared from the spot, performing a hyperdrive jump.

The shuttle entered a colorful tunnel. Not long after, the carrier suddenly shook, and the light outside the window disappeared, turning into a black secondary dimension space. They had arrived at their destination.

A grayish-white embryo floated in the middle of the dimension, guarded by a large number of mechanical troops.

The projection of the Realmless King was right beside him. When it sensed the vehicle entering, it could not help but turn around. When it realized that it was Han Xiao, it approached him.

"Black Star, you're here too."

"Tell me about the situation." Han Xiao flew to his side.

"The energy of this dimension is flowing into the embryo at an extremely high speed. If this continues, it will collapse very soon. I feel that this embryo is about to be born…" the Realmless King explained.

Han Xiao nodded and looked at the embryo.

The gray fog under the membrane was originally very stable, but at this time, it was like boiling water, and it was fluctuating wildly. The long black shadows inside were becoming more and more distinct, attacking the membrane from the inside, causing bumps to appear on the embryo.

In Han Xiao's senses, this embryo seemed to have turned into an energy black hole. The quality, space, and energy of this secondary dimension were all collapsing toward the embryo and being devoured.

When some eggs were born, they would eat the eggshells to replenish their nutrition. In Han Xiao's opinion, the second dimension where the Pivotal Snake Egg drained its energy from, like a parasite, was similar.

Not long after, the secondary dimension became riddled with holes. The remaining debris was quickly eaten up by the Pivotal Snake Egg, and the embryo was directly exposed in the space storm.

Han Xiao had already retracted his mechanical army. He did not interfere with the changes of the Pivotal Snake Egg and watched from the side with the Realmless King.

Chi!

The membrane suddenly split open, and the grayish-white fog inside leaked out, spreading outwards. The surrounding chaotic space stream could not penetrate this layer of fog.

Han Xiao pulled over a cloud of fog and analyzed it. He realized that the substance formed by this fog was a special biological particle that could isolate space storms and seemed to have the ability to shatter through space, allowing one to travel through dimensions.

The membrane quickly shriveled, but the fog was still increasing, covering the appearance of the Pivotal Snake. Only a black shadow could be seen in the gray fog, like a dragon hiding in the clouds.

Right at this moment, the Pivotal Snake suddenly flew in the opposite direction of the two of them.

"Is he trying to escape?"

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled, and with a wave of his hand, the space device locked onto the Pivotal Snake, preventing it from moving.

He slowly approached and flew into the gray fog. The interface immediately indicated that he had received continuous attacks. The surrounding gray fog was actively repelling outsiders, but the damage was too low and could not break through his defense. He did not lose any health at all.

Entering the center of the gray fog, Han Xiao finally saw the true appearance of the Pivotal Snake…

This was an enormous dark gold snake-shaped creature. It did not have an outer carapace, and its entire body was gleaming with a metallic luster. Its skin was constantly releasing more gray fog. This seemed to be something that was automatically generated by it, so it should be an external protective layer. It had two pairs of enormous membranous wings on its back and a pair of sharp claws on its abdomen. Its head looked like a snake's head, but it did not have a mouth or nose, only a pair of cold golden vertical pupils.

Compared to the Space Louse, the Pivotal Snake looked much more beautiful.

"Although it's called a snake, it looks more like a dragon…"

Han Xiao thought to himself. He took out his psychic communication device and tried to communicate with the Pivotal Snake.

Han Xiao could feel the Pivotal Snake's cold and aloof emotions, but it did not respond to his probing.

'Eh, newborn animals treat the first creature they meet as their parents. Isn't this how they act…

Even if it's not like this, with my charisma and affinity, this little animal shouldn't be so cold to me…'

Han Xiao was curious and tried a few more times. However, the Pivotal Snake only stared at him with its cold golden eyes and did not reply. It was as though it was extremely wary of the outside world.

Seeing this, he stopped communicating and directly poked the Pivotal Snake.

The next moment, the other party's attributes popped up on the interface. Han Xiao quickly browsed through and was stunned.

In the Pivotal Snake's stats window, there was a talent ability that could sense the World Tree's main body. However, it was currently in a gray frozen state, and the ability introduction stated that it would only be activated when it reached adulthood. At this time, the Pivotal Snake was still a hatchling.

"Such talent! As expected of the World Tree's nemesis!"

Han Xiao was shocked and immediately became surprised.

This was a pleasant surprise. This meant that the three Universal Civilizations had a stable way of finding the World Tree's main body. They no longer had to place all their hopes on luck!

Hmm, that doesn't seem right. If not for Harrison, he wouldn't have been able to touch the Realmless King, much less the Pivotal Snake Egg…

In the end, it was all because of Harrison's luck?!

"His Luck Glow is stronger than I thought…"

Han Xiao was speechless, and his brain immediately started thinking.

He did not expect the Pivotal Snake to have such an ability, which meant that his plan could be changed. With such a trump card, the most important thing now was to nurture the Pivotal Snake infant and let it enter adulthood as soon as possible. This way, he could directly mess with the World Tree's heart like a playboy.

"However, the expeditionary army cannot pause its actions. Who knows how long it will take for the Pivotal Snake to reach adulthood…"

Han Xiao made up his mind and continued trying to communicate with the Pivotal Snake. However, the Pivotal Snake hatchling still did not respond. It seemed like it would do whatever it wanted, and Han Xiao did not know what to do with it. After all, this was the first time he had come into contact with a Pivotal Snake. He wondered if all newborn Pivotal Snakes were like this.

He did not dare to deactivate his control over the Pivotal Snake hatchling either. Judging from how this thing ran away the moment it was born, it was most likely going to die if he let it go.

Han Xiao had no choice but to put the communication problem aside for the time being. He grabbed the Pivotal Snake and walked to the Realmless King's side.

"It's a very strange creature that's very useful to me. It feeds on secondary dimensions. Since you're called the Lord of a Million Dimensions, I'll leave the feeding mission to you."

The Realmless King's face fell when he heard this.

Those secondary dimensions were all territories that he had collected. Lending them to the three Universal Civilizations was already very depressing, and now he even wanted to feed them to this creature? Do you really think I'm a dog that you can slaughter as you please?!

Seeing that he did not respond, Han Xiao raised his brows. "You're not willing?"

"…I'm honored." The Realmless King agreed to Han Xiao's unreasonable request without hesitation.

Stop talking, I'm a coward.

"Don't worry, I won't let you feed them for nothing. The three Universal Civilizations will give you some main universe materials in exchange."

Han Xiao smiled and comforted him.

Since the Realmless King liked to collect trash, the three Universal Civilizations would definitely not be stingy with this cost. After all, what they did not lack the most was trash.

After successfully persuading the Realmless King to be generous, Han Xiao turned to look at the Pivotal Snake hatchling again. His eyes sparkled, as though he had seen the light of hope.

The Pivot Snake lowered its head and looked at him. Its golden eyes flashed with a human-like look of rejection as if it was a prisoner facing a guard.

Sensing this emotion, Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

"My first impression of it isn't too good. Could it be that the Pivotal Snake loves freedom? It seems like raising this creature won't be that easy."

Chapter 1410: Hidden Change

Han Xiao did not continue to stare at the Pivotal Snake. He left an Observer's Mark and summoned two apostles and a group of elite mechanical soldiers to act as bodyguards. Only then did he bring it back to the outpost to inform the leaders of the three Universal Civilizations.

The leaders of the three Universal Civilizations were overjoyed when they learned about the situation of the Pivotal Snake. They immediately told the expeditionary army to cooperate with the Realmless King to nurture the Pivotal Snake's infant and provide strict protection. They also treated the Pivotal Snake's abilities as top secret.

The Pivotal Snake's infant was extremely wary of the outside world, but it was born with the desire to absorb more nutrients. The Pivotal Snake only calmed down a little when the Realmless King unwillingly took out a new secondary dimension to feed it. It started to absorb the dimension energy and ate obediently.

Han Xiao did not leave immediately. Instead, he stayed there for a while and tried to communicate. However, the Pivotal Snake had always ignored the others, so he had no choice but to temporarily give up on the idea of gaining Favorability.

After staying in the secondary dimension world for seven to eight days, the battle on the frontlines also came to an end. The World Tree once again lost the battle, and the Flickering World border defense circle repelled the enemy. The two sides were still in a stalemate.

The results of this battle were announced by the three Universal Civilizations, and the victory at the individual strength aspect was emphasized. The galactic residents were overjoyed, and their sense of security increased greatly. Their confidence in the war increased to a certain extent.

The frontline battle report also spread to the Holy Accord Organization, causing many of the Holy Accord Revivors to exclaim.

"The strength of the Beyond Grade A Association is getting stronger. They don't even need to use their full strength to kill a Tree King."

"I can tell that they're much stronger than ten years ago. So remarkable. Sigh, I also wanted to participate in Black Star's training."

"It's a pity we can't expose ourselves easily…"

Many of the Holy Accord Revivors sighed with complicated expressions.

These revived individuals who lived in seclusion in the Holy Accord did not appear in the outside world, and they were still unregistered. Although they had already reached an agreement with Han Xiao to take action when the time came, they had not been summoned yet. They could only continue to hide their existence in the Holy Accord and not participate in the training.

Some of them originally wanted to participate, but Han Xiao did not allow them to be exposed, so they could only give up. Having lost this opportunity, they could not help but feel regretful. If they had known that they would have to participate in the war anyway, they would have chosen to leave their seclusion together with the rest of the revivors at the start.

"Hey, Oathkeeper, when can we join the battle?" someone could not help but ask.

Oathkeeper was expressionless as he said coldly,

"Don't ask me. My words don't count."

"Then hurry Black Star more. Otherwise, what's the use of you?"

"..."

Oathkeeper took a deep breath and calmed himself down.

Ever since Black Star became a Transcendent, his leadership position in the Holy Accord organization existed in name only. He had no choice but to ask Black Star for his opinion in almost everything.

What was even more outrageous was that these snobbish Holy Accord Revivors used to be grateful to him when they just revived and respected him. Now that a new generation had replaced the old, these people had all become Black Star's lackeys and did not give any regards to him, the leader of the organization in name. It was seriously infuriating.

However, Black Star was the only Transcendent in the current Galactic Society, so what else could he do? Oathkeeper had already given up on competing with Black Star. His subordinate position was becoming more stable, and he had to accept reality.

One of the Holy Accord Revivors rubbed his hands and said with a deep voice, "Black Star has given the three Universal Civilizations such a huge advantage. According to the current situation, we might not even have the chance to make a move. Just the association and the direct descendants of the civilizations are enough to deal with the high-level combatants of the enemy… With Black Star's personality, he might continue to hide our existence as a trump card if he can suppress the enemy."

"That makes sense. Doesn't that mean we can enjoy the chance to revive in the Sanctum for free?"

Everyone's eyes lit up.

Secondary dimension world, World Tree territory.

Numerous members of the World Tree were gathered there, and every spaceship was glowing with green light.

"The search force has been assembled. Please give instructions."

In the bridge of the flagship, the Secret Tree King was inspecting the troops. An executive officer walked over quickly and reported in a low voice.

The Tree King nodded and said casually, "Since everyone is here, let's go."

In order to find the mother tree's natural enemy, he had specially come to the secondary dimension world to manage the situation and spent a few days gathering a large number of Blessed Races.

Although the nemesis had not been born for long and Mother Tree's perception was vague, the World Tree was extremely powerful in the secondary dimension. It had countless troops stationed there, and it was not afraid of spending time to find a needle in a haystack.

At this time, the Secret Tree King thought of something and sneered.

"By the way, the enemy seems to have been searching for the main body of the mother tree. We can also solve this matter by capturing the enemy's team and obtaining their intelligence."

"Understood."

The order was quickly passed down, and the search fleet formed by the World Tree's Blessed Races started moving, turning into streams of light and scattering.

Seeing this, the Secret Tree King narrowed his eyes, raised his palm, and dense magic power flashed between his fingers.

He decided to take action personally this time. If he was lucky enough to meet the enemy's fleet in the secondary dimension, he would not let any of them escape.

In a desolate universe belt in the explored universe.

A small spaceship slowly landed on a desolate planet. The ground cracked open automatically, revealing a parking orbit.

The spaceship smoothly connected with the orbit, moved in, and disappeared into the dark hole. Very soon, the hole closed again, and the disguise was restored.

After gliding in the darkness for a while, the spaceship finally stopped and arrived at a secret underground base.

The hatch slid open, and a figure walked out.

On the other side, another person was already waiting on the platform. When he saw the person, he said in a deep voice,

"How's the situation outside?"

"Another Tree King has been killed. The three Universal Civilizations and the World Tree are in a stalemate. According to this trend, the World Tree will not be able to break through the border defense circle for a very long time."

"Is that so… it seems like the three Universal Civilizations are still very tenacious. With Black Star around, it's still unknown who will win."

"Right now, the World Tree's biggest weakness is the lack of intelligence. If they get enough intelligence, the situation will change drastically… What did the superiors say?"

"Our superiors have already given orders for us to find a way to provide information about the galactic society to the World Tree while hiding ourselves. The most important thing is to provide the coordinates of the various Star Fields controlled by the three Universal Civilizations so that the World Tree can obtain a detailed strategic map… The Star Alliance has also agreed to this operation. They have always wanted to get rid of the threat of the three Universal Civilizations. After observing for so long, they have finally found a perfect opportunity to destroy them with a borrowed knife."

"Phew, I can't remember how many years I've been hiding here. I can finally take revenge… It's time for the three Universal Civilizations to pay the price for what they did back then!"

The two of them had strong hostility toward the three Universal Civilizations.

Chapter 1411: Lurkers

In the unexplored universe, Star Alliance capital.

Savignes quickly walked into the office of the Star Alliance Leader.

The Star Alliance Leader was waiting for him. Seeing him walk into the room, he put down the report in his hand, looked up, and slowly said,

"How's the situation?"

"I've already sent out the instructions. The lurkers will take action soon," Savignes said with a deep voice.

"Hmm, this chess piece has been set up for so many years. Now is the time for them to show their value." The Star Alliance Leader paused for a moment before changing the topic. "However, we have to pay attention to the method of providing intelligence. Everything needs to be done under the premise of our existence being hidden. The three Universal Civilizations and the World Tree are both huge threats. If our existence is exposed to them, the dark clouds of war will cover us too. With our strength, it would be beyond our capabilities no matter which side we fight head-on."

"Don't worry, we're all in this together. We won't joke about the safety of the Star Alliance," Savignes said solemnly.

"Hmm, you guys have been with the Star Alliance for many years, and we are already one. This operation is not only to eliminate potential threats but also for your revenge." The Star Alliance Leader nodded.

"That's right. Back then, we were defeated by the three Universal Civilizations, and only a few of our people managed to escape. It was almost impossible for us to survive, and we became a wandering civilization in the universe. If not for encountering the Star Alliance's team, our civilization might have died long ago. To this day, we are thankful to the Star Alliance for their help."

Savignes lowered his head and said respectfully.

When the Lore Civilization had been defeated, his ancestors had gathered the remaining members of their race and united them. It had been difficult for them to survive. Now, Savignes had taken over the authority of his predecessors and was the current leader of the Lore Civilization.

The history of the Lore Civilization was quite ancient, it was once a member of the explored universe. It was one of the competitors in the exploration era war. Unfortunately, it lost the war, and the civilization was destroyed. Its homeland fell, and only a few survivors escaped on spaceships. Because they were worried about being eliminated, they decided to enter the unexplored universe and travel far away, becoming wanderers of the universe.

After many twists and turns in the wormhole, this group of wanderers happened to arrive in the Star Alliance's territory.

The Star Alliance was a large joint civilization formed by forty-six civilizations. They lived quietly in a corner of the unexplored universe. By chance, they picked up this group of wanderers, and the intelligence brought by the Lore Civilization immediately attracted their attention.

This was the first time the Star Alliance had heard of the existence of a powerful civilization outside their territory. The intelligence provided by the Lore Civilization showed that the three Universal Civilizations were strong enough to destroy the entire Star Alliance, which made the Star Alliance extremely fearful and vigilant. In their eyes, the three Universal Civilizations could bring a calamity to the Star Alliance at any time, and swallowing them up was a huge hidden danger that made them unable to sleep or eat in peace.

Facing an unfamiliar and powerful civilization, the Star Alliance did not dare expose their existence to communicate with the other party. They could only observe silently. Under normal circumstances, even if the Star Alliance knew that there were strong enemies around, they would be helpless. However, the Lore Civilization provided them with a way.

When the wanderers escaped from their homeland, they had brought along a large number of coordinates. This was a priceless fortune, and the Star Alliance saw an opportunity.

Based on this information, the upper echelons of the Star Alliance finally decided on a strategic operation called the 'Observer's Plan'. They sent out lurkers to the explored universe through wormholes. They hid their identities, gathered intelligence, and waited for an opportunity while monitoring the actions of the three Universal Civilizations.

The three Universal Civilizations did not have an Information Form warning network like the World Tree. As their territory was extremely large, there would always be gaps in the screening and security mechanisms. As long as the outsiders operated properly, they would be able to successfully infiltrate the three Universal Civilizations. In Han Xiao's previous life, the World Tree had been hiding like this for many years, gathering enough intelligence before launching a full-scale attack on the three Universal Civilizations.

The Star Alliance knew their limits, and they did not think that their small body would be able to withstand the three Universal Civilizations' attacks. Thus, they only let the lurkers observe and not take part in any other actions. They were like the lowest level galactic hackers, completely inconspicuous. They only searched for public intelligence on the internet and did not try to obtain any secrets. They were extremely cautious, which was why they were able to remain hidden until now and watch the development of the three Universal Civilizations.

After receiving repeated checks from the Star Alliance, the Lore Civilization finally became a new member. They were able to procreate, but they never forgot their history, and always thought about revenge. They cooperated with the Observer's Plan and helped the Star Alliance hide in the explored universe.

This time, the three Universal Civilizations were invaded by the World Tree, which gave the Star Alliance a hope of eliminating the threat. They could not defeat the three Universal Civilizations themselves, so they decided to add fuel to the fire.

The Star Alliance Leader rubbed the back of his hand and said, "We can use the World Tree to get rid of the three Universal Civilizations, but the World Tree itself is a new threat. The ideal situation is for both of them to suffer, so we can take advantage."

Savignes nodded heavily. "The three Universal Civilizations' technology level is very high. If we can take over their achievements, we will be able to advance quickly."

"However, this is very risky, and we might expose ourselves. We have to think about it carefully… If there's really a chance, we can't miss it."

The eyes of the Star Alliance Leader flickered. He naturally coveted the technological achievements accumulated by the three Universal Civilizations. Although the risk was high, the benefits were equally tempting.

The three Universal Civilizations had stabilized the situation and blocked the World Tree outside. This was not what the Star Alliance wanted to see. Destroying the good situation of the three Universal Civilizations and bringing the flames of war into the entire galactic society to cause chaos was in line with this third party's interests.

The Star Alliance Leader did not mind taking advantage of the situation. Under the premise of hiding their identity, they secretly participated in this feast.

Secondary dimension world.

A team of three Universal Civilizations' expedition army was traveling in the secondary dimension, recording the coordinates.

"This place is not far from the base dimension of the World Tree, and Blessed Race members might appear. Keep your spirits up and prepare to retreat at any time."

In the cockpit, the commander stared at the radar with a serious tone.

In the past few years, as the expedition army explored deeper and deeper, the encounters with the World Tree Blessed Races became more frequent. Fortunately, they ran fast enough, and most of the time, there were no accidents.

However, fleeing the danger was not always an option. The search network of the Blessed Race was extremely dense, and the expeditionary army did not wish to start a conflict. Thus, the exploration progress became slower and slower and there were not many loopholes to exploit.

"If this goes on, I don't know when we will get results. The World Tree has already reached our territory. We don't have much time left…"

The commander sighed.

"Wuwuwu—"

Suddenly, an ear-piercing alarm sounded on the radar. It was like a thunderclap, scaring everyone.

Not far away, cracks suddenly appeared on the dimensional barrier, and green streams of light shot over.

"It's the World Tree Blessed Races! Retreat!"

The commander's expression changed.

The expedition team immediately turned around and locked onto the evacuation route. The shuttle engine buzzed and turned into a stream of light, escaping from this dimension into another.

However, before the expedition team could come to a stop, the alarm on the radar sounded again, and the space cracks opened. Another group of World Tree Blessed Race members was rushing over.

"This is a premeditated attack!"

The commander immediately reacted. With a heavy expression, he commanded the fleet to continue fleeing.

The fleet passed through five secondary dimensions in a row, with the World Tree Blessed Races following closely behind them.

Suddenly, the commander stopped running. He took a deep breath and made up his mind.

"Prepare to self-destruct."

Hearing this, the crew members in the bridge all felt a chill in their hearts. They did not speak or object, only silently activating the self-destruct sequence.

The soldiers of the three Universal Civilizations could not revive as they wished like the World Tree. Without the protection of the Underworld, they would truly die in battle if they died. All the expedition teams were mentally prepared to sacrifice their entire fleet if the situation turned bad.

The energy core stabilizer disintegrated, and the psionic energy that had lost control began to expand, emitting a strong light.

"I'm honored to have worked with all of you. Long live the Dynasty."

The commander looked at the determined faces of the crew members, saluted, and then looked at the World Tree pursuers outside the porthole. He closed his eyes and prepared to die.

Buzz!

However, at this moment, everything froze in an instant. All the crew members could not move, and the self-destruction process stopped. The psionic energy that was about to go out of control stopped in an instant.

The Secret Tree King's figure appeared in the cabin unknowingly. He sized up everyone's determined faces and sneered.

"Quite unyielding. It's a pity that I came personally. No matter how determined you are, it's useless."

The Secret Tree King maintained the effect of the spacetime freeze spell. He rubbed his palm lightly, and the green lustrous power of the Tree King spread out, turning into a space crack. From within, a snake-like World Tree Root extended out and penetrated all the battleships of the expedition team. More and more small tree roots were separated and inserted into the bodies of all the crew members.

Then, these roots absorbed their essence like straws. At the same time, they transformed the team into one of their own by reforming them in the Information Form layer. The expedition team slowly integrated into the World Tree Root and sank deeper.

This process lasted for a long time before the World Tree sucked the entire expedition team in. Then, with a flash of light, it vomited again. However, it was different from before. All the crew members were flowing with green light and transformed into the members of the World Tree.

"Your Excellency Tree King."

The soldiers from the Crimson Dynasty lowered their heads and bowed respectfully.

The Secret Tree King ignored them and focused on the mental network, sharing the memories of these people and the sailing log of the spaceship.

After browsing for a while, the Secret Tree King's eyes flashed, and he revealed a playful expression.

"Heh, so it was here. I found your nest."

At this moment, the Secret Tree King suddenly felt something and looked into the distance.

"Predicting me?"

A cold look appeared in the eyes of the Secret Tree King. His hand gestures changed, and his magic power surged out, following the mysterious sense of the source.

At the same time, somewhere on Floating Dragon Island.

"Pfft!"

Aesop, who was feeling the sudden premonition, was shocked. It was as if his brain had been hit by a hammer, and he collapsed to the ground with a shocked expression.

A cold magical power shattered the foresight in his mind and damaged his spirit.

Those who could cause a backlash to a Foreseer were basically all Mages. With different foresight abilities, the difficulty of the backlash would also change. Aesop's foresight ability was not ordinary. In all these years, he had experienced countless passive foresight and had also foreseen many Beyond Grade A Mages. The worst-case scenario would be a failure, and this was the first time someone had caused him a backlash.

Chapter 1412: Change

At the expeditionary army outpost.

An exploratory fleet was docked at the dock. Harrison and his teammates alighted from the spaceship, took off their life-preserving helmets before taking a deep breath.

"I'm dying of suffocation. The air in the base's large ecological shield is still the best. In the past few days outside, the gas filters of the spaceships have all become smelly."

"Really? Why don't I feel anything?"

"I wonder if it's because us Gukates have a better sense of smell than most galactic species?"

"It's a pity that I didn't gain anything from this trip."

Hearing his crewmates engage in idle chatter, Harrison rubbed his forehead in frustration.

Ever since he unearthed this ally, the Realmless King, the upper echelons had allowed him to lead an expedition team alone. From a follower to a team commander, he had a certain degree of freedom to make exploration plans.

Black Star had always said that Harrison was lucky, and Harrison was willing to believe that it was true. He secretly hoped that his luck would help him find the World Tree's main body and end the war as soon as possible. However, after so many years, the luck that he had high hopes for seemed to have become dormant. Other than escaping from the pursuit of the World Tree's Blessed Race a few times, he did not have any new achievements in exploring.

Now that the expeditionary army's exploration progress had come to a standstill, Harrison was both anxious and worried. As the saying went, if one walked by the river all the time, one's shoes would inevitably get wet. The expeditionary army kept wandering around the territory of the World Tree, and they met their pursuers time and time again. He felt that there might come a time when they would fail.

At this moment, one of the team members patted Harrison on the shoulder and said, "Captain, how long do we rest this time before we start the next exploration?"

"Ten days," Harrison replied.

"Got it. Let's go to the base cafeteria for lunch. Want to come?"

"No, I'll report to the logistics department and have them repair and maintain the spaceship. I still have to write a routine report." Harrison waved his hand.

"Alright, we'll bring you some food. What do you want to eat?"

"Then I want…"

Harrison was just about to say something when he suddenly stopped. At that moment, a chilling feeling gripped his heart.

Without getting an answer, the team member blinked in confusion and asked again, "Why aren't you saying anything? What do you want to eat?"

Harrison's mind was in a mess, and he felt a strong sense of vigilance. He could not help but look up at the scenery outside the port.

"What are you looking at?" The team member turned his head and followed Harrison's gaze. The only thing he saw was the dim yellow light of the setting sun in the secondary dimension. It was like an oil painting with the aura of history, but he did not see anything unusual.

"Something's not right…"

Harrison became warier.

The team member wanted to ask more, but at this moment, the dimension barrier in the distance suddenly lit up with a blue light and quickly turned into a huge space vortex. It was as if a hole had been torn open, and the green and lustrous World Tree Blessed Race swarmed out like locusts, covering the sky and covering the earth. They were like tiny green dots that quickly enlarged in everyone's vision.

"Wuwuwu—Alert! The space barrier has been broken! Enemy attack!"

An ear-piercing alarm suddenly resounded throughout the base. All the expeditionary army members who were resting and waiting in the base jumped in shock. The sound of anxious shouts, anxious footsteps, and chaotic crashing sounds created a riotous symphony.

"Everyone, retreat at full speed! Prepare to self-destruct! The defense team will be staying behind to buy time!"

The roar of the person in charge of the outpost sounded in the communication channel. Half an hour ago, an expedition team had self-destructed and lost contact. He was still investigating this matter and was not sure if there had been any intelligence leaks. He did not expect the World Tree to arrive so quickly.

The World Tree was extremely powerful in the secondary dimension, and the defense of this outpost was limited. The coordinates of the dimension had already been exposed, and if they fought head-on, it would attract more of the World Tree Blessed Race. In the preset plan that the three Universal Civilizations had planned, if this outpost was attacked, the first priority would be to self-destruct and clear the traces, while the expeditionary army would quickly retreat. Unless they had no choice, they would not choose to fight head-on.

"Let's go!"

Harrison's expression changed drastically, and he could not care less about anything else. He quickly called his teammates to board the dock and started the engine.

The outpost became chaotic all of a sudden, and the automatic defense team was hastily activated to fight against the endless stream of World Tree Blessed Race to buy time. Meanwhile, the expeditionary army members behind swarmed toward the warehouse and quickly found their vehicles to evacuate.

Streams of light shot out from the base and scattered to escape into different secondary dimensions.

Very soon, the vanguard troops of the World Tree Family started fighting head-on with the defense team of the outpost. In an instant, countless battleships exploded into fireworks.

At the same time, the fortresses in the outpost activated their self-destruct sequence and exploded. The gate that connected to the main material universe was also destroyed by the physical missiles fired by the base. Flames soared into the sky, black smoke filled the air, and countless debris rained down.

The defense team was quickly destroyed, and the outpost exploded violently. The same scene happened in multiple secondary dimensions. The World Tree obtained precise coordinates half an hour ago, quickly assembled, and located their destinations directly. A large-scale blitzkrieg was carried out, catching the three Universal Civilizations off guard. The bridgehead that the three Universal Civilizations had built in the territory of the Realmless King were destroyed one after another, and many expedition teams had to escape.

On the other side, the Realmless King's residence.

A magic portal shining with green light suddenly opened, and the Secret Tree King slowly walked out. The first thing he saw was the black mountain range and the huge throne in the middle of the dimension.

However, there was no sign of the Realmless King on the throne.

"Am I late? Or was it a coincidence that he's not at home?"

Secret Tree King activated his perception magic and realized that the Realmless King was not hiding anywhere in the area. He could not help but feel a little regretful.

The stabilization zone controlled by the Realmless King had some reputation in this secondary dimension area. The World Tree Blessed Race had also heard about it, but they had never paid attention to it.

When he found out from the expedition team that the three Universal Civilizations were working together with the Realmless King, the Secret Tree King had wanted to go straight to the Realmless King's base camp and turn him into a member of the World Tree. However, he realized that the Realmless King was not at home, so he could only give up on this plan for the time being.

The Secret Tree King raised his hand and clenched his fist. Magical runes shot out and turned into a surveillance spell that took root in this secondary dimension. The moment the Realmless King returned to his base, he would come and attack again.

After casually setting up the spell, the Secret Tree King summoned the teleportation gate and stepped into it. The vortex quickly shrank and disappeared with him.

At the same time, in the secondary dimension at the edge of the Realmless King's territory.

Space was slowly collapsing, and wave after wave of dimensional energy was being devoured by the Pivotal Snake hatchling. At the side, the Realmless King who was in charge of feeding it suddenly stopped, and his heart tightened.

He had a basic sense within the territory that he controlled. Just now, he had sensed that the World Tree Army had raided the secondary dimensions that were lent to the three Universal Civilizations one after another. Almost all the outposts had fallen, and the most terrifying thing was that an uninvited guest had arrived at his headquarters. It was obvious that their target was him.

"The World Tree still came!"

The Realmless King panicked.

Although he treated the intelligence of the three Universal Civilizations as a bargaining chip, he was not willing to reveal it to the World Tree unless he had no other choice. The risk was too high, and the World Tree was obviously targeting him now. Beyond Grade As had gone all the way to his base, and even if he expressed his willingness to cooperate, they would most likely kill him to ensure that the intelligence was reliable.

"Luckily, I came out. If I had stayed at home, I would have turned into the puppet of the World Tree…"

The Realmless King felt a sense of lingering fear, and he looked at the Pivotal Snake with a complicated expression.

When Black Star told him to take out his own territory to feed the Pivotal Snake, the Realmless King was very unhappy. Now that he looked at it, he only felt glad… If not for Black Star forcefully giving him this job, he would not have come out to walk the Pivotal Snake today, and would most likely have been trapped by the World Tree's experts at his home.

Does that mean… Black Star saved my life?!

"Since I can't go back, I can only walk this path to the end!"

The Realmless King quickly made up his mind.

He did not want to get involved in the war between two Universal Civilizations, but one of his trusted subordinates had already provoked the three Universal Civilizations and dragged him into it. Thus, he had no choice but to cooperate with the three Universal Civilizations. Right now, it was already too difficult for him to leave.

Since the World Tree had already set its sights on him, he had no choice but to take a stand. He had to suck up to the three Universal Civilizations and defeat the World Tree.

With this in mind, the Realmless King turned to the Mechanical Oracle monitoring the Pivotal Snake and reported the situation.

The battle did not last too long. The World Tree Family wiped out the expeditionary army outpost. The surprise attack ended very quickly, and a large number of expedition teams fled in all directions. A portion of the World Tree fleet chased after the fluctuations of the dimensional travel, while the rest of the troops had already begun cleaning the battlefield, summarizing the results of the battle, and finishing up the work.

The roots of the World Tree extended out from the spatial rift, and expeditionary army spaceships were hanging on them. The Secret Tree King was floating at the side, sharing his memories with his eyes closed.

Not long after, the Secret Tree King opened his eyes again. His originally relaxed expression was now extremely solemn.

"I didn't expect the mother tree's natural enemy to have fallen under the enemy's control. The situation is dangerous…"

Eliminating the enemies that were searching for the mother tree was originally just a matter of convenience. He did not expect to find the mother tree's natural enemy because of this. This was not good news.

If the mother tree's natural enemy entered maturity, it would be able to sense the location of the mother tree's main body. If it could only move independently, it would not be a big threat. However, if it was controlled by the enemy, the threat level would soar to the extreme, which meant that the enemy could find the mother tree's main body.

The Secret Tree King knew the severity of the matter. This meant that the World Tree, which was supposed to fight a war of attrition without any pressure, had to seize whatever time they had. They had to either kill the Pivotal Snake before it reaches adulthood or completely defeat the three Universal Civilizations before then.

The only good news was that the Pivotal Snake had just been born, and it would take a long time for it to reach adulthood.

He immediately sent this matter to the Ancestral Tree King. The next moment, the voice of the Ancestral Tree King sounded in his mind.

"Good job, or else we would still be kept in the dark. Summon a portion of your high-level combatants to hunt down the mother tree's natural enemy. You must eliminate it!"

"Alright, I happened to obtain the coordinates of the enemy's territory in the secondary dimension from their memories. We have a new target."

"Hmm, the Fortitude Tree King and I will be ready to receive you at any time. I'll leave the rest to you." The Ancestral Tree King nodded.

"Just nice, I can successfully open up the secondary dimensional battlefield zone this time and solve both problems together."

A cold light flickered in the Secret Tree King's eyes. He was not satisfied with destroying the outposts of the three Universal Civilizations. What he had his eyes on was the base camp that the three Universal Civilizations had developed in the secondary dimension world for a long time.

The two sides had fought for more than ten years, and only today did they grasp the general situation of the three Universal Civilizations. They were no longer led by the nose, and they finally had a breakthrough.

Exploration Universe, frontline base.

Han Xiao was listening to the battle conference when a report from the Mechanical Oracle suddenly appeared in his mind.

"Oh? The World Tree found the expeditionary army outpost and launched a surprise attack. Did they succeed?"

Han Xiao frowned.

He was somewhat surprised by this, but not too surprised. As the expeditionary army's exploration time increased, the risk of exposure also increased at the same time. He had long been mentally prepared for this, and the only thing that made him feel strange was the difference in time from his expectations.

It had only been a few days since he had returned from the expeditionary army outpost, and he was still thinking about the follow-up plan when the World Tree broke through the outpost. It seemed like a coincidence, but Han Xiao felt that there was something fishy about it.

"The secondary dimension battlefield has in the end been established, and that is the World Tree's home ground. Their attack this time probably allowed them to obtain the coordinates of the shallow dimensions, and this two-way battle is disadvantageous to the three Universal Civilizations… However, the three Universal Civilizations have also made preparations in the secondary dimension, so the situation will not be as bad as in my previous life."

Han Xiao pondered.

At this time, Simon, who was explaining the strategy, suddenly paused. A remote projection of a high-ranking military officer appeared on the conference table. His expression was extremely serious as he said in a deep voice,

"This is an emergency. The secondary dimension expeditionary army outpost has been raided by the World Tree, and it has almost completely fallen. Some of the intelligence has been leaked, and the World Tree has likely obtained the coordinates of the shallow dimension. It is estimated that a second front line will be opened, and we urgently need high-level combatants to help!"

The three Universal Civilizations' notification was a step slower than the Mechanical Oracle's. As soon as they finished speaking, all the officers present were shocked and turned to look at Han Xiao.

Hearing this, Han Xiao slowly nodded and asked,

"Who is leading the enemy?"

"According to the information from the frontline, it's a Super who has never appeared before."

The image of the Secret Tree King appeared on the virtual screen. This was a photo taken before some bases self-destructed.

"Secret Tree King…" Han Xiao immediately recognized this person." Alright, leave this to me. "

At this moment, Simon opened his mouth and said with a frown, "Warring on two fronts will restrict our high-level combatants. Aurora won't be able to split herself up. At the same time, the enemy might even deliberately avoid Black Star, allowing them to use their foreign experts… I will definitely agree to assist the secondary dimensions, but the frontlines of the border are important battlefields. We have to maintain a sufficient number of advanced combatants."

"This is not a big problem. I have enough The King mechanical suits to move quickly on both sides. Also… I have more manpower."

Han Xiao nodded.

Compared to the terrifying scale of the galactic battlefield, the secondary dimension world was heavily divided due to its different specialties, which indirectly strengthened the importance of individual strength in the secondary dimension battlefield.

It was time for the Holy Accord Organization's hooligans, who had been idling around for decades, to come into play.

Furthermore, this Secret Tree King was worth him taking action.

Chapter 1413: Battle and Emergence

On the white desert ravaged by the radiation storm, a bright light suddenly flashed. An expedition starship that was emitting flames emerged from the crack and fell down as if it had lost all its power. It crashed onto the ground, shaking up the white sand in the sky. Its momentum did not decrease, and it plowed a deep ravine on the ground.

The azure particle shield, which was on the verge of shattering, endured the impact and flickered like a light bulb with a loose circuit. Then, it disappeared, and the spaceship suddenly sank. Its head was inserted into the desert, and its tail was raised up high. The distorted thrusters exploded with sparks, and it finally malfunctioned, spewing out black smoke.

Clang! Clang! Clang!

The hatch of the spaceship was stuck, and there was a sound of collision coming from inside. The alloy door protruded out, and then it was sent flying with a bang. The deformed hatch smashed onto the sand and slid out more than ten meters.

Harrison and the others walked out while holding onto the injured parts of their bodies. Their bodies swayed as if they had drunk fake wine. The gravity stabilization device and gyroscope of the spaceship had failed, and it fell to the ground.

One of the team members looked at the paralyzed spaceship and said in a panic, "Oh no, the spaceship is damaged. We can't run anymore!"

"Don't panic. The enemy hasn't caught up. Hurry up and repair it."

Harrison held his dizzy head, gritted his teeth, and ordered his teammates to repair the spaceship.

The outpost was attacked, and a large number of expedition teams fled in all directions. The World Tree Blessed Races pursued them relentlessly, and they also met the enemy. The team was left with only one spaceship, and it was not easy for them to shake off the pursuers. The spaceship that had endured the fierce attacks was pushed to the limit and broke down.

"I wonder how the outpost is doing," one of the team members muttered.

"It is definitely destroyed. The World Tree came prepared. With the armed forces of the outpost, it's impossible for them to survive."

"While we were escaping, the commander was still giving orders in the main control room. I'm afraid he has already sacrificed himself by self-destructing, living and dying with the base…"

The atmosphere in the crowd was filled with sadness. Having worked together for more than ten years, many of the expeditionary army members were already familiar with each other. At this time, the future of so many of their comrades looked ominous, and they were all worried.

"The situation of the World Tree attack should have been sent back to the main universe. Before I evacuated, I had already sent a message to His Excellency Black Star using the quantum network base station at the outpost. He should have received it, but he has yet to come to the rescue. I wonder…"

Harrison's tone was hesitant. The moment he was attacked, he had sent out a request for help. While escaping, he had been protecting the 'Throne' that Black Star had given him. He had been waiting for Han Xiao to arrive, but there had been no response.

"Can we contact him again?" someone quickly asked.

"Not at the moment. There's no linkable base station, so I can't contact the outside world for the time being…"

Before Harrison could finish his sentence, a spatial fluctuation suddenly appeared on the spaceship, and Han Xiao walked out from the damaged cabin door. The moment everyone saw him, they were immediately surprised.

"Your Excellency Black Star! You're finally here!"

"We're saved!"

Han Xiao raised his hand and gestured for them to control their emotions. He then looked at Harrison and sized him up. "Looks like you're in good shape. You're not injured."

Harrison greeted him with a disappointed expression. "You're too late. The outpost has fallen. They…"

Han Xiao interrupted him, nodded, and said, "Alright, I already know about this. Since the outpost is gone, so be it. The three Universal Civilizations have already sent people to pick up the other expeditionary army soldiers. I'm here to pick you up… and your teammates."

When the emergency notification from the three Universal Civilizations had reached the main base in the Siebert Fortress, Han Xiao had already received Harrison's request for help. The reason he had only rushed over now was that he had spent some time deploying the high-level combatants of the association and made a trip to the Realmless King's side to protect the Pivotal Snake. He had hidden the Pivotal Snake in a secret place and only came to pick up Harrison after doing all these important things. Han Xiao was not afraid of anything happening to Harrison. He had been using the Observer's Mark to monitor Harrison's situation. Seeing that he was safe, he did not teleport over immediately.

"What about the outposts? Aren't you going to reinforce them?" Harrison asked.

"There's no need. The dimensional coordinates of the outposts have been exposed, so it's not suitable to rebuild the base. Even if we want to rebuild the outpost, it will have to be somewhere else. The losses this time are not too big. The outposts have served their purpose over the years."

Han Xiao waved his hands.

The purpose of the outpost was only to facilitate the expeditionary army's exploration of the deep layer dimensions, and the coordinates of the various dimensions had already been recorded into the database over the years. The coordinates of the Realmless King's territory and the areas around the World Tree had already been controlled by the three Universal Civilizations, which meant that these places had become 'new shallow layer dimensions'. Thanks to the special structure of the secondary dimension world, and since they had the coordinates, the subsequent troops could quickly jump over even without the outpost. They did not have to travel for many years like in normal exploration. This was the most important result.

As for the outpost itself, it did not have any irreplaceable value. With these coordinates in hand, it could be rebuilt at any time. Therefore, this loss was nothing in the eyes of the three Universal Civilizations. They were more concerned about the degree of information leakage.

Harrison nodded and asked, "What do we do next?"

"I'll take you to the base camp of the three Universal Civilizations in the secondary dimension world. They have already gathered their troops there and are preparing to deal with the possible attacks from the World Tree. This time, the coordinates might have been leaked, and the World Tree opening up the secondary dimensional battlefront should be a foregone conclusion. The three Universal Civilizations will have to face a two-way battle from now on… After sending you off, I'll have a short meeting with the leaders of the three Universal Civilizations to discuss this matter."

Han Xiao said casually with a calm tone.

At this time, there was a high chance that the World Tree was still cleaning up the battlefield in the various outposts, but he did not have any intention of retaliating. Even if he went over, the Secret Tree King might not appear, and he would alert the enemy on top of making a wasted trip. He might as well wait for the Secret Tree King to start a two-way battle and then give him a big slap. If the World Tree had the coordinates of the shallow layer dimensions, it would not take much time to jump over, and they might even start another round of blitzkrieg. Therefore, Han Xiao guessed that the Secret Tree King would not take too long.

Han Xiao gave a simple explanation and did not say anything else. He took out a new carrier, set the coordinates of the destination, and called everyone to board the ship.

Everyone obediently accepted the arrangement. Compared to the other expeditionary army soldiers, this group of people was lucky enough to be received by Han Xiao personally and escape from danger thanks to Harrison's luck glow.

...

The Galactic Alliance Army was divided into many smaller armies. The border defense army guarded the frontlines of the Flickering World, while the secondary dimension garrison was responsible for guarding the base camp in the shallow layer dimensions. This was the foundation of the three Universal Civilizations in the secondary dimension world. If it was destroyed, they would lose most of their control over the secondary dimension.

A few hours after the outposts were attacked, the garrisons in all the war zones in the shallow layer dimension were fully prepared for battle.

At this moment, in one of the shallow layer dimensions.

While the blue energy was being replenished, the scene was like an ocean. A dynasty fleet that belonged to the secondary dimension garrison floated in the air and waited quietly. All the battleships were specially designed for the secondary dimension. Compared to the dynasty's standard heavy military starships, they were much slender and more balanced.

"I've just received news that a war has broken out at the Flickering World's frontline, and the World Tree Army has launched another attack. At this juncture, it's very likely to be a double-layered tactic of the enemy, so the enemy can appear at any time. Everyone, focus!"

In the main ship, the commander spoke in the military channel.

The dynasty soldiers of the various fleets were extremely focused and did not dare to be distracted.

After waiting for a while, the fleet commander suddenly received the order from the other troops. His eyes narrowed, and he said with a deep voice, "The World Tree Army has already attacked. Thirty-four war zones have been invaded, and the other garrison troops are exchanging fire. The enemy will be here soon…"

As soon as he said that, the space wall suddenly opened up with jump points like beehives. The World Tree's Blessed Races swarmed out like a green flood.

"Attack!"

The fleet commander roared.

Bang! Bang! Bang!

The next moment, countless beams of energy lit up in the battlefield and formed a dense net, shattering a large group of battleships.

The two troops were fearless. It was as if they had turned into two giant beasts, one black and one green. They started to bite each other ferociously, not caring about their own injuries. They only cared about ripping off the flesh of the other party.

The same thing was happening in hundreds of shallow layer dimensions. War had broken out!

The warfare mode of the secondary dimensions was different from that of the main universe. Every war zone was a divided battlefield. With the help of the special 'geographical' structure, countless fleets fought as they traveled through the various secondary dimensions while carrying out operations like restraining, pulling, encircling, and counter encirclement. The situation changed rapidly, and the flames of war engulfed countless small worlds. The secondary dimensions were blasted into smithereens, and their remains were devoured by the space storms.

The high-level combatants of both sides also started to fight each other, and the battlefield changed from one dimension to another.

...

In a shallow layer dimension war zone riddled with holes, a transportation door hung high up in the sky, spitting out a few injured Beyond Grade As from the three Universal Civilizations. Not far away, a green transportation door opened, and more Holy Tree Emissaries chased after them.

The few Beyond Grade As did not have time to recuperate and quickly turned around to fight. They were once again at a disadvantage, and the situation became worse.

"Don't even think about leaving the secondary dimension world alive!"

The Holy Tree Emissaries were filled with killing intent, and their attacks were ferocious. Their eyes were even flashing with joy.

In the past, when they fought with the Beyond Grade As of the three Universal Civilizations, due to the existence of the Healing Esper, all the high-level combatants of the enemy were like a death squad, making them feel extremely miserable. They could not even feel the joy of the World Tree's infinite revival.

However, it was different now. In the secondary dimension battlefield, due to the special battlefield structure, the Healing Esper would be greatly restricted and would not be able to take care of every battlefield… Furthermore, the Healing Esper did not even have the time to come over. The troops in the main universe launched an attack, dragging many enemy high-level combatants to the frontlines, including the Healing Esper.

Now that they saw the enemy being restrained again, the Holy Tree Emissaries were finally overjoyed.

Austin was among the Beyond Grade As that were surrounded. Half of his magic treasures had been destroyed, and he was struggling to resist the attacks.

"The situation isn't looking good. Without reinforcements, we will definitely suffer losses."

Even with the Sanctum Revival, most people did not wish for themselves to end up in such a state. There was only one Aurora, and everyone wanted to stay on the front line and fight alongside the milkmaid. Therefore, there were very few high-level combatants who were willing to rush to reinforce the troops in the shallow layer dimensions. Other than the direct descendants, none of the others were willing. They were all ordered to come and help, and there was a huge difference in numbers with the enemy. The situation did not look good.

By the side, Beiger was fighting with a high-level Holy Tree Emissary, and they were locked in an intense battle. He whispered, "Don't panic, we still have reinforcements."

"What reinforcements?" Austin frowned.

At this moment, the space wall in the distance of the battlefield suddenly opened up, and an unmarked fleet charged into the battlefield, firing densely packed sharp missiles at the World Tree Blessed Races, which exploded on the shields.

The next moment, the area where the missiles exploded turned into chaotic space. A batch of World Tree Blessed Race members was sucked into it and disappeared without a trace.

"This is…" Austin's pupils constricted.

"The Holy Accord's Dimensional Exile Bullet," Beiger continued.

"Holy Accord? What is…"

Before Austin could ask further, waves of Beyond Grade A energy soared into the sky.

Boom!

A few unfamiliar Beyond Grade As flew out from this mysterious fleet, quickly closing in on the Holy Tree Emissaries.

Austin felt the pressure lessen, and he quickly backed away. He looked at the battle and was shocked.

"These are the reinforcements you mentioned? Who are they?"

"Don't you find them familiar?" Beiger raised an eyebrow.

Austin looked over and immediately recognized a few people. They were all famous Primordial Ones in history.

Thinking about Beiger's identity, he suddenly realized something.

"They're Revivors like you? I thought Black Star did not revive them. When did this happen ‽"

"You will know the details later. Now is not the time to talk about it."

Beiger did not explain further and dodged the enemy's counterattack. A forbidden spell ray penetrated the enemy's chest.

Austin's heart skipped a beat. He looked at them deeply and did not ask any more questions.

Similar scenes were happening in many of the war zones. The dozens of revivors who had been hidden in the Holy Accord for many years finally joined the battle for the first time, helping the Beyond Grade As and quickly stabilizing the situation of the high-level combatants.

Not only was the World Tree surprised by this wave of reinforcements, but even the three Universal Civilizations were confused. They could not figure out the origins of these reinforcements.

At the same time.

The leaders of the three Universal Civilizations, who were monitoring the battle in the secondary dimension, all turned to look at Han Xiao, who was watching the battle together in the office. Their expressions were mixed with shock and complicated emotions.

"Black Star… aren't you going to explain?"

Chapter 1414: Ambush

Without looking back, Han Xiao casually replied, "As you can see, these are all reinforcements that I've pulled over to fill the gap in our combat strength."

The church head knocked on the table with his knuckles and said with a deep voice, "Don't play dumb. I'm asking how they got here. When did you revive these people?"

Hearing this, Han Xiao then turned around and glanced at the three of them.

"Do you think all the revivors are willing to appear in public? I never said that the ones in the association are all the revivors there are. As for who exactly I revived, I have no obligation to tell others. Don't ask what you shouldn't ask."

The three of them choked and looked at him deeply.

They did not need to think too much to guess that this was Black Star's backup plan. There was probably a group of revivors hidden in the dark, which was most likely arranged during the confrontation back then as a trump card against the three Universal Civilizations.

If they had decided to carry out the purge back then, the result would have been hard to determine. Now that Han Xiao had just revealed this trump card, the three of them were shocked.

However, after knowing him for so many years, the three of them had a deep understanding of Black Star's unfathomable habits. They were already used to Black Star setting up spies everywhere. Perhaps this group of revivors that had suddenly appeared was just the tip of the iceberg of his hidden force…

The three of them looked away with heavy hearts.

This was not the time to be bothered about such things, the three of them were still more respectful toward Han Xiao.

Now that Black Star was on the same level as them, the three of them saw that he did not want to explain and so they did not continue asking.

Furthermore, compared to the importance of Black Star himself, having another batch of revivors did not seem like a big deal. With Han Xiao, who was a Transcendent, the impact these hidden revivors had on the three of them was limited.

Of course, Han Xiao would not take the initiative to explain the origin of the Holy Accord. Looking at the three of them, he could not help but smile.

Back then, he had hidden the strength of the Holy Accord organization to leave a path of retreat for the association, allowing the Beyond Grade As to be divided into two parts—the open and the dark.

He had originally planned to reveal the tip of the iceberg of the Holy Accord at the right time and make the three Universal Civilizations wary. However, his plans could not keep up with the changes. Now that he had stepped into the Transcendent Grade, the deterrence of a single person was comparable to the entire Beyond Grade A group. The Holy Accord Revivors trump card was not as important as before. However, it was still useful. It was not a bad thing to make the three Universal Civilizations warier.

Han Xiao paid attention to the battle once again. After watching for a while, he suddenly locked onto the Secret Tree King and Clotti who were fighting on the surveillance screen.

"My prey has appeared. Excuse me."

The remote projection disappeared.

Only at this moment did the three Universal Civilizations' leaders relax. They looked at each other and saw the fear in each other's eyes.

...

In a certain war zone in the shallow layer dimension battlefield.

Bang!

The rainbow-like magic light penetrated the surging dark energy and landed on Clotti's body, leaving a new wound. The powerful annihilation force sent him flying, crashing into the dark brown ground and smashing through hundreds of layers.

"Cough cough…"

The cells in his body withered under the influence of the Annihilation spell. Clotti quickly used his energy to stabilize his injuries before looking up at the enemy in the sky with a grave expression.

The Secret Tree King was floating in the air, looking down at him from above. Forbidden Spells were brewing around him, rapidly taking shape and falling like a storm.

Clotti gritted his teeth to suppress his injuries and manipulated the dark energy to meet the attack. However, the stalemate only lasted for an instant before he was sent flying once again, with many new wounds on his body.

"This Tree King… is too strong…"

Clotti clutched his wound, his eyes shining with shock.

He had judged the strength of the Tree King from the Subduing Tree King, the Heart Tree King, and the Lord's Avatar of the Fortitude Tree King. He had thought that even if he could not defeat this new Tree King, he would at least be able to hold on for a long time. However, Clotti did not expect that this guy who called himself the Secret Tree King was stronger than the other three. He was the National Pillar, but the other party beat him like beating a younger brother. It was easy and relaxed.

Among all the opponents that he had fought, only Black Star and Wuornos could deal with him so easily.

If the other Beyond Grade A Mages were just ordinary magic cannons, then this Secret Tree King was a rapid nuclear bomb. The strength, frequency, and speed of his casting far exceeded all the Mages that Clotti had ever seen!

In the sky, the Secret Tree King temporarily stopped attacking. He moved his fingers and casually played with a ribbon made of magic power.

"You actually dared to fight me one on one. Should I say that your courage is commendable, or you are overestimating yourself? Unfortunately, only that Mechanic or that Esper has the qualifications to fight me. Your strength is a little too weak. If this continues, I won't have any interest in killing you…"

The only opponents that the Secret Tree King cared about were Han Xiao and EsGod. Although Clotti's combat strength was not low, and his dark energy control Esper Ability was rather penetrative, it was not much of a threat to him, a Mage who grasped multidimensional energy.

Feeling the other party's contempt, Clotti's face darkened. He silently gathered his energy and prepared to go all out.

However, right at this moment, a spatial fluctuation appeared in their senses. The space wall in the distance opened up, and a figure covered in a hooded black robe appeared. His clothes fluttered in the wind, and the edges of his clothes were like black flames. He was brimming with the aura of a peak Beyond Grade A, attracting their attention.

"Who are you?" Clotti turned around. He did not know if he was friend or foe, but he immediately became more alert.

"We're on the same side."

Oathkeeper glanced at him before staring at the Secret Tree King.

"Another one?" The Secret Tree King narrowed his eyes. "You're in cahoots with those new reinforcements, right? You should be their leader. Interesting, you still have a group of high-level combatants hidden… Heh, so what? You can't turn the situation around. Sooner or later, we'll wipe out all your forces in the secondary dimension world!"

Through the mental network, he had already found out about the Holy Accord Revivors reinforcing the three Universal Civilizations' Beyond Grade As.

In the eyes of the Secret Tree King, facing an opponent like the World Tree, the three Universal Civilizations should have felt immense pressure and gone all out long ago. However, the other party was still holding back even now. It was truly unfathomable.

Furthermore, with the Secret Tree King's personality, he was a little unhappy about this… Why, is our World Tree not worthy of your full strength ‽

Ignoring the Secret Tree King, Oathkeeper communicated with Clotti telepathically.

"Leave this to me. Go help the others."

"Can you do it? This Tree King is very strong. We'd better work together to deal with him." Clotti expressed his doubts.

"This Tree King is a Mage, and I can see that his spells have bonuses in the secondary dimension world. I should not be his match, but I only need to stall him. In this aspect, I'm more suitable than you. There's no need to waste combat power on him."

Oathkeeper responded.

Not long ago, the expeditionary army outposts had been attacked, and Han Xiao had finally informed the Holy Accord Organization to take part in the battle. Many of the Holy Accord Revivors had already prepared themselves mentally. They did not need any mobilization and set off on their own. On one hand, it was for the sake of the Sanctum Revival qualifications, and on the other hand, it was also because they were in the same boat.

Other than that, Han Xiao also requested the Holy Accord to bring along Dimensional Exile Bullets, High-Level Lifeform Energy Disorder Shockwave, cross-dimensional detection radars, and other special technologies to provide support. Oathkeeper had no choice but to do as he was told. As the Holy Accord organization's troops had always been on standby, they quickly came over.

Clotti did not respond, but at this moment, the Secret Tree King suddenly attacked. All kinds of powerful forbidden spells were cast continuously, firing at the two of them.

Bang! Bang! Bang!

Magical lights flashed in the sky, beautiful and deadly. Oathkeeper and Clotti immediately reacted and moved around, dodging nonstop.

On the other side, the Secret Tree King was multitasking. While quickly constructing spell models and casting forbidden spells, he communicated with the Ancestral Tree King through the mental network.

"There's no sign of that Mechanic in the frontline battlefield or the secondary dimension battlefield. He has that sealing ability, so there's a high chance that he's targeting a tree king. Therefore, his target should be me. Maybe he's secretly observing. After I fight these two opponents for a while, he should jump out and ambush me."

Hearing this, the Ancestral Tree King expressed his approval in the mental network and said with a deep voice, "Your judgment is very reasonable. Continue fighting. As long as that Mechanic is lured out, I will immediately descend and catch him off guard."

"Okay."

The two of them quickly came up with a plan. They planned to use the Secret Tree King as bait to lure the snake out of its hole.

The mantis stalks the cicada, unaware of the oriole behind. Since it was very likely that Black Star had his eyes on the Secret Tree King, the Ancestral Tree King also chose to launch an ambush. He had two goals. One was to find an opportunity to kill Black Star, and the other was to think of a way to save the Heart Tree King. If he did not deal with Black Star, how could he talk about unsealing the Heart Tree King? At the very least, he had to snatch that Universal Treasure with the sealing ability.

It was not that he thought too highly of the Heart Tree King. Even the simple-minded Subduing Tree King had 'decisively' self-destructed twice to escape from being sealed. Only the Heart Tree King had been affected. The Ancestral Tree King only wanted to take back the sealed Tree King Crown. Otherwise, there would always be a gap in the five Tree Kings.

With Oathkeeper joining the battle, the two of them were finally at a stalemate with the Secret Tree King. The three of them fought intensely, chasing each other non-stop. The battlefield changed again and again. One moment, it was an abyss-like blackish-purple space, then it was a holy land-like silver kingdom, then it was a nascent dimension born in the void, and the next moment, it was an unstable secondary dimension at its end. Without exception, every battlefield was shattered by the aftershock of their battle, and batches of fleets were devoured by the space storm.

The three of them arrived at a shadow dimension. Suddenly, the space wall in the distance opened, and another figure entered the battlefield. It was Han Xiao.

The Secret Tree King noticed Han Xiao at first glance and immediately ignored the other two opponents. He stared at Han Xiao with a strong battle intent and killing intent in his eyes.

"You're finally willing to come out ‽"

Han Xiao glanced at him, waved his hand, told Oathkeeper and Clotti to stop and retreat to the side, then spoke to the Secret Tree King in the public channel.

"There are three of us here. Aren't you going to run?"

"Run? Who do you think I am ‽"

The Secret Tree King suddenly waved his palm, and an invisible spatial fluctuation swept across this space. The entire secondary dimension instantly turned into a mirror-like space, as though it was trapped in a crystal. The images of the battlefield were flowing in the sections of the space, overlapping and dazzling.

The spatial barrier suddenly formed, isolating Clotti and Oathkeeper in the outside world. They could only see what was going on inside the barrier, but they could not participate in it. It was as if the two of them were in parallel spaces that had no intersection.

Inside the barrier, only the Secret Tree King and Han Xiao were looking at each other.

"You want to fight me one on one?" Han Xiao looked around at the barrier and smiled strangely.

"I've always wanted to fight you, so why would I run? I thought you would launch a sneak attack, but I didn't expect you to appear so openly… However, this doesn't matter. This barrier is our battleground. If you have the ability, don't use that teleportation technique to escape. I'll definitely kill you today!"

The eyes of the Secret Tree King flickered. He knew that Black Star had the teleportation technique that could ignore crowd control, so this barrier was only to prevent the other enemies from disrupting the battle and create the illusion of a one-on-one battle. As long as Black Star did not teleport away and stayed behind to fight him one-on-one, the plan would be half complete.

He did not hesitate and immediately cast all kinds of spells toward Han Xiao. On the surface, it seemed like he was going to fight Han Xiao one on one, but he had already secretly used spells to guide the Ancestral Tree King into the barrier, preparing to launch a pincer attack.

However, before the spell could hit its target, a powerful pressure swept out like a storm with Han Xiao at the center, shaking the Secret Tree King's mind!

Boom!

Countless machines surged out from the Godly Stronghold and instantly condensed on Han Xiao's body. They combined into a gigantic Mechanical Divine Body, which was the Supreme Heavenly Venerate. Transcendent Grade's energy fluctuations erupted without restraint!

The face of the Secret Tree King instantly changed, and the ferocity on his face turned into fear and disbelief.

"This is the level of the Tree God ‽"

He was not mentally prepared at all.

At this moment, all tactics and plans were thrown to the back of his mind.

The Secret Tree King did not hesitate to construct a transportation door and escape. He was no longer arrogant and only panic remained in his mind.

However, Han Xiao was faster than him. With a flash, his gigantic body teleported behind the Secret Tree King and tore the roots of the World Tree apart. Then, the Emperor Skysplitter Blade slashed down and invisible psionic energy waves exploded like a blade wave.

Crack!

The sound of a mirror shattering could be heard. Within the range of the psionic wave, the space barrier, various forbidden spells, transportation door, and everything else that was constructed by magic power rapidly collapsed like a sandcastle!

There was not the slightest bit of resistance!

"What?!"

The Ancestral Tree King, who had just teleported behind Han Xiao and was about to launch a sneak attack, froze on the spot. His expression changed drastically!

Chapter 1415: Overwhelming Combat Strength; Wrecking the Tree God

The Emperor Skysplitter Blade and the psionic wave launcher had already been enhanced by Han Xiao's [Beyonder Artifact] to become a 'Divine Artifact'. With just a simple press of the A button, its power was no different from a destructive ultimate move!

[TL Note: The author is probably expressing the huge damage caused by a normal attack, hence describing it as the press of an A button like a normal attack on a console.]

Facing the Secret Tree King's terrified gaze, the Emperor Sky Splitter stabbed forward. The huge blade expanded rapidly in his eyes, and he could not react in time.

Boom!

The huge blade slammed into the dimensional wall of the secondary dimension, creating countless cracks like cracking porcelain. The power of the attack was transmitted to the entire secondary dimension, exceeding the upper limit. The entire shadow dimension exploded, and all the darkness dissipated.

However, the Secret Tree King was not sent flying. Instead, it was firmly stuck to the tip of the blade by an intense gravitational force field. At the same time, the Supreme Heavenly Venerate extended a finger and pressed it against the Secret Tree King's body. The invisible power of the Spacetime Amber passed through his finger and began to make amber on the Secret Tree King's body.

The soul link of the Spacetime Amber had already reached the highest fifth level in the past decade. There was no need to touch the target with the original body of the Spacetime Amber, only physical contact was needed to activate the seal. This meant that the Spacetime Amber no longer needed to be carried around, and it could be placed anywhere.

At the same time, due to the [Energy Base—God of All Machines] talent of the Super God Mechanic, the form of his basic existence was not limited to his physical body. The Mechanical Deity that he had fused with was also his main body. This meant that he could use the Mechanical Deity's body to touch the target, which would also satisfy the judgment of the Spacetime Amber!

The Secret Tree King was rooted to the ground by a bunch of Universal Treasure-level control devices. The extremely destructive psionic energy waves flowed along the blade and entered his body, crushing large amounts of his cells. The energy in his body was suppressed by the Super God-level energy, and he could not even self-destruct. Furthermore, he did not dare to self-destruct in front of a Super God. That was truly 'courting death'.

Black Star was too fast, exceeding the Beyond Grade A realm. He could not react much at all, as if he had fallen into such a state the moment he came back to his senses.

"How can someone break through this limit? This kind of power cannot be controlled by an individual!"

The Secret Tree King panicked, his face pale.

He did not expect a Tree God to appear in this civilization. How could there be such a huge change in just ten years?

The World Tree had been growing for countless years. Other than the Ancestral Tree King, the other four Kings had all changed positions before. Although the Ancestral Tree King had the authority to remove the other Kings, he rarely used them. Generally speaking, unless the Tree King was dead, he would not do any personnel changes.

However, the Tree Kings could revive, so why would they still die? This was the problem. Some of the Tree Kings had tried to reach a higher level, but all of them died without exception. They thought that they could revive through the World Tree, but after suffering from mutations and dying during the Promotion, the information form would directly leave the connection of the World Tree, unable to revive and be completely dead. After failing time and time again, they learned from the previous mistakes, and the later generations of Tree Kings did not try to advance anymore.

In their eyes, the Transcendent Domain was an insurmountable chasm that could not be crossed by an individual. It was the limit of a single life form. Only by using a different method could one temporarily step into a higher level. The Tree God advent was one of the methods.

This kind of thinking was not strange. Having a powerful Superpower system did not mean that one could become stronger indefinitely. Although many civilizations liked to confuse the differences between the two, these were two different concepts. Be it the World Tree experts or the Beyond Grade As of the three Universal Civilizations, they all were similar in that they recognized the existence of an individual limit… The difference lay in how both parties had determined the limits of their individual strength. Because up till now, no one had truly reached the absolute limit, thus there appeared many different boundaries of strength.

"I have to break free from his control, or else…"

The Secret Tree King made up his mind and activated his cell reactor crazily. Ignoring the damage to his cells, he squeezed out all his magic power and attacked the energy lock. After struggling without caring about the consequences, the control field finally loosened.

"There's still a chance to escape!"

The Secret Tree King was overjoyed. Just as he was about to accumulate his strength to burst out and break through Han Xiao's control, the power of the Tree King in his body suddenly leaked out like a flood and was sucked away by an invisible force. His body suddenly sagged, and his accumulation of strength was interrupted. A sense of weakness spread throughout his body.

"My Tree King Crown!"

He suddenly raised his eyes and looked in the direction of the Ancestral Tree King.

The Ancestral Tree King's figure was already covered by a rapidly expanding ball of green light. It was like a gigantic egg, and a gigantic figure could be vaguely seen within. The energy fluctuations from within were rising rapidly.

How could the Secret Tree King not recognize this scene? The Ancestral Tree King had already activated the descent of the Tree God and instantly retracted his Tree King Crown as well as his strength. It was obvious that he had abandoned him to reduce the overall losses on their side. Not only did he not plan to save him, but he had even destroyed his hope of escaping!

"No!"

The Secret Tree King's eyes widened in shock.

Han Xiao noticed the change in the Ancestral Tree King and looked back. He then looked down at the Secret Tree King and said in a joking manner.

"We agreed to spend some alone time together. I didn't expect you to secretly make it into a threesome… Alright, go to sleep. I'll play with him first."

As soon as he said that, he suddenly moved his finger, and the Spacetime Amber took shape!

Deng!

The terror on the Secret Tree King's face froze as if he could not believe that he was taken down so easily. His entire body was frozen in amber.

"Success!"

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

The Secret Tree King was extremely strong among the Beyond Grade As, but he could not do much damage to him. Although it was a sudden attack, it was mainly because of the huge difference in strength that the Secret Tree King did not have the time to use all sorts of methods before being defeated.

Compared to the various schemes he had used to seal the Heart Tree King before, sealing an even stronger Secret Tree King this time was much easier. His strength had exceeded an entire realm, and although it was not as simple as a Beyond Grade A fighting a Calamity Grade Super, it was still a crushing victory.

The next moment, a channel opened up on the fingertips of the mechanical finger, swallowing the ambered Secret Tree King.

After doing this, Han Xiao turned around and faced the rapidly expanding green light belonging to the Ancestral Tree King.

Seeing this, Han Xiao's eyes sparkled. He could roughly guess why the Secret Tree King had fled so decisively and was so afraid of him.

"So that's how it is. The World Tree also has the power of a Beyond God. The reason why the Secret Tree King has no fighting spirit is that he has seen this power before… Maybe the Transcendent Grade of the World Tree has already unlocked the ability to kill using the information form state. Therefore, in his opinion, whether he self-destructs or not, I can directly attack him in the information state and kill him completely, since I can break the mechanism of the World Tree and strip him of his immortality. That's why the Secret Tree King is so afraid of me…"

Han Xiao immediately became alert.

"If that's the case, doesn't that mean that the Transcendent Grade of the World Tree can also threaten me?"

Without another word, he opened fire at the green light. He had no habit of waiting for others to transform.

Right at this moment, the green light suddenly exploded, and a gigantic tree palm extended out from the light. Green light gushed out from the palm and turned into a barrier, blocking the torrential attacks of the mechanical army.

The figure of the Ancestral Tree King had already disappeared, and in its place was a gigantic treant. His entire body was glowing with green light, and countless World Tree Roots were wrapped around his body like woven vine armor. On every part of his body, many small roots grew out like dancing little snakes, tearing open space cracks one after another and absorbing the matter and energy on the other side of the tunnel.

"What f*ckery is this?"

Han Xiao glanced at the interface. The other party's name was [Tree God (Incomplete)], and a large amount of information was filled with question marks. It was clear that its level was higher than his, and it was also at the Transcendent Grade.

"Interesting, the World Tree still has such a method hidden. Why have they never used it before…"

Han Xiao frowned, pondering in suspicion.

In the war in his previous life, the World Tree had never used this method. Logically speaking, since their nest had been destroyed, they should have used all their trump cards to stop the enemy. However, even when the three Universal Civilizations blew up the World Tree's main body, the Tree God never descended.

He originally thought that the World Tree did not have the strength of a Transcendent, but it seemed like that was not the case. There were definitely secrets that he did not understand.

At this moment, a mental signal came from the Tree God. There was no clear content, only messy thoughts and intense hunger, much like a wild beast.

"Are you trying to eat me?"

Han Xiao could sense the meaning behind Tree God's words, and his heart skipped a beat.

It seemed like the mind of this Tree God was very chaotic, and he did not have a rational leader controlling it?!

Before he could observe any longer, the Tree God pounced on him and started entangling with the Supreme Heavenly Venerate.

Countless roots of the World Tree shot out, glowing with a green light as they smashed toward Han Xiao's body. They were continuously cut by the Emperor Skysplitter Blade, but new ones quickly grew out.

One was a machine, and the other was a tree. Two huge objects were brawling it out in the space storm. Dozens of Mechanical Oracles led their troops and fired at the Tree God. Every moment, countless attacks landed on the Tree God. However, its health seemed to have no limit. Not only did the body formed by the World Tree Root have high resistance, but it also possessed extraordinary regenerative power.

Oathkeeper and Clotti had already moved far away. The aftershock of the battle between the two Transcendents was too terrifying, and they had no room to interfere. They could only follow behind and watch from afar.

"I didn't expect the World Tree to also have the combat power of a Transcendent Grade, to be able to fight Black Star head-on. If they had used it earlier…"

Clotti's eyes widened in shock.

"Can't you tell? This Beyond God level combatant doesn't seem to be an individual. The World Tree Civilization must have paid some price to create a Transcendent Grade level combatant." Oathkeeper shook his head and analyzed calmly. "Furthermore, he and Black Star aren't evenly matched. Look, he's already at a disadvantage."

Due to the incomplete Tree King Crowns, the Tree God advent this time was not complete, and its combat capability was not at its peak. After fighting for a while, the Tree God gradually fell into a disadvantage under Han Xiao's fierce attacks. It could only rely on its strong physical strength to resist the attacks, and the number of times it attacked decreased.

Han Xiao also felt the weakness of the Tree God, and he started to analyze.

Although he is at the Transcendent Grade, his combat power seems to be lacking. It should be because of that 'incomplete' title. This is not the complete form of the Tree God yet… Could I have been involved in this?

Han Xiao's thoughts raced. Although he did not know the conditions for the Tree God's Advent, when he thought about how one of his requirements was to find Supers from the other four classes as helpers when he advanced to the Transcendent Grade, he had a vague guess.

The composition of the five Tree Kings is similar to the requirement to advance to the Transcendent Grade. Could this be the birth condition of the Tree God? If that's the case, I've sealed the Heart Tree King and the Secret Tree King, so the complete version of the Tree God cannot be activated?

The more Han Xiao thought about it, the more likely it seemed.

Does this mean that I accidentally weakened the other party's trump card?!

Amazing! Let's see who dares to say that I'm unlucky in the future. I might be usually unlucky, but I've never failed at a critical moment!

Chapter 1416: Fight and Gap

Boom!

The battle between the two Transcendents became more and more intense. The battlefield was moving rapidly in the spatial storm as if it had split into two clusters of light, one black, and one green. They were entangled with each other and were crazily eroding each other's space. The sound of the energy shockwave was constantly heard, and it burst out with strong light one after another. It was like Armageddon, or the birth of the world.

Countless mechanical soldiers flew out from Han Xiao's Godly Stronghold. From afar, they looked like black smoke released by the Supreme Heavenly Venerate, turning into thousands of streams. Some were like whips, constantly clashing with the World Tree Roots, while others released billions of rays of light, bombarding the various parts of the Tree God.

Among them, there were dozens of specks of light, the size of dust, jumping around the Tree God's body, tearing off roots one after another. These were the many Mechanical Oracles under Han Xiao. They all had different abilities, and under the enhancement of Mechanical Force, they had strength that far exceeded normal soldiers. They were all elite units.

Under the continuous accumulation of mechanical soldiers, the body of the Supreme Heavenly Venerate seemed to grow endlessly. On the other side, the speed at which the World Tree Roots was forming on the Tree God also became faster and faster. Under the layers of binding, its body also grew rapidly, and the two huge objects grew at a similar speed.

"Tsk, so big…"

Oathkeeper and Clotti looked at the two of them in shock.

The shockwaves of the battle between the two Transcendents became more and more intense. In order not to be implicated, the two of them had already retreated further away. However, Han Xiao and the Tree God's bodies still occupied their entire field of vision, and they could not even see the entirety of the battle. It was as if they had no end.

At Oathkeeper and Clotti's level, they naturally did not have megalophobia. However, at this moment, as they looked at the two gigantic creatures exuding a terrifying pressure with every movement, they could not help but feel an instinctive fear in their hearts. It was an indescribable fear that existed beyond their range of understanding!

A strong sense of danger surrounded the two of them. The more they looked, the more unstable the energy in their bodies became. Their hearts felt like they were going to jump out of their throats. It was as if they were bursting with the full strength of a Transcendent. It was a scene they could not look at directly!

Unknowingly, waves of terror assaulted their brains, making them want to look away. However, their eyes seemed to have separated from their bodies and were no longer under their control. Their gazes were fixed on the two Transcendents.

Swoosh!

At this time, the Emperor Skysplitter Blade burning with dark blue psionic energy tore apart a large area of the space storm and stabbed into the Tree God's body. However, the roots in the Tree God's body quickly tied up and sewed the wound like needles. At the same time, tiny roots that looked like meat sprouts grew out from the wound and intertwined with each other, healing the wound in the blink of an eye.

In addition, a portion of the psionic energy covered by the blade was absorbed by the Tree God. It also had the devouring ability of the World Tree, so it did not reject any energy.

At the same time, the slashes left by the Emperor Skysplitter Blade in the spatial storm spread rapidly, turning into a spatial rift that tore open a passage to a secondary dimension.

However, not only did the two of them not get pulled in by the attraction force of the secondary dimension, the anti-gravity force on their bodies pulled this secondary dimension out instead. The internal matter gushed out along the space crack and sprayed onto the two of them.

This scene was like a fruit that had a hole in its skin. It was being held tightly, squeezing out all the juice and flesh from the hole, and turned into a mess.

Swoosh—

Every slash of Han Xiao's blade tore open a spatial rift that led to different secondary dimensions. Very soon, many colorful spatial tunnels appeared on the battlefield. Countless secondary dimensions sprayed out streams of matter, and all kinds of strange things were scattered all over the sky. There were also all kinds of strange creatures that were crushed into powder by the shockwaves and fused into the energy storm that the two of them were fighting in.

Looking at the interior of these spatial tunnels, one could see that these secondary dimensions were rapidly drying up, as though their bodies had been hollowed out.

Such a battle had already exceeded the capabilities of a Beyond Grade A. Although the aftermath of their battle could shatter the secondary dimensions, Beyond Grade As were the ones absorbed by the secondary dimensions, destroying the secondary dimensions from the inside. However, the Transcendents could use their own gravitational force to stop the secondary dimensions from absorbing them, and even pull out the 'intestines' of the secondary dimensions.

The Tree God had been resisting Han Xiao's attacks all along. As its roots moved, the almost endless power of the World Tree was released. It was like a green wave, attacking and defending at the same time. It had countless uses and dyed the area with a faint green light.

Ding!

With the Tree God as the center, a special spatial fluctuation was suddenly released. Immediately after, a layer of green world phantom seemed to overlap with the area, spreading out endless faint green light, quickly completing 'taking root'.

The next moment, Han Xiao suddenly felt a strong restraining force, and his strength was suppressed inexplicably. Not only did the Supreme Heavenly Venerate's movements slow down, but the strength of all the mechanical troops also decreased. The power of the Tree God increased instead, and it could teleport freely in this area. Its mobility immediately increased.

"It seems to be a dimension projection…"

After taking a look, Han Xiao recognized what this green world phantom was.

Transcendent Grade had already formed an inner space and inner universe in their body, and a second Void Dimension had been born in their body. The Tree God should also have an inner dimension within its body.

The scene in front of him should be to open up his inner space and summon a dimension projection, turning a certain area outside his body into an inner dimension environment to form his own domain. This would allow him to gain the home-ground advantage and increase his strength and suppress his opponent.

Furthermore, this domain moved along with him, and even if the battlefield was constantly shifting, it would not be affected.

With a thought, Han Xiao activated the Void Dimension consciousness in his body and summoned an inner space projection. A gray domain with blue electric arcs instantly opened up and squeezed out the green domain of the Tree God.

The debuffs brought by the Tree God Domain disappeared immediately. Not only did Han Xiao return to normal, but he also felt the huge buffs brought by the domain. Furthermore, the domain around his body moved according to his will, like a new sense organ.

In the space storm, the grayish-blue and green colors corroded each other, and the Void Domain and the Tree God Domain were separated. Before Han Xiao could even savor the sensation, he felt the pressure of the domain, and he could not help but increase his energy.

Buzz!

The Void Domain immediately expanded outward, compressing the Tree God Domain to a smaller size. At the same time, Han Xiao keenly noticed that the enhancement of his Domain had become stronger, while the Tree God Domain had become weaker.

"Fighting by projecting the inner space? So this is the normal style of a Transcendent Grade battle…"

Han Xiao was overjoyed.

In the past few years, he had been exploring the strength of the Transcendent Grade. Although he had gained some benefits, he did not have any opponents of the same level, nor did he have anyone to learn from. Although the current Tree God was not complete, it was still quite familiar with the usage of the Transcendent's methods. It was enough to give him quite a lot of inspiration and imitate the other party's techniques.

Just fighting with a Transcendent brought him a lot of benefits.

Han Xiao activated Virtual Creation, and the various materials in the Godly Stronghold were consumed rapidly. In the blink of an eye, a super-large cannon appeared behind him. Its caliber was almost the size of a small planet, and its barrel was as deep as an abyss.

This type of giant cannon was already considered an interstellar mega machinery, and it would take quite some time to build. However, it could be built in an instant with [Virtual Creation (Pseudo)]. The efficiency was multiplied countless times.

In Han Xiao's opinion, the biggest feature of this ability in a battle was to adapt to the situation and create different devices that he needed on the spot even if he had made no preparations.

No matter how strong a foundation a Mechanic had, they would not dare to say that their resources would be able to adapt to all situations. For example, he would not have the time to build a live ammunition cannon of this size. Now, he realized that the Tree God's resistance to energy was a little abnormal. Now that he had a requirement, he could directly use Virtual Creation to create it, which was convenient and fast… Other than not returning the materials after it disappeared, there were no other shortcomings.

Buzz—

Surging energy accumulated in the cannon barrel, and a bright light flashed. A planet-sized giant bullet shot out, carrying huge kinetic energy, and smashed into the Tree God's chest, deeply embedding inside. Large pieces of shattered roots flew everywhere.

The bright light almost blinded Oathkeeper and Clotti. The bullet exploded, instantly splitting the Tree God in half. Countless shrapnels of the bomb with magnetic force burst out, cutting the two parts of the Tree God into pieces.

Han Xiao was about to give chase, but at this moment, the Tree God's body suddenly shrunk rapidly, turning from solid to illusory, fusing into a World Tree Root and disappearing.

"We were only halfway through the battle. Why did he run away?"

Han Xiao destroyed the root of the World Tree but did not sense the power of the Tree God. At the same time, the other party's domain also disappeared. He immediately understood.

The Tree God Domain was also equivalent to the World Tree's 'taking root' area, so it had a connection with the World Tree territory, which meant that the Tree God could teleport to any corner of his hometown instantly. In this aspect, it had the style of the King.

"Not only is he tanky, but he can even run… Tsk, he must be imitating me!"

Han Xiao knew that he had beaten off the Tree God and shook his head.

The main reason was that the appearance of the Tree God was a little sudden for him, so he was not prepared. However, he had already completed his goal of sealing the Secret Tree King, and he had even accidentally exposed another trump card of the World Tree. He did not lose out.

Furthermore, with the Tree God's tankiness, he might not be able to kill this guy before he mastered a way to attack the Information Form.

Speaking of which, why did this Tree God not attack him at the Information Form layer just now? Are there any conditions to use it, or could it be that the incomplete version of the Tree God could not use this move?

"Although this so-called Tree God doesn't seem to be my match, it seems to have the ability to destroy Information Form, so I need to deal with it carefully… Also, after this battle, my combat power has been exposed, and I don't know how the World Tree will react. I have to think about it carefully."

Han Xiao pondered.

He calmed himself down and opened the interface to take a look.

"However, I didn't expect to trigger a mission like this. I thought that the challenge mission would only go as high as a Beyond Grade A. After all, it's understandable to challenge Beyond Grade As. To let the players challenge Transcendents… so senseless? There's no chance of success at all. To think that such a mission would be triggered."

At this moment, Oathkeeper and Clotti finally relaxed. Their hands and feet were cold, and their hearts were still beating rapidly.

Although the battle had already ended, the terrifying pressure from the battle between the two Transcendents had already been deeply imprinted in their memories. It was like an ordinary person riding a small boat and being helpless in the storm. The indescribable terror that came from their instincts still lingered in their minds, leaving a deep impression that could not be erased.

"I didn't expect that even a Super at my level would be so afraid. The difference between the life levels is too huge. Is this the Transcendent Grade…"

Oathkeeper wiped his non-existent cold sweat.

At this moment, he suddenly felt that being a follower seemed quite good…

Chapter 1417: The Behind-the-Scenes and the Truth

Since his Luck Glow guinea pigs were not around at the moment, it was not a good time to complete the mission. Han Xiao closed the interface and looked at Oathkeeper and Clotti.

"Do you not have anything to do? Is the war over? Did the enemy retreat?"

"No…" Oathkeeper and Clotti regained their senses and shook their heads.

"Then what are you guys doing here? Aren't you going to deal with the enemy?"

"I'll go now."

Oathkeeper immediately stepped into the spatial rift, searching for a shallow dimension battlefield to join.

Clotti looked at Han Xiao deeply before disappearing.

The three Universal Civilizations did not monitor the battle between the two Transcendent Grade Supers in the spatial storm, but he remembered everything. Be it Black Star's terrifying combat strength or the fact that the World Tree had a Transcendent Grade trump card, he had to report this important information to the upper echelons.

Han Xiao did not retract his troops, only shrinking the body size of his Supreme Celestial Venerable. He tore open a spatial rift that led to a battlefield, before controlling the Mechanical Deity to walk in.

The battleships that filled the sky were shooting and killing each other. Their formations were interconnected, and the battle was intense. The three Universal Civilizations were in a dire situation, and they were being surrounded and destroyed.

When the World Tree Blessed Race saw a Mechanical Deity covered in black clouds descend, they immediately changed the direction of their attacks and fired at it.

The Supreme Heavenly Venerate however did not move at all. The mechanical soldiers that formed a black cloud beside him immediately split up and blocked in front of him. At the same time, they activated their shields, forming a gigantic psionic shield that protected the entire Supreme Heavenly Venerate. All of the fleet's firepower was blocked and the surface of the shield was covered in bright lights and ripples.

Han Xiao raised the Emperor Skysplitter Blade and pointed it at this large World Tree fleet that covered the entire sky. He twisted his arm slightly and spun the blade in a semicircle. The next moment, an invisible psionic wave spread out from the tip of the sword and quickly engulfed most of the fleet.

The next moment, countless battleships exploded at the same time. Their shields shattered and disappeared, all of them malfunctioning and falling in different directions.

Wherever the psionic waves passed, battleships fell like raindrops!

As he was now, Han Xiao no longer needed to use the Human Wave Tactic to deal with a large number of troops. The Psionic Wave was a killing machine for group battles, and it was finally used on the official battlefield. The number of fleets was almost meaningless in front of this technology.

"This black technology is more useful than I expected. It was not in vain that I strengthened you into a Divine Artifact."

Looking at the spectacular sight of the spaceships falling from the sky, Han Xiao could not help but feel happy.

This time, he had revealed his strength to seal the Secret Tree King. There was no need for him to continue hiding, so he naturally chose to join the battle.

"Lord, there are too many battlefields. Do you need us to attack?"

Psionic Prime asked respectfully as he stood on the shoulder of the Supreme Heavenly Venerate with the rest of the Mechanical Oracles.

"Bring your children to help." Han Xiao nodded.

As soon as he said that, the dozens of Mechanical Oracles immediately took action. They each brought a group of mechanical troops and headed to different shallow dimension battlefields to support the three Universal Civilizations.

With the support of Han Xiao's Mechanical Force, the combat power of the mechanical army was extraordinary. With a huge leap, the mechanical army entered the battlefield one after another, giving the various World Tree Blessed Race members a huge blow.

Han Xiao, on the other hand, controlled the Supreme Heavenly Venerate to move alone. The huge Mechanical Lifeform strolled through the battlefields one after another, waving the enormous double-bladed sword, the Emperor Skysplitter Blade, and constantly activating its AOE. Psionic waves slashed out like light blades, sweeping through the World Tree fleets.

After fighting for an unknown period of time, Han Xiao could not remember how many of the World Tree Blessed Race he had wiped out. Suddenly, the World Tree fleet stopped firing at the same time in the various shallow dimensions.

Their blitzkrieg had started with great momentum, and they wanted to end the battle quickly. However, they had now kicked on an iron plate. Seeing that the situation was not going to work, the Blessed Race finally gave up on this invasion and chose to retreat.

"We finally repelled the World Tree."

In the meeting room of the leader of the main universe, the three Universal Civilizations' leaders looked at the scene of the World Tree Army retreating and finally relaxed.

"It was not easy for the World Tree to find an opportunity to open up the second frontline. They will not give up so easily. After resting for some time, they might make a comeback." Louis pondered.

The Pope nodded and added with a worried tone, "The opening of the second battlefront is extremely disadvantageous for us. The secondary dimension battlefield is a meat grinder that is even more terrifying than the main universe's border. The main purpose of this battle is to fight head-on, and the losses will not be low. While their fleet can be constantly renewed, our losses are real. Although the Underworld can store the souls of most of the fallen warriors, Aurora's current energy level cannot take care of all the losses of our soldiers in the interstellar battlefield…"

Marbruce clasped his hands together and suddenly said, "It's not a big problem. The enemy has an army, and we have Black Star."

Hearing this, the other two had complicated expressions.

After receiving Clotti's report, they finally knew the true strength of a Transcendent. They had already tried their best to raise their expectations, but they had still underestimated Han Xiao's strength.

"Sigh, the combat power of a Transcendent is truly astonishing. However, I didn't expect the World Tree to also have another Transcendent," the Pope said with surprise.

"Luckily, Black Star has stepped into the same grade. Otherwise, no one on our side would be able to counter the World Tree's trump card. We would definitely suffer heavy casualties…"

The three of them had mixed feelings and some lingering fear.

The Transcendent Grade Black Star made them extremely afraid, but he also gave them a sense of security. If Black Star did not break through this limit, the galactic society would be at an absolute disadvantage in terms of individual strength. Once the Tree God descended, they would be easily defeated.

The current situation was barely stable, and at least half of it was due to Black Star's efforts. The contribution he had made was greater than all three of them combined.

"However, after this battle, the World Tree should have been frightened by Black Star. The next time it wishes to attack the shallow dimensions, it will probably think twice before making such plans."

The three of them nodded and heaved a sigh of relief.

...

World Tree Territory, Tree King Palace.

Green lights gathered on the throne and condensed into the bodies of the Ancestral Tree King and the Fortitude Tree King. Both of them had ugly expressions, not only because the Secret Tree King was sealed, but also because of the consequences of the Tree God's advent.

"The Secret Tree King is also gone… I didn't expect the Mechanic, who was still a peak Beyond Grade A ten years ago, to have stepped into the Transcendent Grade."

The Ancestral Tree King rubbed his forehead, trying to alleviate the pain in his soul. He spoke with a hoarse voice that was filled with shock and anger.

The moment Black Star revealed his true strength and instantly captured the Secret Tree King, he was shocked. Knowing that the Secret Tree King probably could not be saved, he decisively gave up on the Secret Tree King and activated the Tree God's Advent without hesitation.

The arrival of the Tree God was like mixing the bodies and souls of the five Tree Kings together. It was extremely painful, as it forcibly formed a new consciousness between them, fusing with the will of the mother tree. The aftereffects were very severe. After disintegrating, the Tree Kings would have cognitive disorders from time to time, and their minds would be in a mess for a long time before recovering.

If not for the fact that he had no other choice, the Ancestral Tree King would not have wanted to use it. It was not because he wanted to compete with Black Star, but because he was worried that if he did not summon the Tree God, he would not be able to escape from Black Star's hands, inevitably following in the footsteps of the Secret Tree King.

In addition, every time the Tree God descended, it would severely deplete the power of the Tree King Crown, causing the powers of each Tree King to decrease. It would take time for the Crown to recover. The time taken for the Tree King Crown to return to its peak was also the cooldown period for the Tree God's Advent. If the Tree Kings used the Tree God's Advent consecutively, the Tree King Crowns would shatter and disappear after three times. It would take thousands of years for it to be reborn, which meant that the Tree Kings would no longer have any special bonuses during this time. It would be a mere title.

Furthermore, the descent of the Tree God required a special fuel. It was a material called the 'Legacy of the King'. When a Tree King failed to advance to the Transcendent Grade and died, this special material would be produced. The mother tree could not convert this and could only store it. Although it had accumulated over the years, the number of Tree Kings who chose to advance in recent times was decreasing. Each 'Legacy of the King' used would mean one less… and only the Ancestral Tree King knew about this!

As the most experienced tree king, the Ancestral Tree King also knew another secret—any member of the World Tree would die if they chose to advance to the Transcendent Grade. This had nothing to do with their talent but was rather a restriction of the mother tree.

In the beginning, the mother tree was not as strong as it was now. Instead, through the feedback provided by its civilization, it had devoured countless things to grow to its current state.

Only by devouring something new and possessing the information state of that thing would the World Tree be able to unlock the corresponding abilities. The World Tree had never devoured a Transcendent Grade Super before, so Beyond Grade As were the individual limits of the World Tree Supers.

However, this did not mean that the members of the World Tree would not be able to advance. In fact, as long as a Tree King could step into the Transcendent Grade, they would be able to take back their information state that had been devoured by the mother tree. They would then be separated from the World Tree and gain their freedom.

However, the World Tree would not allow any member to escape its control. So long as someone tried to advance, not only would the mother tree not protect them, but it would also automatically interfere. This was because everyone's Information Form was under its control, thus it could easily trigger a vicious mutation during their promotion. Therefore, in terms of strength, one would never reach the Transcendent Grade. All the Tree Kings that had tried to advance had died and turned into the 'Legacy of the King', which was the Beyonder's Vestige, stored in the World Tree.

Therefore, the will of the Mother Tree had such a strong appetite after it descended as the Tree God Advent, and it could not wait to eat Black Star… So long as it devoured this true Transcendent Grade life form, it would be able to obtain the information form of the Transcendent Grade and unlock the upper limit of individual strength.

Of course, there would be a price to be paid for the ability to revive indefinitely. Their upper limit was shackled, and only when the World Tree grew would their upper limit be increased… However, no one except the Ancestral Tree King knew about this.

The Ancestral Tree King never chose to advance because he did not want to benefit others. Furthermore, he kept this secret and did not tell the subsequent Tree Kings.

All sorts of thoughts flashed through his mind, and the Ancestral Tree King said with a deep voice,

"The timing of that Mechanic's advancement is too coincidental. Our luck is not on our side. Luckily, I took back the crown of the Secret Tree King at the crucial moment. Otherwise, the power of the Tree God would have dropped even further."

"The Secret Tree King can't be saved now. Who are you planning to let inherit this title?"

The Fortitude Tree King clenched his teeth as he held his head in pain and asked.

"…Let's think about it again."

The Ancestral Tree King's expression was grave as he looked at the three empty thrones. His mood was extremely bad.

Of the five Great Tree Kings, one had died, two had been sealed, and only two were left. When had they ever been in such a sorry state during their battles in the universe?!

This was a truly miserable outcome…

Furthermore, the person who stayed behind to accompany him was the most annoying salted fish, the Fortitude Tree King. This caused the Ancestral Tree King to only feel more tired.

The one he wanted to eliminate the most was the Fortitude Tree King. It was not only because this guy liked to slack off, but also because he suspected that he might have guessed something. That was why he was so lazy and did not bother to advance anymore.

The Fortitude Tree King however did not notice the look in the Ancestral Tree King's eyes and said worriedly, "The Tree God's Advent is incomplete, and we are no match for that Mechanic. Our individual strengths are also completely suppressed. What should we do in the future?"

"We can only temporarily give up on the battle of individual strength. Don't let the high-level combatants make a move, or we'll be sealed one by one. Furthermore, we probably won't be able to save the Heart Tree King. That Tree King Crown might be lost forever…"

The Ancestral Tree King was depressed.

"What about the mother tree's natural enemy?" the Fortitude Tree King asked with a worried tone.

"…That is another time bomb. I have to think of something."

The Ancestral Tree King's expression darkened.

The World Tree was originally very calm about this war. It was in no hurry and was fearless like a fisherman.

However, the appearance of the Pivotal Snake had hit their weak spot, causing their advantageous situation to become precarious. They had no choice but to race against time, causing themselves to fall into a quagmire!

If it was just the coordinates of the mother tree's main body being exposed, the Ancestral Tree King would not panic. He had always emphasized that the main body could not be moved, but the main body of the mother tree was not fixed. Although the moving process was troublesome, it could indeed be transplanted into other secondary dimensions.

The reason he had revealed the fake information was to leave himself a way out. He was akin to a crafty rabbit with three burrows, and he could also use that as a trap… However, no civilization had forced him to reveal this trump card, so the Ancestral Tree King had kept it a secret until now.

However, a Pivotal Snake in its adulthood could sense the location of the mother tree's main body at any time. It was equivalent to a radar that could locate the mother tree from an infinite distance. No matter how many times the main body was transplanted, it would be useless. This was a huge matter regarding the survival of the civilization, and the Ancestral Tree King had to take it seriously!

However, even if the World Tree could sense its natural enemy, the Pivot Snake was protected by the Mechanic, and they had almost no chance at all. This was the biggest threat!

After thinking about it, he was still at a loss as to what he could do.

The only way he could think of now was to destroy the three Universal Civilizations without caring about the casualties. This way, even if Black Star had the Pivotal Snake, it would be difficult for him to gather enough strength to attack the mother tree.

"Even so, it will only treat the symptoms and not the root cause. That Mechanic will forever be a threat to the mother tree…

If there are no new variables, I'm afraid…"

The Ancestral Tree King clenched his fists. A layer of haze covered his heart, and his expression wavered.

Chapter 1418: Han Xiao: Thank You for Delivering a Trump Card

The World Tree Blessed Races lost in the secondary dimension battlefield, and the alliance army that was originally fighting at the frontline of the Flickering World also stopped attacking and temporarily retreated. Compared to the danger of fighting in the shallow layer dimension, the defensive perimeter of the Flickering World border was impregnable.

With this wave of attacks, many of the shallow layer dimensions were riddled with holes. Although they managed to repel the enemies, the damage was not small because the battlefield was in the territory controlled by the three Universal Civilizations. A portion of the territory was destroyed, and the three Universal Civilizations quickly cleaned up the battlefield and repaired all kinds of war facilities.

Han Xiao, on the other hand, withdrew his abilities and left a portion of his mechanical army to help clean up the battlefield. He then used remote projection to meet with the leaders of the three Universal Civilizations.

As soon as Han Xiao arrived, he heard a round of bootlicking.

"Black Star, you've worked hard!"

"Luckily, we repelled the World Tree Blessed Races. If we let the enemy destroy our territory in the secondary dimension, we would have been in a passive position and would have dragged down the battlefront of the main universe. This was all thanks to you. We thank you on behalf of the entire Galactic Society."

"I didn't expect the World Tree to also have Transcendent Grade combat power, but it's still not as strong as you. We trusted the right person."

Han Xiao raised his brows and looked at the three of them. They had friendly smiles on their faces, and their attitude was even friendlier than before.

"Alright, alright, stop bootlicking."

Han Xiao did not feel anything.

He knew the three of them too well. They were just afraid of his Transcendent Grade strength, so they were not stingy with the praises and wanted to gain favorability with him.

Hearing this, the three of them did not speak anymore. Marbruce asked curiously, "You fought with the World Tree's Transcendent. How do you feel? Is there any pressure?"

Han Xiao shook his head and said,

"The World Tree's Transcendent is called the Tree God, and it doesn't seem to be a single life form. It might be an individual created through some form of fusion. I realized that its combat power wasn't at its peak. I am guessing that the Tree God's bad state is related to the two Tree Kings being sealed…"

He briefly explained his discovery.

"In that case, it seems like you did a good job sealing the Heart Tree King back then. You have foresight," Louis praised.

Han Xiao waved his hand. "Don't be too happy yet. Although I can deal with the Tree God, it will be very difficult to kill him. His regeneration ability is as amazing as mine, and he can turn illusory and return to the inside of the World Tree at any time, as agile as me."

"It can't be, doesn't that mean he is just as disgusting as you… Ahem, I mean, tricky…" Marbruce quickly coughed and changed his words.

Han Xiao rolled his eyes.

"Anyway, the Tree God is not easy to deal with. However, I feel that this ability cannot be used casually. There should be a price to pay. Otherwise, they would have used the Tree God to kill everyone ten years ago."

The three of them nodded and looked at each other as if they had come to an agreement.

"Black Star, we have an idea, or rather, a request. We hope that you can temporarily guard the secondary dimension alone."

Han Xiao raised his brows. "You mean, other than the fleet, I will be the only high-level combatant in the entire shallow layer dimension? No matter how many Beyond Grade As the World Tree sends out, I'll deal with them alone?"

"With your ability, one person is equivalent to hundreds of Beyond Grade As. There's no need for the other combatants to stay here. We believe in your ability. You can guard the secondary dimensional battlefield alone!"

Marbruce's tone was serious, and his words had the meaning of 'we have high hopes for you'.

Han Xiao curled his lips. "If I didn't know that you guys don't dare to have an internal conflict now, I would have thought that you guys are trying to trick me."

"You must have misunderstood us. We're not like that." The three of them looked helpless.

"I think you guys misunderstood your own image. When did you become human?"

Han Xiao shrugged and said casually,

"Alright, since you guys want me to hold the fort alone, I will guard the secondary dimension alone. It's not difficult anyway."

Because the World Tree's main body was rooted in the secondary dimension, this was the main battlefield to further resist the foreign enemies. Han Xiao had originally planned to wait here for the opportunity.

This time, Han Xiao suddenly thought of something, and his tone became serious. "Speaking of which, the time when the World Tree discovered the expeditionary army outposts was a little coincidental. It happened not long after the appearance of the Pivotal Snake. I suspect that the two are related."

Hearing this, the three of them instantly perked up.

"What are your guesses? Share them."

"I've told you about the Pivotal Snake's ability. When it matures, it will be able to track the location of the World Tree's main body. Therefore, I suspect that there is a two-way connection between the World Tree and it. With the World Tree's maturity, it might be able to sense the Pivotal Snake's location. Therefore, the outposts were exposed."

"Then what do you plan to do?" The three of them were slightly shocked.

Since I'm guarding the secondary dimension, I can also protect this key trump card, the Pivotal Snake, and bring it with me. No matter how the World Tree attacks, they will have to get past me first.

Han Xiao paused before continuing.

As for how to prove this point, it will depend on what the World Tree does next. If they have the information about the Pivotal Snake, they will know that they are on the passive side, and they will definitely go crazy and strengthen their attacks, not caring about the losses, all for the sake of time… They don't have to do this just because I have shown extraordinary combat strength, so once the World Tree shows signs of this, it would mean that my guess is correct.

"Good idea. Let's do it your way."

The three of them relaxed and expressed their trust.

After discussing the follow-up plan for a while, Han Xiao deactivated the projection and returned to his room.

He first went to check on the status of the Pivotal Snake. The Pivotal Snake did not get involved in the battle and remained indifferent to him.

The Realmless King, who had already been promoted to a stockman from the trash station owner, was even more respectful, indicating that he would play with the snake seriously.

Leaving behind more Mechanical Oracles to protect the Pivotal Snake, Han Xiao then changed into the King and teleported back to the main universe, arriving at the Siebert Fortress at the border of the Flickering World.

He easily found a group of mascots, and without a word, used a combo attack 'crouching dragon touch Feidin'.

After getting enough luck, Han Xiao closed the door and opened the interface to complete the Tree God's challenge mission.

The format of the mission was the same as the Beyond Grade A Challenge mission, with the duration as the rating, but the reward was many times higher.

The two of them had fought for a long time, and he had already unlocked all the levels of rewards. The experience reward that he had accumulated from this mission had replaced [Ending the Darkness] to become the highest experience gain mission that he had ever seen. It had reached a total of 2.4 Trillion Experience which was more than double the experience reward of [Ending the Darkness]. In other words, it was equivalent to more than 20 Manison.

The other rewards also appeared.

You have received [Character Summon Card - Tree God (Incomplete)]!

Character Summon Card - Tree God (Incomplete): [World Tree Devouring] 一 Devour materials or energy to convert into the power of the World Tree to replenish your energy. You can summon World Tree Roots. Usage: 0/4]

"Recovery ability? It's so-so… However, if I used this Character Summon Card, would I be devouring things or helping the World Tree devour?"

Han Xiao scratched his head.

When he fought with the Tree God, if he used this move to summon the World Tree Roots, would the roots listen to him or the other party?

Furthermore, if the World Tree saw that he could summon the roots of the World Tree, would it think that he was its half-brother ‽

You have received a reward: Draw one of Tree God's Ability/Talent.

Note: Tree God is a special life form. Parts of abilities have been adjusted.

Randomizing… complete!

Please select one of the five options below as the reward.

[Tree King Crown —Liberation] —Ability: Merge Tree King Crowns to summon the Tree God. Liberating a Tree King Crown will increase the Tree God's strength, but the price is the destruction of the Tree King Crown.

[Information Uniqueness—Conceptual Immortality] —Talent: As long as there are information carriers in the entire universe that record your deeds, as long as someone still recited your name, you will not completely perish. Even if your soul and body perish, you will be reborn in a certain time and space through information state disturbance.

[Mental Network — World Tree] — Ability: Enter the World Tree's Symbiotic Mental Network. No delay in communication with any life form of the World Tree regardless of the distance.

[Inner Space Enhancement] — Talent: Your Inner Space is stronger and harder to break.

[Information Form Obliteration] — Talent: You can ignore space restrictions and damage the other party's Information Form base, causing damage. At the same time… Individual memory, network data, book records, and other information carriers will also be affected.

Hiss…

Han Xiao took a deep breath.

"As expected, the Transcendent Grade has the ability to attack Information Form and can be used against people of the same level."

He carefully browsed through it a few times and roughly understood the mechanism of [Information Form Obliteration]. To explain it simply, it was probably to eliminate all traces of the other party's existence in the world. Not only would everyone forget about him, but even the internet data and text records would disappear. It was specifically used to restrain [Information Uniqueness—Conceptual Immortality]. It was similar to the information form of the sub-body of the Destiny's Child. It could not be observed or spread.

As for the revival mechanism of the World Tree and the Underworld Hero Spirit, there was a high chance that they would be broken, and those who were affected would die completely. As for the Sanctum Revival, he was not sure if it would be affected.

However, this talent could not be used casually. One of the most important factors was the state of the target… Even if there was a huge difference in strength, as long as the target could resist, [Information Form Obliteration] would not work.

The simplest trigger condition was for the target to be on the verge of death or be in a state of 'death', or be killed by the ability user.

At this time, Han Xiao also realized that this was the reason why the Secret Tree King did not dare to self-destruct. Self-destructing in front of him was equivalent to giving up on resisting, exposing his belly and letting him do whatever he wanted. However, this guy did not expect that he did not have this ability before.

"I didn't know how to do this, but you guys personally gave this ability to me. Thank you."

Han Xiao laughed.

After pondering for a while, he finally decided to choose [Information Form Obliteration].

Perhaps he would be able to unlock this skill by himself later on, but he had no clue at the moment. Who knew what the conditions would be for him to comprehend it?

Han Xiao had always believed that only the benefits on hand were meaningful, and this ability was the trump card that he urgently needed in the current situation.

Furthermore, he had a worry.

Han Xiao had always thought that the three Universal Civilizations had won after blowing up the World Tree's main body in his previous life, but now that he saw that the Tree God had the [Information Uniqueness—Conceptual Immortality], would it also be used on the World Tree's main body?

Did the three Universal Civilizations' victory in his previous life end the war once and for all, or was it temporary peace? Did the World Tree disappear, or was it reborn somewhere?

Even though the possibility of this speculation was not high, Han Xiao felt that he had to obtain the [Information Form Obliteration] as insurance.

You have received the new talent [Information Form Obliteration]!

The next moment, a mysterious feeling appeared in Han Xiao's mind. He turned to look at the metal table beside him.

His vision changed. He seemed to be able to see fine threads extending from the table, penetrating the wall and extending into the distance. Following these threads, he seemed to see all the information carriers related to it. He seemed to be able to see the source of the materials of this table, where they were processed, assembled, and how they were transported to this place. How many people were in contact with it…

However, when he wanted to take a closer look, these images disappeared as though it was just an illusion.

"Interesting."

Han Xiao looked around the room. Many threads extended from the objects, which meant that they were connected to various information carriers. He had a feeling that he could cut these threads.

"I can only see the connection, but I can't see the exact situation… If this ability is improved further, won't it mean that I will be omniscient? Could this be the development path of a Transcendent?"

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

Suddenly, he had an idea. He opened the interface, wanting to see the information connection of the interface. However, there were only two threads. One was connected to him, and the other extended indefinitely.

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and suddenly had a bold idea.

"What will happen if I cut this… Forget it, I'd better not create trouble now."

Chapter 1419: Super Star Cluster Frustrated, Version Update

Han Xiao shook his head and retracted his [Information Form Obliteration] vision.

The ability that he drew this time was not too bad. In his mind, the Tree God was ranked third on the Good Guy List, and the second was the Germinal Organization leader.

The first place could only belong to Manison.

Speaking of which, the Tree God still has quite a lot of good stuff on it. It would be great if I could draw a few more times… However, the World Tree probably won't use this trick on me so easily anymore. I don't think the chances are high.

Han Xiao stroked his chin and pondered.

During this extraction, he had also seen a portion of the Tree God's abilities from the options. Among them, [Tree King Crown —Liberation] confirmed his guess. The Tree God was indeed a product of the fusion of the various Tree Kings, and it seemed to consume a lot of energy. Since he had defeated the Tree God, the possibility of the other party using this move against him would not be high.

"However, based on the current situation, the three Universal Civilizations have turned from passive to active. They're the ones who are on pins and needles."

Han Xiao smiled to himself.

The current situation was much better than in his previous life. Most of it came from his hard work—I am carrying the entire galactic society!

At this moment, black flames appeared in front of him and quickly formed Oathkeeper's soul projection.

"Your Excellency Black Star, the three Universal Civilizations are cleaning up the battlefield, and our Holy Accord organization has already taken the opportunity to evacuate. We have not crossed paths much. What are your next instructions?"

Han Xiao glanced at Oathkeeper and saw how obedient he was. He could not help but laugh. "Your attitude changed very quickly. Are you afraid after seeing my heroic appearance?"

"…" Oathkeeper's eyes twitched, but he did not speak.

There was no way he would admit it. Not in this life.

Seeing that he did not reply, Han Xiao clicked his tongue and said, "Don't be so reserved. I still like your arrogant look."

"…Stop joking."

"Alright, alright, I won't tease you anymore." Han Xiao smiled. His expression then turned serious, and he said, "The Holy Accord has been exposed to the world this time, but I don't plan to let you guys debut… cough, I'm talking about leaving the seclusion. Anyway, you guys can continue to return to the dark side. Without my call, you don't have to take the initiative to participate in the battle, and you don't have to have too much contact with the three Universal Civilizations. It's best to communicate everything through me."

"Then what will the association say? They will definitely ask when this batch of revivors appeared. If you keep hiding it, they might become suspicious…" Oathkeeper said.

"You don't have to worry about that. I will explain it to them under the premise of hiding the details of the Holy Accord."

Han Xiao waved his hands.

"Alright." Oathkeeper nodded.

"By the way, there's one more thing. Members of the Holy Accord can choose not to fight, but you have to contribute your technology in the secondary dimensions, such as Dimension Exile Bullets, Energy Disorder Shockwave, and so on to be used in war."

"Alright, I'll listen to you."

Oathkeeper had already lost his anger from being tortured by Han Xiao, so he agreed expressionlessly.

...

At the same time, the Super Star Cluster Alliance was holding a meeting. The leaders of the various civilizations had complicated expressions on their faces.

"The three Universal Civilizations have repelled the secondary dimensional invasion of the World Tree… How fierce."

"At this rate, the three Universal Civilizations will be able to stop the enemy outside the territory of the explored universe. The situation will not be chaotic."

"If that's the case, we won't be able to carry out the plan…"

The leaders did not know what to say.

The Super Star Cluster Alliance had originally planned to leave the explored universe with their entire civilization while the three Universal Civilizations were busy fighting the World Tree Civilization.

However, from the looks of it, the three Universal Civilizations had not fallen into a hard battle at all. They were very stable!

It was all Black Star's fault. He did not even give them a chance to start their plan!

"Sigh, leaving the explored universe is one of the few opportunities for us to develop freely. Let's continue watching and hope that the World Tree is more reliable."

The Star Arc Leader sighed helplessly.

This plan was very important to the Super Star Cluster Alliance. Even if the current situation was disadvantageous, they would not give up easily, but it was inevitable for them to feel depressed.

A civilization leader narrowed his eyes and said in a low voice, "Maybe we can help the World Tree…"

However, before he could finish, the Star Arc Leader glared at him and scolded, "Don't drag us down if you want to die! If we're found out, we're dead!"

He could not believe that someone would suggest such a suicidal idea.

No matter how much they wished for the World Tree to disrupt the situation, they could only silently cheer for the World Tree and passively wait for the situation to change. How could they give any substantial help? Wouldn't that be colluding with the enemy ‽

Speaking of this, the Star Arc leader was furious. Your World Tree is so impressive, I thought you could beat up the three Universal Civilizations, but you can't even get past Black Star.

How could they even talk about invading?

What a joke!

...

A few days later, the victory in the shallow layer dimensions was quickly spread throughout the galactic society under the push of the three Universal Civilizations. Although they agreed to Han Xiao's request and did not emphasize the battle between him and the Tree God, it still made the galactic residents very excited.

Originally, when they heard the news of the World Tree invading from the secondary dimension, most of the galactic residents were filled with fear and panic. They only heaved a sigh of relief when they saw the three Universal Civilizations successfully defeating the enemy. They became even more excited, and their confidence in the three Universal Civilizations winning this war increased.

Because they felt that staying in the explored universe was much safer, the level of chaos on various planets had also been greatly reduced. Many galactic residents had settled down, and the frequency of demonstrations had decreased. There were also fewer people running away, making it easier for the administration.

The sudden appearance of the Holy Accord Revivors this time made them an important contributor to the war. However, they left after the battle and did not communicate with the three Universal Civilizations. Their actions were very mysterious and aroused the curiosity of the galactic residents.

On the internet, many galactic residents recognized some of the people based on the Wayne Card combination. They were all famous Beyond Grade As in history.

Thus, all the clues pointed to Black Star, who grasped the Sanctum Revival. Countless galactic residents were passionately thinking about it, and various versions of their speculations were circulating on the internet.

The main planet of the Beyond Grade A Association, conference hall.

All the Beyond Grade As gathered together and stared at Han Xiao.

"Black Star, you have to give us an explanation. Who are those revivors?"

"Exactly! You've been hiding it from us for too long."

"This must have something to do with you. If you say you don't know, I'll ignore you for a month!"

Most of the people who questioned him were Beyond Grade As of the current era, but Beiger, who knew the truth, and the rest of the revivors did not say anything and just watched the show.

"Cough, that…" Kasuyi raised his hand slightly and coughed." Actually, I also know a little about this. "

As soon as he said that, everyone's eyes turned sharp and focused on him.

No way, you knew about it in advance when Black Star first revealed the Sanctum Revival. How did you know about this too? You even helped Black Star hide it from us?

In the past, when we saw your heavy facial features, we felt that you had a lot of experience, so we chose you to be the vice president. Now, it seems like you have already completely turned into Black Star's image!

Sierron, who was standing at the side, was jealous and envious. We're all vice presidents, so why do you know so many secrets? Why am I kept in the dark like a fool? You guys are treating me like a decoration!

Damn it, I can also be a trusted aide. I also want to be in the same boat as Black Star!

Han Xiao was surprised. He turned to Kasuyi and asked, "When did you know?"

"I guessed."

Kasuyi smiled in embarrassment.

During the training period, Han Xiao once entered the Sanctum and got Oathkeeper to contact Kasuyi.

Although Oathkeeper did not reveal anything about the Holy Accord, Kasuyi's first impression was that Oathkeeper was Han Xiao's secret subordinate outside. After some deduction, he guessed that Han Xiao might have a backup plan and might have hidden a batch of revivors. Therefore, Kasuyi was not surprised that the Holy Accord organization had appeared. Instead, he felt that it was 'as expected'.

Han Xiao thought about it for a while and guessed where Kasuyi had learned it from. He did not mind and turned around to look at everyone else.

"I originally planned to explain this to everyone. Back then, when the three Universal Civilizations clashed with the association, I specially got a group of revivors to hide and form a special group. If anything happened to us, we would have a way out and also have ways to counter the enemy, so don't blame me for hiding it.

"You all know what happened after that. The World Tree suddenly invaded, and we made peace with the three Universal Civilizations and fought against the enemy together, so I kept this trump card hidden. Not long ago, the secondary dimensional battlefield was in danger, so I sent them out to help."

Everyone nodded in agreement.

However, Sun Hunter asked casually, "Since they're exposed, why don't they join the association?"

Han Xiao smiled. "This concerns our future development path. In my mind, a portion of the Beyond Grade As should form an organization in the dark, one in the open and one in the dark, guarding each other. Unless something big happens, they will remain in the dark. These mysterious revivors are the first batch of members. They are not simply obeying orders, they also have the idea of retiring, so this mission is very suitable for them.

I plan to keep this system as a place for Beyond Grade As to retire. Once everything stabilizes, if anyone gets tired of conflict and politics, they can choose to retire in this organization and regain their adventurer identity."

As soon as he said that, everyone's eyes flashed. They caught Han Xiao's hidden meaning and could not help but look at him deeply.

It seemed like Black Star would no longer be satisfied with the association after becoming a Transcendent. When the war ended, he would most likely make use of the official position recognized by the three Universal Civilizations to do something big…

'War is indeed the catalyst for ambition…'

Many Beyond Grade As felt this way.

However, from a personal point of view, they did not reject this point. Black Star was an ambitious leader, and it was a good thing for them.

"Then I have no objections."

"Us too."

"You sure have foresight."

Everyone expressed their agreement and gave a round of praise.

Han Xiao smiled and was about to speak when the interface suddenly vibrated.

He was slightly stunned. He opened the interface and looked at the notification. His eyes lit up.

[Version 5.5 started!]

Data is being obtained… Data obtained!

Player forums have been opened.

Welcome to"Galaxy"Version 5.5 —[Age of Black Star— War of All Territories]

"Oh, this small update is finally over?"

Han Xiao immediately perked up.

The players had gone offline more than ten years ago due to a mini version update. He did not expect the cute leeks to come back at this time.

However, Han Xiao was not happy for long before his attention was attracted by the change in the name of the version.

"War of All Territories?"

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

According to his experience, the version update would usually be on the eve of some major event.

The situation of the three Universal Civilizations was great, and the World Tree had fallen into a passive state. However, the version had such a name. This made him feel that things were not simple.

"The name of this version refers to whose territory it is. Are we going to overthrow the World Tree, or will the World Tree attack the three Universal Civilizations like in my previous life? They are now blocked outside the border of the Flickering World, do they still have such an opportunity… Hmm, it's best to take precautions and inspect it."

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

Chapter 1420: Online

In one of the Black Star Army bases, white light flashed, and countless army players appeared out of nowhere. Very soon, there was a veritable sea of people.

The players were already familiar with this. They opened the interface to look at the version number while opening the quantum network to look at the current time.

"Oh my, the time span for this version is only slightly more than ten years, much shorter than the last time."

"It's just a small version update, I guess."

"Didn't the three Universal Civilizations say that the World Tree Civilization will enter the territory in ten years? The timing should be just right. It seems like Galaxy Times was right. This is the time for the update, right into the stage of the war."

"It's not easy to finally get a universal war. As long as the version update doesn't directly skip it, I'll be satisfied."

Many players browsed through the events of the past decade as they casually chatted.

There was nothing much worth paying attention to during the ten years of preparation. Only the changes in the Beyond Grade A population interested many players.

"No way, Lagi is already a Beyond Grade A Super?"

"The gambling dog Hadavy hasn't advanced yet? Hahahaha, I knew it!"

"Nero's life is really smooth-sailing. Is this what it means to be a part of the later generations…"

"F*ck! EsGod was already released, and he even killed a Tree King? Amazing!"

"Tsk, there are too many new Beyond Grade As. The cost of collecting all the Wayne Cards has increased again."

"F*ck, did Black Star and the Dragon Emperor announce their relationship? Damn it! There's no hope for this old man anymore… My partner was born before I was, and they've already aged when I'm at my peak. Is this what a bitter life is like…"

"What are you thinking? Black Star is mine!"

"They're a perfect match, so how can a demon like me object? Boohoo…"

Many army players flipped through the rumors of Beyond Grade As one after another, their gossipy hearts burning.

Initially, other than Han Xiao and a few other Beyond Grade As, the other top-notch experts did not have much contact with the players. The players did not have a deep impression of them, so they would not deliberately remember them. However, the existence of the Wayne Cards had become a bond between the two parties, which led to the players being extremely familiar with the names and deeds of every Beyond Grade A.

However, compared to the casual players, the professional players were more concerned about utilitarian matters. They were not in the mood to gossip and were mainly gathering useful information to discuss.

Maple Moon analyzed in a low voice. "The name of the version after this update has an additional 'War of All Territories'. The World Tree will most likely be able to fight its way in. This should be the theme of the version."

"Hmm, I did some research on the internet. The World Tree has already reached the border, but it is temporarily blocked by the Galactic Alliance Army. Furthermore, the World Tree invaded from the secondary dimension a few days ago and was forced to retreat. The current situation of the three Universal Civilizations isn't too bad."

Maple Moon looked at the interface and said, "The level cap has been unlocked for this version update. This way, the players in the top tiers should be able to enter the Calamity Grade."

Frenzied Sword nodded in agreement and said, "As our overall strength increases, there will be more ways to increase our strength. Furthermore, some of our abilities will undergo a qualitative change. I think there will be a huge change in this Pro League."

This mini version update did not take long, and the main storyline mission did not change. What the professional players cared about the most was that the level cap was unlocked from level 180 to level 200, and there was room for improvement.

"Let's go to the frontline first and get to the command center to arrange a combat mission."

"Let's go. If we're late, we'll miss out on the good missions."

The players were in an uproar for a while, before they finally understood the current situation. They all took their spaceships to the frontline, and streams of light left the base.

...

On the other side, the main planet of the Beyond Grade A Association.

Han Xiao had already announced the end of the meeting. When he returned to his room, he saw many players online through surveillance.

"Has his level been unlocked to level 200? As long as one doesn't have too many subclasses, the players who grew themselves in the standard manner should be able to enter the Calamity Grade. The scale this time will be huge."

If it was in the past, Han Xiao would have been afraid, but now, he had enough confidence. Even if a large number of players entered the Calamity Grade, they would not be able to cause him much trouble.

Although he had reached the Transcendent Grade, he had yet to reach the limit of that realm, thus he still had to harvest leeks. However, before the last update, he had already harvested a large number of players' wealth. Now that the players had just come online, their wallets were dry. He had to wait for them to earn some money before he could reap the profits.

Furthermore, Han Xiao had found another way to farm EXP, and that was to use psionic waves to rampage on the battlefield. This speed was much faster than the mechanical army, and the cost was extremely low and convenient. Even if there was a level penalty, where the normal members of the World Tree could only provide the lowest 1 EXP, he took whatever he could get.

The people of the World Tree revived continuously, thus they were perfect targets for gaining experience.

Han Xiao decided that he had to have his cake and eat it too.

The players were already on track, so there was no need to worry too much. Han Xiao was more concerned about the meaning of the name of the version since he had no idea what the implications were behind it.

"No matter what, this is a clue…"

Han Xiao nodded to himself.

Under his influence, the direction of "Galaxy" was completely different from his previous life. He had also come into contact with many secrets that the players in his previous life could not touch. He did not dare say that he understood this universe completely. Even if the suspicion based on the name of the version was just groundless speculation, it was better to be cautious.

Han Xiao closed the interface and summoned Phillip to give some orders. He then changed into The King and teleported to Floating Dragon.

Currently, the entire Planet Aquamarine civilization had migrated, and Floating Dragon had followed them. They were currently taking refuge in the Central Galaxy.

In the huge palace of the Dragon Emperor, a light flashed, and Han Xiao's figure appeared out of thin air. He turned around and walked toward Aesop's residence.

Since there were no clues, he would ask the metaphysical.

He soon arrived at his destination and pressed the doorbell.

"You're here?"

Aesop opened the door and invited Han Xiao in.

Han Xiao did not stand on ceremony. He sat on the sofa and smiled. "How didn't you foresee that I would come to find you?"

"Prophecy isn't always effective. Ever since you became a Transcendent, prophecies regarding you have become more and more difficult…"

Aesop shook his head.

"That's true." Han Xiao nodded.

He had already done the test. As a Transcendent, his information projection state had undergone a sublimation, as if it had a certain level of information concealment property. It was difficult for outsiders to predict it.

"Why are you looking for me?" Aesop paused and said, "If it's a prophecy, please forgive me for being powerless. I can't use my ability for the time being."

"Hmm? What happened?"

Han Xiao was slightly stunned. He looked at Aesop carefully and realized that Aesop's face was dispirited, as though he had been seriously ill.

"When I received the passive prophecy the other time, I suffered a backlash. The target of my prophecy was an unprecedented mage who inflicted damage on me. My spirit still needs time to recover. Before that, I can't help you…" Aesop coughed and said with a weak tone.

"You didn't tell Ames?" Han Xiao raised his brows.

"No, she was too impulsive. I don't know how she would react if she knew about this."

Aesop shook his head. He rarely revealed important prophecy information to Ames and would only discuss matters with Han Xiao.

"I was going to tell you, but you rushed to the battlefield before I could say anything."

"When did this happen?" Han Xiao asked.

"Calculating the time, I should have triggered the prophecy just before the expeditionary army outpost was attacked."

Hearing this, Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

Such a coincidence… Could it be the Secret Tree King? That guy was indeed a very powerful mage.

"Do you have any other memories of that mage?"

"No, my foresight was shattered. I can't even remember what he looked like."

"Is that so…" Han Xiao pondered." I might have guessed who this person is. He should be an expert from the World Tree."

"How is he? Did he cause you any danger?"

"Don't worry, I've already sealed him up. If you're angry, you're welcome to visit him anytime."

"Forget it then. I don't have your bad taste." Aesop waved his hand.

Han Xiao smiled, stood up, and was about to leave when Aesop suddenly said, "By the way, when will you and Ames reproduce?"

Han Xiao paused and said helplessly, "How would I know? I can do it anytime, but she doesn't agree. We'll have to see when she changes her mind."

"Heh, she's just being stubborn. As long as the mood is right, everything will be fine." Aesop was instantly energized. "Back then, I traveled around the galaxy and made countless females fall in love with me. If not for my unwillingness, my children would have already spread across the various Star Fields. Let me tell you, I have quite a lot of experience in this area. Come, come, let me teach you some moves…"

"You should keep it for yourself. I don't need it." Han Xiao's eyes twitched.

"Eh, why not? This is all the spiritual wealth left behind by our predecessors. Once you've learned all these tricks, you'll be able to convince Ames. I'm not even willing to teach anyone else… Hey, don't go, at least listen!"

"Get lost."

Han Xiao did not want to bother with this old man who had a rich history of love. He changed into The King and left, leaving Aesop in the room, sighing with regret.

Holy Accord Organization Base, Destiny's Child Laboratory.

With a flash of light, Han Xiao teleported over. The experimenters of the Holy Accord looked up, before continuing with their work.

Han Xiao woke Destiny's Child up with ease. After communicating for a while, he let Destiny's Child predict his concerns.

After a while, Destiny's Child shook his head, indicating that he could not foresee it.

Seeing this, Han Xiao knew that his predictions would most likely not work. The other party had most likely used some sort of information concealment.

"Looks like I can only increase the screening intensity and pay attention to any abnormalities…"

Han Xiao pondered.

...

Central Galaxy, desolate universe belt.

In the secret base of the Star Alliance, a group of observers was gathered in a large room, staring at the device in the middle of the room.

This device was a cylinder with a diameter of about ten meters and a height of about fifteen meters. It was silver-gray, and its surface was connected to many wires. The indicator lights were flashing crazily, and there was a buzzing sound. This was a long-distance material transmission device.

After a while, the material transmission device suddenly shook, separating from the top and bottom. The pillar above slowly rose, and the interior of the pillar was revealed empty. There was a space covered by a transparent cover, and a white suitcase was lying inside.

"My hometown sent it over."

The Observer Captain stepped forward and twisted the valve. He opened the cover of the material transmission device, picking up the white suitcase from within, and opened it on the spot. Inside the suitcase were three white cans without any labels.

He took a pistol-like device from one of the team members and scanned the three cans one by one. After reading the numbers, he nodded.

"Confirmed. They are all particles that have been enciphered."

Everyone was overjoyed.

The Star Alliance had ordered the Observer Team to secretly leak information about the three Universal Civilizations. They had thought of many ways, including using the energy released by the Supernova to transmit a wave-like information surge to the entire universe, as well as using the Star position transmission method to secretly send messages to the World Tree, but they were all rejected.

In the end, the Star Alliance chose to encode the tiny particles. They used the technology of microscopic transcription to spread the particles in the lower dimensions and record a huge amount of information. They then returned to their original form and turned the tiny particles into information carriers, containing all the information they wanted to leak.

The Star Alliance mass-produced a pile of coded particles and prepared to throw them out of the border through the wormhole. This would cause the storage device to self-destruct at a certain time, attracting the attention of the World Tree and spreading the particles at the same time.

They believed that with the technology of the World Tree, they should be able to discover the abnormality of these encoded particles and intercept them.

The Star Alliance had been developing for a long time, and they had a high level of technology. They also had some knowledge of information forms, and they had always provided information cover for the Observer teams. They were not afraid of being discovered through any prophecy. They had secretly stolen the technological results of the galactic society for many years, and they were confident that they would not be discovered.

Chapter 1421: Suspicion

Since he was suspicious, he had to take action. This had always been Han Xiao's style. He told Phillip to monitor the intelligence of the galactic society and report any abnormal movements immediately. However, after being cautious for a few months, he did not discover anything. The situation was still changing.

Because of the Pivotal Snake, the World Tree Civilization could not wait to attack the border defense circle again and again. The other troops entered the battlefield like there was no end to them and did not care about the damage. However, the Galactic Alliance Army was not to be trifled with. How could their defense line be broken so easily?

Even in the secondary dimension battlefront, the World Tree Blessed Races did not believe it and invaded many times. However, with Han Xiao in the shallow layer dimension, it was like an immovable guardian deity. The Blessed Races invaded again and again, but they lost every time. They abandoned countless fleets and escaped many times, allowing Han Xiao to gain a lot of wealth.

The worst part was in the individual strength level. The World Tree realized that they were being completely crushed. The Flickering World had Aurora, the healer, as well as EsGod and Herberlon, who were top-tier combatants; the World Tree experts were exchanging their injuries for nothing. The secondary dimension protector was Han Xiao, who was at the Transcendent Grade. Even the Tree Kings did not dare show their faces, so the others were useless.

All of a sudden, the Holy Tree Emissaries, Ancestral Spirits, and Army Commanders realized that there was no use for them in both battlefronts.

If they had already invaded the territory, they would have been able to move around in the universe nimbly with their individual strength, just like special forces. This would have affected the energy of the enemy civilizations and caused all kinds of damage. However, in the current situation, they could only wait for orders.

After a few months of war, the tens of millions of players had once again integrated into the atmosphere of it. They could choose both fronts, and the missions were much richer. Their wallets also became thicker. Unfortunately, Version 5.5 had unlocked a new level cap, and the players' main goal was to level up. They did not have much money to spend.

As more and more players stepped into the Calamity Grade, the qualitative change also appeared. The players became more prominent on the battlefield, and the three Universal Civilizations paid more attention to them.

From the perspective of the upper echelons, the explored universe was rich in resources. They were able to fight the battle of attrition with the World Tree Civilization for a long period of time because of their strong productivity. However, there was always an end to this path, and the World Tree Civilization was superior in this regard. As time passed, the three Universal Civilizations felt that they would start to weaken sooner or later, and the various hidden dangers of wartime policies would gradually appear.

Of course, this kind of situation would not happen anytime soon, and they were not the ones who were troubled. The three Universal Civilizations were currently sitting on the high platform, and they wished to fight a war of attrition more than the World Tree in exchange for time for the Pivotal Snake to grow. Therefore, the players who had the Calamity Grade potential and could not be killed were important strategic weapons in the eyes of the three Universal Civilizations, and they were not afraid of exhaustion.

The situation had been good for the past few months, and the galactic society was filled with confidence.

Although the players did not know about the Pivotal Snake, after analyzing the situation on the surface, they felt that the three Universal Civilizations were definitely going to win. After learning Black Star's operation, the matter would be settled with F2A[1]. With such an overwhelming advantage, how could they lose‽

At this point, Han Xiao noticed something.

"All the members of the Super Star Cluster Alliance have set up secret stargates in their territory and gathered a large number of civilians, resources, and long-distance battleships. They are suspected to be preparing an escape?"

Han Xiao flipped through the information, his expression changing as he pondered.

Facing the invasion of the enemy, these advanced civilizations left themselves a way out. It was normal for them to make backup preparations. Even though the entire population was optimistic about the war and their confidence was boosted, the advanced civilizations still planned for the worst, which was understandable. Han Xiao had noticed the Super Star Cluster's actions before, but he had not taken it seriously.

However, because of the suspicion of the 'War of All Realms', as well as the fact that everything had been peaceful for the past few months, Han Xiao's skepticism had become more and more serious. Right now, he was a little suspicious about everyone. Even though the Super Star Cluster Alliance's plan was reasonable, it was still a little glaring in his eyes.

Han Xiao recalled the performance of the Super Star Cluster Civilization's troops on the battlefield. Although they had completed their mission, he felt like they had not used their full strength.

In the past, he had thought that the Super Star Cluster was afraid of being used as cannon fodder by the three Universal Civilizations, so they were being cautious. However, when added to his skepticism now, he felt that something else was going on.

After all, the conflict between the Super Star Cluster Alliance and the three Universal Civilizations was deeply rooted. It would not be their style if the Super Star Cluster Alliance did not seize the opportunity to do something in this kind of power reshuffling invasion.

"I feel like they're not just making a Plan B, they have other plans as well…"

Han Xiao stroked his chin and made up his mind to gather the secrets of the Super Star Cluster Alliance.

Anyway, regardless of whether there was a problem or not, it was not a bad thing to investigate. It would be best if he could find some evidence.

After sending a message to Phillip, telling him to pay attention to intelligence about them, Han Xiao exited the quantum network and walked out of the room. A huge cloud appeared in his eyes. Pivotal Snake was hiding inside, and beside it was the stockman Realmless King, as well as a group of mechanical soldiers acting as bodyguards.

Everyone was currently in a secondary dimension, allowing the Pivotal Snake to devour as much as it wanted. Han Xiao had been using the portable fortress to stay close to it, and while protecting it, he was also thinking about how to speed up the Pivotal Snake's growth.

Because of this, he had no choice but to do a full-body check of the Pivotal Snake. Of course, the Pivotal Snake was unwilling, but under his forceful control, it could only stare at Han Xiao with its cold and unwilling eyes, allowing Han Xiao to move its body back and forth.

After checking its body, Han Xiao realized that there was no gender difference in the Pivotal Snake, it could be said to be a hermaphrodite.

After a more detailed examination, Han Xiao also figured out how the Pivotal Snake reproduced, which made him feel a little complicated.

The reproduction of the Pivotal Snake needed to be done in a mating-like manner through the secondary dimension that had given birth to a consciousness, absorbing the secondary dimension in another way and turning it into an embryo. This kind of behavior could be called self-reproducing, or it could be said to be hybrid breeding. It just did not need the 'help' of its own kind.

However, thinking about it, it was likely that the Pivotal Snake would not be able to meet another of its kind in its lifetime. Furthermore, it was being hunted by the World Tree. If it could not reproduce alone, it would probably have gone extinct long ago.

The problem was that the Pivotal Snake usually ate secondary dimensions… In other words, this snake would reproduce with its food…

Furthermore, after sleeping with him, you still want to eat him up as nutrition… Are you a female praying mantis?

All kinds of thoughts flashed through Han Xiao's mind. He looked at the Pivotal Snake who did not even bother to look at him, and had some ideas.

"No matter how much the Pivotal Snake eats, it will at most gain weight and will not enter the mature stage quickly. The growth of a creature has to follow the rules… But if I change the foundation of its existence, I don't know if it will be effective."

Han Xiao had a bold idea.

If the Pivotal Snake was allowed to develop properly, who knew how long it would take for it to reach adulthood. However, if he used [Life Transformation—Virtual] to turn it into an artificial intelligence life form, the difference in life forms would be like the difference between heaven and earth. Would he be able to instill a large amount of data into it to speed up its maturity?

The only problem was that he did not know if the Pivotal Snake could still keep its perception of the World Tree after its existence transformation.

Logically speaking, if the perception came from the Information Form level, it should not have any effect no matter what life form the Pivotal Snake had changed into.

However, Han Xiao did not dare take the risk. There was only one Pivotal Snake, and he could not reverse its transformation.

"If only I could get one more, I could experiment…"

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and looked at the Pivotal Snake.

Why not… let this snake give birth now?

Speaking of which, it's still a cub, can it stick it up?…

Han Xiao fell into deep thought.

While Han Xiao was studying about breeding, the World Tree Civilization made some discoveries.

In the Tree King's palace, the Ancestral Tree King listened to the report from the frontline with a subtle expression.

"Is it confirmed? The particles you intercepted contained a lot of information about the enemy civilization?"

"That's right. These particles used microscopic recording technology that involves the transformation of dimensions. We're still trying to decode them and restore the specific content, but we can't be wrong. There are many spatial coordinates and star maps of the enemy's territory."

"There's such a thing?"

The Ancestral Tree King's eyes flickered.

The two armies were at a stalemate at the border, and the World Tree had also built a base and placed it at the entrance of the three Universal Civilizations. Not long ago, an urgent report came from the frontline. The radar of the frontline station had discovered that there were abnormal spatial reactions and weak signs of energy explosions somewhere a certain distance away. Thus, they sent out an exploration team to check, afraid that the three Universal Civilizations were not satisfied with defending and were creating problems.

However, after some testing, they discovered that it was a temporary wormhole that had disappeared by the time the exploration team had arrived. To be cautious, the exploration team searched along the traces of the energy explosion, and the microscopic vision scanner quickly discovered that some special particles were floating in the area that seemed to have been scattered in all directions by the explosion. Therefore, the exploration team collected a portion of them, but they unexpectedly discovered a large amount of information related to the three Universal Civilizations.

When he first found out about this, the Ancestral Tree King's first reaction was that it was a misleading tactic. He thought that it was fake intelligence from the three Universal Civilizations who wanted to trick them with false information.

The second reaction was that there was a traitor within the three Universal Civilizations. For some reason, they wanted to collude with the enemy… This was not the first time the World Tree had encountered such a thing. In their journey to conquer the universe, as long as the enemy was a composite civilization alliance, the internal structure would not be as solid as iron.

His third thought was that there was a third party, hoping to add fuel to the fire and fish in troubled waters… The World Tree was equally experienced in this.

"The variable actually appeared here…"

These thoughts flashed through the Ancestral Tree King's mind, and a strange expression appeared on his face. He seemed to heave a sigh of relief, but there was also a sneer on his face.

He had been at his wits' end for the past few months, and he had been worrying about the war with the three Universal Civilizations. He did not expect someone to send him a pillow[2] just as he was about to doze off. The most important thing now was to confirm if the intelligence was real. As long as it was not fake intelligence that the three Universal Civilizations deliberately released, there would be a favorable turn in the battle.

"Decipher all the contents as soon as possible and sort them out. At the same time, try to deduce the origin of this wormhole."

The Ancestral Tree King did not hesitate and told the research department to quickly produce results.

Whether it was a traitor or a third party, no matter what their motive was, no matter if they wanted to make use of the World Tree… it did not matter to him. What was important was to eliminate the three Universal Civilizations and remove the biggest threat to the mother tree!

As for the other problems, once the threat was eliminated, the World Tree would once again be invincible. There would be plenty of time to slowly resolve them. The Ancestral Tree King had always been able to focus on the main conflict.

On the other side, Flickering World, Siebert Fortress, strategic command room.

"Reporting, there is an abnormal spatial reaction outside the border. It is suspected to be the formation of a wormhole." The military radar sent out a notification.

The military officers present moved closer and looked at the source. They realized that the abnormal signal was outside the border defense circle, not too far from the World Tree camp.

"Can we investigate and see what's going on over there?" a staff sergeant asked.

"Insufficient information. Recommended field inspection," the military artificial intelligence replied.

Hearing this, everyone looked at each other and muttered softly.

The border defense army was stationed at various posts in the defense circle. If they left this place, it would be difficult for them to deal with the World Tree fleet without the endless supply of defense mechanisms and fast support channels. Therefore, the border defense army had always focused on defense and would not take the initiative to attack.

The source of the anomaly was outside the defense circle. If they wanted to field investigate, they would have to move the fleet. Not only did they keep an eye on the World Tree, but the World Tree also kept an eye on the defense circle. Once the border defense army sent out a fleet, the World Tree would definitely send troops over to fight in the field and eat the fleet they sent out. Furthermore, from the distance, the World Tree was closer to the abnormal reaction source. Even if they sent troops over, they would most likely not gain anything.

Generally speaking, border troops rarely sent people to carry out such risky missions of unknown value.

However… the players were perfect for this job.

[1] A Starcraft 2 Macro Bot. The bot is so powerful that you just need to press F2 (select all armies) and A (attack) to win Back

[2] Timely help Back

Chapter 1422: Conspiracy

"Our mission this time is to investigate the abnormal signal area outside the border defense circle. There's a high chance that we will encounter a battle with the World Tree fleet. Everyone needs to be prepared to sacrifice themselves."

In the cabin, the light blue projection of the commander floated on the tactical command platform, explaining the details of the mission to the players in the room. If it was a normal person, he would not mention 'sacrifice', but it did not matter to the Immortals. All the people participating in this mission were players.

Most of the time, this kind of scouting mission was a mistake and would not yield any results. If there was no players' suicide squad, the command center might not even send people to investigate.

Most of the people were listening attentively, but Black Tea was distracted. He stayed behind the crowd and opened the forum to flirt with the female players.

As an old player who had been scammed in Version 1.0, Black Tea had seen everything and was now more interested in female players. These combat missions were more or less the same—charge, die, pay, and complete.

Anyway, no matter what the commander said, when the actual mission was carried out, they still had to adapt to the situation. Black Tea was already familiar with the process and had his own way of doing things. In his opinion, there was no need to listen to the details at all. It was better to spend this time flirting with a few girls.

Not long after, the hyperdrive lights covering the ships dissipated, and the reconnaissance team had already arrived at their destination. In the universe outside the window, there was a World Tree team that seemed to be searching for something in the area. The number of battleships was less than half of the reconnaissance team, and as soon as they saw the three Universal Civilizations' reconnaissance team, they immediately turned around, as if they were trying to escape together.

"World Tree fleet detected, attack!"

The commander did not hesitate and immediately gave the order. This reconnaissance team fired at the World Tree exploration team without hesitation. The intercepting ship accelerated and chased after them with a group of players. Very soon, they caught a few World Tree exploration ships that could not escape in time.

Bang! Bang! Bang! The intercepting ships shot out charge cabins one after another, biting the bodies of the enemy ships, penetrating the exterior armor, and embedding themselves in. The players inside boarded the ships noisily, planning to control the spaceships.

High-temperature flames spewed out, and lasers shot out in all directions. The group of players immediately started a massacre in the exploration ships, fighting with the members of the World Tree. It could be said that they were unstoppable. The World Tree warriors were either burnt to ashes, beaten into meat pies, or shot into sieves. The ground was filled with tattered corpses.

Black Tea tilted his body slightly and avoided a laser beam. He pointed his sword with a backhand stance, and a stream of white Pugilist energy shot out. It was sharp and cold, like a qi sword, and penetrated the chests of three World Tree warriors, instantly killing them.

"How is it, pretty cool huh?"

"Brother, you're so strong. Can you bring me to dungeons in the future?" The female player in the video acted cutely.

"It depends on your performance."

Black Tea had a smug smile on his face as he spoke in the private chat. Even on the battlefield, he was flirting with girls. He turned on the video call to let the girl see his heroic side.

In the past few months, he had already completed the level 180 Promotion Mission, successfully advanced, and entered the Calamity Grade. He was undoubtedly the leader among the current players. This kind of boarding battle was not a problem for him at all, and he could easily pick up girls while fighting.

He chose the Pugilist class naturally because it was the most flashy of the five classes. Whether he was strong or not was a matter of one version, but whether he looked cool or not was a matter of life.

While Black Tea was chatting, his teammates were already ploughing through the World Tree soldiers and getting further away.

After watching the group of people leave happily, Black Tea did not follow them. He smiled and shook his head, showing the demeanor of a gentleman. He said, "You can't get too excited when you're doing missions. Look at these people. They're classic negative examples. They've finally gotten the chance to be unparalleled, and they're already so reckless. You have to use your brain when doing missions. Learn a little."

After putting on a show, Black Tea did not follow the rest of the team. Instead, he turned around and walked into the corridor alone. He casually broke the walls and floors of the cabin and went straight into the belly of the ship.

Very soon, he arrived at a gate without any obstructions. On the gate were the words 'Analysis Room' and 'Research Area' written in the language of the World Tree Civilization. Due to the invasion of the spaceship, all the guards had gone to protect the energy core, engine, control center, bridge, and other key areas. There was no one there, only some simple defense facilities that were dismantled by Black Tea.

"Brother, what are you doing here alone?" The female player blinked and asked in confusion.

"Hehe, I told you to use your brain. Think about it. Our mission is to investigate the abnormal situation in this area, and the World Tree fleet is one step ahead of us, but they're still here, seemingly looking for something. This proves that they've already discovered something. The World Tree exploration ship has a simple analysis lab, so there might be clues here. This is the main goal of our mission. If we can snatch the World Tree's exploration results, we won't have to risk staying here to investigate. We might even be able to complete this without dying."

After taking care of all the defense facilities, Black Tea walked into the room and spoke.

"Wow, you're so experienced!" The female player was full of admiration.

"It's alright, mainly because I've seen too much."

Black Tea was secretly overjoyed.

Although he was indeed experienced, his words were just to show off. He wanted to show off his wisdom and that he was different from those pigs. As for whether he would gain anything here, it did not matter.

However, at this moment, Black Tea suddenly stopped in his tracks and looked up at one of the transparent experiment chambers. There was a ball of light floating inside. When he looked over, the interface suddenly jumped, and a notification popped up.

You have triggered the hidden mission [Source of Change].

Mission Introduction: You have discovered an important clue that can change the war. It has an immeasurable value. If you bring it back, it will greatly affect the direction of the war.

Mission Requirements: Use a container to store this clue and bring it back to the three Universal Civilizations to report.

Reward: Depends on the rating.

Black Tea was stunned.

No way, I was just bragging. It was really true ‽

"See, I told you, there must be some clues here!"

Black Tea immediately became excited and shared the mission interface with the girl. Then, he immediately went to the experiment chamber, searched for a while, found the storage button, and pressed it.

Tiny electric arcs flashed in the experiment chamber, guiding the light into a palm-sized tube container. The two ends of the container automatically turned and closed, and intricate mechanical parts with strong magnetic force joined tightly.

Then, this tube slid along the transparent pipe, and half of it popped out from one of the holes in the operating table, meaning that it could be taken away.

With a click, Black Tea opened the chest area of his mechanical suit and stuffed this round tube container into a storage groove. Then, he closed the armor and protected it. Without another word, he went back the way he came and reported the situation.

This battle did not last long. The reconnaissance team had defeated the World Tree exploration team, and the other party could only escape with their remaining troops. As this place was closer to the World Tree camp, the reconnaissance team did not want to chase after them.

Originally, they did not care about sacrificing themselves and planned to stay here for a while to investigate the abnormal situation. However, after obtaining the intelligence from Black Tea, the team changed their plan and directly retreated to avoid being chased by the World Tree's follow-up troops.

As soon as the reconnaissance team left, the reinforcements from the World Tree arrived. They gave chase symbolically and gave up when they approached the border defense circle. They watched as the reconnaissance team—that had obtained the encrypted particles—returned to the three Universal Civilizations.

Not long after, at the research center of the frontline base, the container brought back by Black Tea was transported. Under the research of a group of scientists, it gradually revealed its true appearance.

"This… this is…"

The research team leader looked at the deciphered content and widened his eyes in shock. He took a few steps back in disbelief.

"Team leader, what did you find?" The officer who was waiting for the results felt his heart skip a beat and hurried forward.

The research team leader came back to his senses and pounced in front of him. He grabbed the officer's shoulder and said anxiously,

"Bad news! Quickly inform the three leaders and His Excellency Black Star! Our territorial star maps have been leaked!"

As soon as he said that, the expressions of all the officers and researchers changed.

...

On the other side, in the Tree King's palace.

"Your Excellency Tree King, according to your orders, we have already handed a portion of the encrypted particles to the enemy. They will firmly believe that this information was intercepted by them."

"Well done."

The Ancestral Tree King narrowed his eyes and nodded.

At such a close distance, the frontline troops had long discovered the uniqueness of the encrypted particles, so how could such negligence appear? All of this was naturally intentional. It was only when the three Universal Civilizations' reconnaissance troops repelled the World Tree exploration team that their reinforcements arrived and acted as though they could not catch up, but it was all fake.

Their true goal was to allow the three Universal Civilizations to obtain a set of encrypted particles in a less suspicious way.

"This is not a bad move. When they see the leaked information, they will most likely suspect that there is a spy. Things will become chaotic." Fortitude Tree King nodded.

"A powerful fortress can be broken through from the inside. Suspicion is the best weapon," the Ancestral Tree King said calmly.

No matter who leaked this information to him, in his opinion, it was most likely that they did not want to be discovered by the three Universal Civilizations.

The Ancestral Tree King did not mind being used, but he would not make the manipulator too happy. Since they wanted to use him, they had to bear the corresponding risk.

On the other hand, even if the manipulator did not care, the Ancestral Tree King wanted to use this method to make the three Universal Civilizations suspicious and even split up.

"That's right. After all, not all civilizations can be as united as us. Everyone is connected to the mental network, and the mother tree will be in charge. There are no secrets," the Fortitude Tree King agreed with a smile.

The Ancestral Tree King narrowed his eyes and glanced at him. He did not know if this was sincere or if there was a deeper meaning behind his words.

...

In the head office of the three Universal Civilizations, Marbruce, Louis, and the Pope received an urgent report on the coding particle at the frontline and immediately held a meeting.

Looking at the countless pieces of intel that had been deciphered, the three of them were furious.

"How bold, someone actually colluded with the enemy!"

The Pope slammed the table angrily.

"No matter who it is, we have to find them!"

Anger burned in Marbruce's eyes.

Originally, the situation was very good. Relying on the border defense circle and Han Xiao, it was enough to resist the World Tree for many years. However, not long after they had gained the advantage, a traitor appeared in their family and leaked countless intelligence!

With these coordinates, the World Tree would be able to jump through space, avoid the border defense circle, and directly invade. Countless battlefronts would be opened, and the stalemate would be broken.

They had worked hard for so many years just to ensure that their territory would not be violated. Now, all their hard work had been wasted. The three of them were already beyond furious. They wanted nothing more than to tear the traitor to pieces!

At this time, Han Xiao received the invitation and appeared in the room. He frowned and went straight to the point.

"You said that the intelligence of the galactic society was leaked? What's the exact situation?"

"See for yourself."

Marbruce separated a section of the virtual screen and sent it to Han Xiao.

Han Xiao quickly understood the situation.

His first reaction was that the World Tree was trying to sow discord, using some kind of method to obtain information and then arousing suspicion within them… However, this information was so detailed that it was impossible to gather unless one had been in the explored universe for a long time. Therefore, it was more believable that someone leaked the information.

"It's either a traitor colluding with the enemy or a third party taking advantage of the situation," Han Xiao said.

"We think so too," Marbruce said grimly. "But in comparison, the possibility of a traitor is higher!"

Han Xiao stroked his chin and said, "If it's a traitor, their goal definitely isn't survival. Based on the current situation, the entire galactic society believes that we can resist the World Tree, so the traitor has other goals, such as taking revenge on you or taking advantage of the situation…"

"We know that."

Louis' eyes flickered with a cold light. Before this, they had already discussed the suspects. Among them, the most suspicious ones were the Super Star Cluster Alliance and the lower level Star Cluster Civilizations. Even the Beyond Grade A Association was somewhat suspicious, so the three of them were wary of Han Xiao.

Although the current favorable situation was the work of Black Star, the position that the three of them were in made them suspect Han Xiao. Even though Black Star had made so many contributions, there was still a motive…

This time, Han Xiao's eyes suddenly flashed.

"The World Tree might have leaked this information on purpose to cause internal strife…"

However, halfway through, Han Xiao stopped and shook his head helplessly.

Even if the World Tree did it on purpose, the information leak was real. Even if they guessed that this was the World Tree's plan, they could not let go of their suspicions. This was an open conspiracy.

If the information was leaked by a third party, it might have been calculated in advance. Not only did they help the World Tree, but they also used the World Tree to raise suspicion in the galactic society.

Han Xiao paused for a moment, put away these speculations, changed the topic, and said, "No matter what, the battle situation has changed. Make preparations as soon as possible to deal with the World Tree's full invasion. This is the most important task."

The three of them nodded.

Although the three Universal Civilizations were prepared for war in the various Star Fields, compared to the border of the Flickering World, the defense of the other areas was naturally much weaker. There were still countless planets scattered around, allowing the enemy to enter their familiar battle rhythm of 'sustaining war with war'.

"We have to find the traitor. Since they've done such a thing, they will definitely do something that benefits them at some point. Sooner or later, they will be exposed," the Pope said coldly.

"The earlier we confirm the target, the better. I will immediately order a specialized team to investigate this matter," Louis said.

Han Xiao thought about it and said, "I need to study these encrypted particles personally. Maybe I can find some clues."

Hearing this, the three of them exchanged looks and finally nodded.

"We can give you a portion of the encrypted particles for research. I hope you find a clue soon."

"Sure."

Looking at the three of them, Han Xiao knew that he was one of their suspects. He could not help but shake his head. At this time, he did not care. If he was in their position, he would not have trusted anyone either.

'I didn't expect the name of the version to come true so quickly. Who is the one behind this… It can't be them, right?'

Han Xiao thought to himself. The stealthy Super Star Cluster Alliance flashed past his mind, and the figures of the Avengers appeared.

Chapter 1423: Third Party And Paying One's Debts

After learning about the situation from the three leaders, Han Xiao did not continue to participate in the 'Among Us' brainstorming of the three of them. He deactivated the remote projection and went to the frontline research facility.

As soon as he walked into the laboratory hall, he could smell anxiety and panic in the air. Countless researchers were moving back and forth, deciphering the encrypted particles.

"Your Excellency Black Star, Ruler Marbruce has given me a secret order. Please follow me."

An officer who had been waiting for a long time immediately came forward and led Han Xiao into the corridor.

Not long after, the two of them arrived at a private laboratory. There was an expert team doing decryption work, but it was different from simply decrypting the content of the encrypted particles outside. This place was also responsible for finding the technical characteristics of the encrypted particles. The moment the door opened, Han Xiao heard the endless argument inside.

"…The structural deviation of this particle is obviously too high, forming a typical three-direction ratio with Marvir's readings. It has the characteristics of the Karpoke warped technology and the Siber space conversion. It's definitely based on the third theoretical model of particle space!"

"It's just similar! You ignored the characteristics of dimension change folds and the weakening of the nuclear force. This is a technology that the three Universal Civilizations have already eliminated!"

Han Xiao turned around and saw the group of experts gathered in front of the experiment table and arguing while pointing at the readings on the apparatus.

The same theory could extend to all kinds of applications and achieve the same goal through different means. However, although some techniques were similar in their performance and final results, there were many differences in the actual usage process. If one tried to understand it in a less correct but simpler way, it would be equivalent to the same character having different ways of writing, so there was naturally more than one way to modify the particles…

By studying the characteristics of these technologies, he could reverse engineer the specific technology used by the encrypted particles. This was also the focus of the research. They were trying to reduce the scope of suspicion by using the encrypted particles' technology.

Han Xiao did not conceal his footsteps and walked over in large strides. Only then did the experts realize that there was an outsider. Seeing that it was Han Xiao, they all bowed respectfully.

He looked up at the encrypted particles floating on the experiment table and waved his hand.

"Alright, stop arguing. Let me see what's going on."

"Please let us know if you need anything."

The group of experts had no objections and retreated to the side, obediently giving up the experiment table behind them.

Black Star was not only the strongest individual strength in the Galaxy that was on the same level as the three leaders, he was also one of the best scientists. These researchers had always admired Black Star, and a small portion of the people present were his worshippers. These normally esteemed high-level researchers were all willing to be his assistants.

Han Xiao looked at the readings and studied the encrypted particles from head to toe. He quickly analyzed the data in his mind and locked onto a few technologies.

As far as he knew, these technologies seemed to be used by members of the Super Star Cluster Alliance. Of course, he could not rule out the possibility of other organizations imitating them.

'According to normal judgment, the Super Star Cluster Alliance is now even more suspicious, but it could also be a deliberate framing… In this case, it's more like a traitor in the galactic society.'

With a thought, Han Xiao released his Mechanical Force and connected it to the encrypted particles. He then activated [Bold Explorer].

Buzz!

Han Xiao's vision suddenly changed, and he arrived at a research institute with different styles. Many researchers were working.

A huge device was spinning. Particles were opened in low dimensional space and recorded into information. Then, they were restored and turned into encrypted particles that were injected into three white cylindrical containers.

He could not control his vision and followed the three white tubes closely. The white tubes were placed into a suitcase and sent into a groove of a material transmission device.

The next moment, his vision turned once again, and he had already arrived at a secret underground base. He saw another material transmission device, and with a flash of light, the white suitcase was sent over. A few life forms walked up and opened it, revealing the white tubes inside.

This time, his vision changed again, and he came to a space in the universe. A blue and black wormhole opened up in front of him, and three white tubes were thrown in. They passed through the colorful space tunnel and flew out from the other end of the wormhole. Then, the three white tubes suddenly burst out with heat, releasing a wave of energy, and all the encrypted particles inside were thrown out.

In the last scene, a World Tree exploration team shrouded in green light appeared in the distance.

The illusion stopped, and Han Xiao's vision returned to normal.

"It seems like these encrypted particles appeared from nowhere till they were intercepted by the World Tree…"

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

Although the illusion provided by [Bold Explorer] did not involve a specific location, Han Xiao was almost certain that this was a third party's doing. There was no other reason other than the researchers in the illusion were all unfamiliar species that he had never seen before. Among the people who received the white suitcase, there was a race that should have disappeared long ago.

"The Lorese people, the intelligent species of the Lore Civilization… The Lore Civilization, the loser of the exploration era, was destroyed by the three Universal Civilizations. It should have been exterminated…"

Han Xiao took out the information and started to think.

From the looks of it, the Lore Civilization had survived, and their goal should be revenge. They were not fighting alone and had even found helpers. Those intelligent species had never appeared in the history of the three Universal Civilizations, so they should be foreign civilizations.

According to the detailed information within the encrypted particles, this foreign civilization should have been lying in wait in the explored universe for many years without being discovered.

'Tsk, another old enemy of the exploration era. The three Universal Civilizations are constantly paying their debts for their past deeds…'

Han Xiao subconsciously rubbed his fingers.

In the World Tree War in his previous life, this foreign civilization did not appear and did not seem to have interfered with the direction of the war. Now, however, they took the initiative to backstab the three Universal Civilizations. Maybe it was because this foreign civilization's situation was different in different timelines, or maybe it was because the situation in his previous life did not require them to interfere… Of course, Han Xiao was not sure if this foreign civilization took action in his previous life. The players did not have the relevant information.

"Seeing that the three Universal Civilizations have the upper hand, they want to destroy our strategy, shatter our advantage, and help the World Tree invade us… They want to take revenge on us, but they also want to take advantage of the situation. They want to hide in the dark and watch the tigers fight each other while they snipe for profits. Tsk, quite malicious."

Han Xiao guessed the motive of the foreign civilization while thinking of a solution.

Although he had confirmed that it was a third party, he did not know their location, so he could not follow the clues. If he searched with great fanfare, it was very likely that the foreign civilizations would withdraw all their spies and cut off all clues.

Furthermore, without evidence, it would not be easy to convince the three big hooligans. Although with his position, even without evidence, the three Universal Civilizations' leaders would still take his words seriously, now that even he was suspected, the credibility would naturally be reduced. The three big leaders would at most be skeptical.

[Information Form Obliteration] could see the connection threads, but this was a destructive ability. It could not see the specific situation and could not trace the source. Even if this batch of encrypted particles was wiped out, the World Tree's side most likely had others, and the situation could not be resolved. After all, this ability wiped out 'individuals', not 'concepts' and 'collective body'. It would not be that if it killed one or two humans, the others would forget about the entire human race.

In fact, the effect of [Information Form Obliteration] was very 'precise', and it would not have much effect on the Information Form of anything else other than the target's. Therefore, the effect of this move would be quite peculiar when it targeted the split parts of a whole body.

If he used [Information Form Obliteration] on this part of the encrypted particles, Han Xiao estimated that the three leaders would remember that he had taken some things to study, but they would forget that he was studying the encrypted particles. Furthermore, the experts present would not remember what they were studying, and these machine readings would also be erased.

If he 'erased' the other encrypted particles that the three Universal Civilizations had intercepted, Han Xiao felt that the result would probably be that the three Universal Civilizations had forgotten about the existence of the encrypted particles, but remembered that 'something' had exposed the presence of a spy leaking information. As for the World Tree, they would remember that they had given 'something' to the three Universal Civilizations, but they would forget that they had handed over the encrypted particles. However, they would not forget about the encrypted particles in their hands.

Han Xiao had made a hypothesis before. If he used [Information Form Obliteration] to deal with the entire World Tree Civilization, the reaction of the three Universal Civilizations would most likely not be 'what have we been doing all these years', but 'we defeated a Universal Civilization with difficulty, but we can't remember what that civilization is called'.

Therefore, [Information Form Obliteration] had a very good effect on individuals with different Information Form, such as living beings. However, when dealing with individuals with a large collective body (such as a grain of sand in a desert, a gun in a batch of standard firearms), the Information Form gap could be deduced by logic… For example, if the experts forgot what they were researching previously, but came to the experiment hall and saw others studying the encrypted particles, they could also deduce that they were probably researching this before.

However, even if you used logic to deduce that, [Information Form Obliteration] was still in effect, you would subtly have memory deviations, quickly forget, subconsciously ignore, common sense errors, and so on. It was just like when you thought of something, you would suddenly forget it and would not be able to recall it no matter what. This kind of situation was not uncommon. It was also like when you believed that the temperature of a normal person's bath was eighty degrees instead of forty degrees, there would be a common-sense deviation that you would not be able to detect, or it would be like the legendary war of '99…

'In any case, I have to find a way to capture this group of lurkers. Currently, I can only use conventional methods to collect intelligence in secret. It's best to monitor the artificial intelligence in the quantum network… They will most likely continue to observe the follow-up effects of this 'borrowing knife to kill others' tactic. Seeing that the three Universal Civilizations are suffering, they probably did not retreat.

Sigh, it would be great if we could retrieve the World Tree's Information Form Warning Network. This thing is simply a black technology to prevent the territory from being infiltrated.'

Han Xiao shook his head helplessly.

Compared to the World Tree, the territories of the three Universal Civilizations were like a sieve. Other people could enter and exit as they wished, even leaving something behind. The three Universal Civilizations would not be able to discover it in a short period. It was simply the standard model of a victim.

He stroked his chin and pondered.

The World Tree and the third party's goal was to cause internal strife in the galactic society, so the most important thing now was to not let the enemy's plan succeed. Since the infiltrators could not be found in a short time and the three Universal Civilizations' suspicions could not be dispelled, it seemed like they could only start with the suspects.

"It seems like the three Universal Civilizations are most suspicious of the Super Star Cluster Alliance, and they happen to be cooking other plans in secret. However, I have yet to find out what's going on… If this causes a misunderstanding between the two sides, I'm afraid both sides will suffer heavily."

Han Xiao was helpless.

In the past, he had always cheated the Super Star Cluster Alliance, and it was not the first time they had suffered for no reason. However, it was the opposite now. He had to think of a way to reduce their suspicion so that they would not become scapegoats…

Indeed, one had to pay for everything they have done!

Chapter 1424: The Face of the Pugilist

In the next few days, the World Tree Army laid low and did not launch any attacks on the Flickering World border or the shallow layer dimensions. They did not exert any pressure, and the flames of war were briefly extinguished. However, the strategic command center of the three Universal Civilizations did not relax at all. The atmosphere was as though they were still fighting intensely, and they knew that this was only the calm before the storm.

The armies that were originally stationed in the various Star Fields for emergencies were put to use. They all entered war mode and patrolled the areas they were in charge of.

The encrypted particles had leaked the star maps of the entire explored universe, including countless spatial coordinates. There were too many routes that the enemy could choose, and they could invade from anywhere.

Han Xiao sent most of the Mechanical Oracles to the main universe to increase the number of high-level combatants. Originally, the three Universal Civilizations had the upper hand in terms of individual strength, but if the World Tree invaded all the territories, the effect of the high-level combatants would be completely different from a frontal battle. The high flexibility would bring about a powerful destructive force, and the battlefront would be split into countless sections. As the defending party that had no choice but to surround and intercept the enemy, their Beyond Grade As would not be enough.

In addition to dealing with the changes in the situation, Han Xiao had also been secretly searching for the spies of the foreign civilizations in the past few days. It was a pity that he was searching for a needle in a haystack and did not find anything. However, he did have some results from his investigation of the Super Star Cluster Alliance.

"So, they want to take advantage of the intense battle and escape from the control of the three Universal Civilizations when they have no time to deal with other matters. They want to head to the unexplored universe and find a place to develop freely…"

Han Xiao looked at the information on the virtual screen with a strange expression.

How badly had they been bullied by the three Universal Civilizations that they wanted to leave their home?

He could roughly understand the thoughts of the Super Star Cluster Alliance. Staying in the explored universe would only result in endless suppression, and they would forever be constrained by the three Universal Civilizations. No matter how much they developed, they would never be able to exceed these three ceilings.

During the reshuffling of the structure due to the enemy invasion, the Super Star Cluster Alliance considered their future and made a decision. For their civilization to develop freely, they decided to take the risk and explore the unknown. This was understandable. After all, they were never on the same side as the three Universal Civilizations.

"This is bad. The World Tree's invasion is their chance to escape. If they really do that, it would be the same as admitting the suspicion. This was akin to having mud on the back of one's pants. Even if it was not sh*t, people would naturally assume it to be."

Han Xiao massaged his brows.

He had already told the three leaders about the result of the third party causing trouble and even pointed out the existence of the Lore Civilization. However, as expected, the three of them did not say that they did not believe it, but only accepted that this was one of the reasons. Unless there was conclusive evidence, they still had to find traitors.

Only when the battle becomes chaotic would the three Universal Civilizations not be able to spare energy in this, and the Super Star Cluster Alliance would be able to carry out their plan. However, it just so happened that someone leaked the information at this time. Such a coincidence? To be honest, if Han Xiao did not know the truth, and looked from the perspective of the three Universal Civilizations, even he would have thought that the Super Star Cluster Alliance was resolute and fierce, and it was definitely because they wanted to escape that they lured the World Tree to invade all territories.

In his previous life, the Super Star Cluster Alliance did not do this but stood on the galactic society's side and fought against the enemies together. This time, they made a completely different choice. Maybe it was because the time period was different, the upper echelons were different, and the logic of their decisions was different. Or maybe it was because their situation was slightly different from his previous life, most of it was because of the butterfly effect he brought. It was more likely that the Super Star Cluster Alliance had not seen the full power of the World Tree invasion like in his previous life and did not feel the true threat of this cosmic disaster, so they still felt that they could stay away from the flames of war and not die at the hands of the enemy…

In other words, they had not been beaten by the World Tree.

"I have to convince the Super Star Cluster to cancel the escape plan. Otherwise, the internal division will be right in front of us. However, no matter how great my reputation is, the Super Star Cluster will not be convinced by my words."

Han Xiao pondered.

On one hand, he did not want the Super Star Cluster to take the blame and allow the third party to go unpunished. On the other hand, the galactic society needed the Super Star Cluster's strength to resist the World Tree's invasion. As long as they were determined to fight, their combined strength could not be underestimated. They were also an important part of the combat power of the explored universe.

"I have to think of a way…"

While he was pondering, an urgent internal message from the three Universal Civilizations popped up on the virtual screen.

"Primeval Star River, Ancient Star Desert, Sea of Star Spirits, Blackhole Edge, Endless Nebula, Shattered Star Ring, and other Star Fields have all discovered traces of the World Tree fleet! Requesting reinforcements! Requesting reinforcements!"

Han Xiao sat up straight, and a cold light flashed in his eyes.

They're here!

...

In the Ancient Star Desert, blue wormholes formed one after another, forming a huge oval-shaped space crack. It was like God had cut open the curtain of the universe, leaving behind a blue scar.

Immediately after, a green light appeared in the enormous space crack. It grew brighter and larger, and finally turned into an overwhelming green tide pouring out!

The seemingly endless fleet of the World Tree crossed the border of the Flickering World and descended directly along the wormhole. The dense streams of hyperdrive light condensed into pillars of light and shot in all directions like a plague virus in the enemy's body, spreading in the blink of an eye.

Countless World Tree warriors revealed fanaticism on their faces as if they were holding a banquet. After being in a stalemate for so many years, they had finally made their way in and dismembered their prey!

On the planets that the World Tree fleet passed by, there was a violent fluctuation in the space. The thick roots of the World Tree tore open space cracks like drilling through soil and extending out from the void into the planets like straws, drawing out dazzling energy visible to the naked eye.

The planet's crust softened and flowed into the roots of the World Tree like a liquid. The material of the planet's mantle and core was also swallowed in large mouthfuls. The planet slowly shriveled up and was rapidly approaching its end.

Wherever the green tide passed, the stars slowly extinguished, and the planets gradually dissolved, leaving only death and desolation.

This reminded the World Tree warriors of the past. They roamed the endless universe, unrestrainedly tasting the delicious taste of the enemy's territory. They cut off pieces of meat from their still struggling prey and ate everything. After all, they were the best hunters in the universe, or even the only predator!

The same thing happened in many Star Fields at the same time.

In a hurry, the Galactic Alliance Army launched a counterattack with the local Star Systems and Star Cluster Civilizations. The flames of war spread across the explored universe.

The battlefront was divided into countless areas, and the World Tree experts finally had a place to use their strength. They were scattered all over the place, fully displaying the flexibility of high-level combatants. The Beyond Grade As of the three Universal Civilizations could no longer stay together, so they could only leave Aurora and go to different areas.

The sudden change scared countless galactic residents, and the situation turned around instantly. The panic that was suppressed in their hearts was released, and it erupted like a volcano, burning away their remaining rationality.

The Ancestral Tree King looked into the distance. His vision seemed to have passed through the barriers of endless space and it locked onto the direction of the Central Galaxy.

"Eat. Eat everything. Give us a feast, and we will give you despair."

...

In a certain army base in the Shattered Star Ring, the Black Star Army's guards were engaged in a fierce battle with the World Tree fleet. On the battlefield, there was a black tide formed by the mechanical soldiers, tearing apart the World Tree battleships one after another.

On a planet not far away, hundreds of World Tree Roots had already been inserted into the planet's core, absorbing energy. In outer space, three Holy Tree Emissaries were chasing after two figures, and five streams of light collided time and time again.

Clang!

Lothaire held a dagger in each hand, and his slash was as fast as lightning. His body was agile, and he moved back and forth between the three Holy Tree Emissaries. They fought intensely, and the silver dagger clashed with the laser and magic.

It looked like he was unstoppable, but in reality, his entire body was covered in wounds. In the intense battle, he had to divert his attention to take care of Karlot, who was slightly weaker. It was unavoidable for him to show flaws.

Lothaire crossed his daggers and slashed out a bright light blade, forcing back the Mechanical Pugilist Holy Tree Emissary. A flash of light appeared in the corner of his eyes, and he dodged without hesitation. In an instant, a gorgeous high-level Arcane Light penetrated his waist, leaving a burning mark.

"Protected your vital point? Your reactions are quite fast."

The Mage Holy Tree Emissary spoke with regret.

Among the three Holy Tree Emissaries, two of them had never appeared on the battlefield before. They were all experts from other races who had been restraining themselves.

It was not until they entered the territory of the three Universal Civilizations and split countless battlefronts that the World Tree activated the foreign experts to increase the size of their high-level combatants.

On one hand, they were agile enough to move alone. Even if Black Star had the method to awaken the foreign experts, he would not be able to catch them all in one swoop. On the other hand, the World Tree was already desperate. As long as they could speed up their invasion, they did not care about losing some of their manpower. They were already mentally prepared for a portion of their experts to be wiped out by Black Star's [Information Form Obliteration].

Lothaire's expression was tense. He pressed on the wound and used his energy to quickly heal it. The wound quickly formed a scab. He looked at his three opponents and felt a chill.

His style of martial arts focused on dexterity, stealth, and assassination. He was not strong in a head-on battle, and it was even more disadvantageous when he was surrounded. At this point, he could not take it anymore.

"Are you alright?" Karlot, who was on the side, also came over. He was also covered in wounds, and he was leaning back to back with Lothaire, and staring at his enemies.

It had only been a few years since he entered the Beyond Grade A realm, and he was still in the process of activating [Everlasting Martial Path]. His combat strength was still at the level of a new Beyond Grade A, and it was extremely difficult for him to fight. He might not even be able to defeat any of the enemies in a one-on-one battle.

The two of them were originally training here, but the World Tree suddenly attacked and dragged them into the flames of war.

"I can still hold on for a while."

Lothaire adjusted his breath, and the Pugilist flames climbed up his daggers again.

The five of them locked onto each other. Their bodies paused for a moment before suddenly bursting out at the same time. They charged forward and clashed again. Blade light, flames, and magic power shot out. The five streams of light were like five silk threads tangled together.

All of a sudden, Lothaire's body paused, and he slashed out with his two daggers, shattering the Arcane Charge of the Mage Holy Tree Emissary. However, amidst the shattered light, the Mechanical Pugilist suddenly appeared, and he was thrown toward Lothaire by a hand formed from magic. Eight spider legs-like mechanical spears suddenly extended from the back of his mechanical suit, and the spears pierced through the protective flames and into Lothaire's body.

Crack!

The silver daggers flashed, and the eight mechanical limbs were all cut off.

Lothaire retreated rapidly, controlling his muscles to squeeze out the broken spear tips in his body, leaving eight shallow wounds. These were nothing more than superficial wounds to him.

However, just as he was about to continue attacking, his body suddenly stiffened. A dark green color suddenly appeared on his wound, and the flesh that was originally recovering suddenly began to fester.

"Biological toxin ‽"

Lothaire's expression changed. He looked up and saw that the broken spear tips were leaking green liquid. He looked at it with his microscopic vision and realized that the green liquid was a group of dark green tiny molecular robots that carried powerful toxins.

Waves of intense pain exploded like a tsunami, and Lothaire's senses were suddenly messed up. It was as though he had lost control of his body, and he began to tremble uncontrollably. The cells in his body were being eroded.

With a flash, the last Pugilist Holy Tree Emissary took the opportunity to join the battle. He held a sharp blade made of anti-regeneration alloy and stabbed Lothaire's neck from behind, wanting to remove his entire spine.

Right at this moment, Karlot charged over from the side to stop this Pugilist Holy Tree Emissary. Unfortunately, he was a step too slow and could only throw a punch in an attempt to save him.

"A new Beyond Grade A wants to… hmm?!"

The Pugilist Holy Tree Emissary originally wanted to kill Lothaire even at the cost of getting injured. However, just as Karlot's fist approached, a strong sense of danger exploded in his heart!

The flames around Karlot's body flowed like water, condensing at the tip of his fist. His strength was contained but not released, but the power of his fist rose steadily, like the Milky Way was turned upside down, the stars were shattered, and an intense sharpness burst out.

At this moment, a thunderous roar containing spiritual fluctuations exploded!

"Martial Deity Fist—Galaxy Severance!"

The fist suddenly landed on the Pugilist Holy Tree Emissary's hastily raised arm, and a bright light burst forth, stealing everyone's vision!

Time seemed to freeze for a moment before it started to flow again.

The other two Holy Tree Emissaries regained their vision and hurriedly looked over, only to see that Karlot had already retreated to the side with Lothaire in his arms. Meanwhile, the Pugilist Holy Tree Emissary remained in place, still in a parry position, but did not move.

However, the next moment, the body of the Pugilist Holy Tree Emissary cracked like porcelain and fell into pieces, eventually turning into dust and scattering in the galaxy.

Instant kill!

"What move is this ‽"

The two remaining Holy Tree Emissaries were shocked. They could not believe their eyes. One of their comrades was killed just like that.

It would be understandable if the other was a peak Beyond Grade A, but was this the power of a new Beyond Grade A ‽

Lothaire had a chance to catch his breath, and he suppressed the poison with difficulty. Seeing this, he could not help but widen his eyes. "You've already created that kind of fist technique?"

"Phew… Phew… No, I only created two stances. I'm still far from perfecting the Martial Deity Fist."

Karlot had expended a lot of energy. This punch contained all of his essence, energy, and spirit, and its power far exceeded his level. At this moment, his entire body was sore, and his stamina was almost depleted. He did not even have ten percent of his energy left.

When he stepped into the Beyond Grade A realm, Karlot had some special insights, and he had an idea. He wanted to create a Pugilist style suitable for himself and named it 'Martial Deity Fist'. He did not use this name because it was arrogant, but because it contained his expectations for himself, hoping to create the most amazing Beyond Grade A Fist Style.

All these years, Karlot had been exploring and integrating all the knowledge he had, and he had only figured out two scattered stances. The power was extremely exaggerated, but the consumption was equally frightening. Even with his Beyond Grade A Pugilist foundation, he could only execute three to four moves.

Lothaire looked at the enemy's corpse and said, "What a terrifying move. You've already surpassed me."

"Do you want to learn? I can teach you."

Karlot smiled shyly.

The two of them thought that this Martial Deity Fist was very powerful, but if Han Xiao was here, he would be able to tell that although the Martial Deity Fist was very magical, it would not be able to unleash such great power when used by others. The truly powerful one was Karlot himself.

This was because the process of creating the Martial Deity Fist was also the stage where Karlot was able to master everything he had learned. During this process, he could almost comprehend a new talent every few days, three of which were extremely powerful.

[Martial Saint's Strength]—When using any Pugilist skills, base power increased by 80% to 240%!

[Martial Deity Fist's Ancestor]—When you use the "Martial Deity Fist" series, your base strength will increase by 100% to 300%!

[One Punch Martial Deity]—Every time you use the skills of the "Martial Deity Fist" series to hit your opponent, you will be able to trigger a severe injury judgment / instant death judgment (the success rate depends on the power of the skill, the difference in level, energy level, attributes, and so on). If the judgment fails, an additional 50% to 150% damage will be dealt!

With so many Pugilist talents, although Karlot was only a new Beyond Grade A, his explosive power was unbelievably strong. As long as he was lucky, it was even possible for him to instantly kill the enemy.

Bang! Bang!

Karlot clenched his fists and looked at the two Holy Tree Emissaries. He said to Lothaire, "I still have some strength left. Continue, don't let them escape."

"Alright." Lothaire gripped his daggers tightly.

While many people were unaware, the face of the Pugilist was quietly forming.

Chapter 1425: Attack and Plan

Somewhere in the Sea of Star Spirits, a refugee planet had already been tightly bound by the roots of the World Tree. The soil, minerals, and forests all turned into streams of data, flowing into it. In the distance, the emergency refuge ship carrying the people of this planet was fleeing through the galaxy.

A World Tree fleet was chasing after them, and the escort fleet of the Galactic Alliance Army was covering them as they escaped.

The two sides fought intensely, leaving traces of energy explosions everywhere they passed. The light reflected in the eyes of the fleeing citizens.

Ten figures with metallic luster dashed around in the escort fleet, firing psionic cannons and destroying spaceships one after another. They were the Machinery Apostles, and their master was in the main ship of the World Tree fleet. It was a Lord's Avatar controlling the mechanical army from afar.

However, there was not a single Beyond Grade A in the escaping fleet. Thus, they could only use the battleship to block the advance of the mechanical apostles.

"The enemy has a Beyond Grade A Mechanic, and we urgently need high-level combatants to help!"

The commander of the escort fleet looked at the one-sided situation and had no choice but to order the fleet to retreat while asking for help in the military channel.

The World Tree ignored their losses to send out a large number of Beyond Grade As, and their total number of high-level combatants exceeded that of the three Universal Civilizations in an instant. The entire force was mobilized, causing the three Universal Civilizations to not have sufficient Beyond Grade As, and they were unable to stop any World Tree Super.

The fleet that was escorting the evacuation of the civilians did not have any high-level combatants. When they met the World Tree fleet that had a Beyond Grade A Mechanic commander, they were immediately beaten black and blue.

"Please continue to hold on for a while longer. We are sending out the available Beyond Grade As." The military intelligence's response immediately sounded in the channel.

The commander gritted his teeth and shouted loudly, ordering the fleet to continue attacking. However, the scale of their army was unable to change from quantitative to qualitative. The ten mechanical apostles led the army and devoured the starships like locusts.

Just as the number of casualties rose to a shocking number, a space on the battlefield opened up like a wave of ripples on water. Then, with a flash of light, a figure rushed out like a burning meteor and slammed into the nearest Mechanical Apostle, sending it flying.

"Reinforcements are here!"

The commander immediately looked at the Beyond Grade As who had come to reinforce them.

Upon seeing this person's appearance, the joy on the commander's face froze.

"Why is it you?!"

"Why do you sound so disappointed? I'm the only one who's free now. If you don't want to, I'm leaving!"

Kohler was furious.

What's wrong with you, little brother? I came to support you, and you're still looking down on me?!

"…I'll leave the enemy's Mechanic Super to you. My troops will support you from the side." The commander smiled bitterly and could only express his cooperation.

Kohler snorted and charged at the ten mechanical apostles.

The soldiers looked over with hope. However, within a few minutes, the imposing Kohler was crushed by the combined attacks of ten mechanical apostles.

"..."

The commander covered his face.

The internal rumors were not false. Kohler was indeed the weakest among the Beyond Grade As.

"I don't want to despise you either, but you're too much. I gave you a chance, but you can't even take care of the apostles, let alone a real battle. I don't even like to use you when playing Wayne Cards…"

Kohler dodged a few psionic beams and managed to return a punch. He sent a mechanical apostle flying and shouted in the channel, "What are you waiting for? I've helped you stall the enemy. Continue asking for help!"

Your tactical role is only to stall…

The commander cursed silently.

Just as he was about to resume his call for reinforcements, a wormhole suddenly opened not far away.

A Mechanical Lifeform flew out from within. Heavy mechanical armor covered its body, and every part of its body was equipped with high-tech melee weapons. It was armed to the teeth, and there were two wing-shaped vector thrusters erected on its back like two chess pieces. It was one of the Black Star Mechanical Oracles who had received orders to reinforce the various battlefronts in the universe, Heaven-Suppressing Banner.

"Black Star's elite troops are here!" Kohler was overjoyed and quickly waved. "Allies! Switch!"

Electric arcs flashed across the Heaven-Suppressing Banner's eyes, and his thrusters shot out streams of light. He instantly accelerated and rushed into the battle.

The ten Mechanical Apostles detected a strong energy reaction. Immediately, eight of them set off to meet the Heaven-Suppressing Banner, leaving only two to hold Kohler back.

A dense psionic cannon beam shot out, and the arm of the Heaven-Suppressing Banner turned into a heavy shield. It suddenly pushed forward, and a bright complicated energy circuit appeared on the shield. A thick psionic shield popped out, blocking the concentrated fire.

Amidst the bombardment, the distance between the two sides rapidly shortened. A mechanical apostle popped out a few wrist blades and headed straight for the energy core of the Heaven-Suppressing Banner. However, the Heaven-Suppressing Banner only turned around lightly and avoided the attack. The moment it passed by, he swiped at his waist, and a mechanical axe immediately unfolded, slashing out like a thunderbolt. The blade light instantly flashed past the mechanical apostle's body.

The next moment, the two halves of the Mechanical Apostle flew out due to inertia. The cut was smooth, and countless precise parts could be seen. The energy core that had been accurately cut in the center jumped slightly, and then exploded!

A huge explosion lit up behind the Heaven-Suppressing Banner, reflecting on its cold alloy shell.

The Heaven-Suppressing Banner was the master of close combat weapons among the Mechanical Oracles. All kinds of weapons appeared like magic, constantly changing and dealing with the Mechanical Apostles with ease. Not long after, it killed more than half of the Mechanical Apostles like cutting vegetables. It was completely different from the scene Kohler showed.

Suddenly, the Heaven-Suppressing Banner stomped on the ground, and an energy shockwave exploded behind him. He turned into a shooting star and rushed toward the World Tree fleet.

The axe slashed out beams of light, cutting the World Tree spaceship in half. In just a few blinks of the eye, the Heaven-Suppressing Banner had already arrived in front of the main ship, and the huge axe surrounded by golden lightning hacked down.

A thick bolt of golden lightning shot out from the axe, instantly shattering the shield of the main ship and melting through the armor. The entire ship exploded, and dazzling light spread out!

Two figures, one chasing and one escaping, rushed out of the explosion. The Lord's Avatar of the Mechanic Army Head was running in front, and the Heaven-Suppressing Banner was chasing after it.

After exchanging a few blows, the Heaven-Suppressing Banner cleaved the enemy's head in half with a swing of the axe. Electric arcs exploded, and the power contained in the body disappeared instantly. The Lord's Descent had already been destroyed by him, and he looked like he had taken the head of an enemy general.

With the current strength of the Mechanical Oracle, ordinary Beyond Grade As were no match for it at all. Their strength was on a completely different level from the Mechanical Apostle stage, and it would not be a problem for them to hold their own in battles against Beyond Grade As.

The high-level combatants of the enemy were eliminated, and the escort fleet immediately stopped their retreat.

The Heaven-Suppressing Banner did not continue to help. It reached out to remove the head of the enemy's Lord's Avatar, before hanging it on its waist as a trophy.

Just as he was about to open the wormhole and leave, Kohler flew over and gave him a thumbs up.

"Not bad. We've finally defeated this powerful opponent."

"When did we join forces? Were you fighting just now?"

The Heaven-Suppressing Banner tilted its head in confusion.

"I helped you restrain two mechanical apostles. Without me, you would have been in danger." Kohler patted his chest and said, "Black Star and I are good friends after all. Protecting his mechanical apostles is just a matter of convenience. You don't have to thank me."

While the Heaven-Suppressing Banner was still calculating the logic behind this sentence, Han Xiao's annoyed voice sounded in the channel.

"Shut up. You're really a noob."

"Oh, so you're here." Kohler laughed without any shame. "I was just joking."

"Hehe." Han Xiao curled his lips. "Heaven-Suppressing Banner, ignore him. Continue your mission."

The Heaven-Suppressing Banner tilted its head, before ignoring Kohler. It opened the wormhole and went to reinforce the other battlefronts according to Han Xiao's orders.

...

Primeval Star River, Mechanical Race territory.

The endless World Tree army was attacking the Mechanical Race's defense line, and the two fleets were already locked in battle.

On the main planet of the Mechanical Race, Manison and Nilfgadi's Lord's Avatar stood at the highest point and looked up at the sky.

The Mechanical Race troops behind him did not panic at all. Instead, they looked at the backs of the two generations of Mechanical Race leaders with fanaticism.

"The Mechanical Race is the first target of the World Tree. Do they think we're easy to deal with? We're not easy to bully." Nilfgadi stood with his arms crossed.

"You don't have the right to say that. All these years, the Mechanical Race was able to develop to its current state because of me. It has nothing to do with you," Manison said calmly.

Nilfgadi snorted but did not retort. He slowly said, "I didn't expect us to fight together under such circumstances."

"I know you don't like me, but don't worry, this battle won't take long."

Manison raised his hands slightly.

Boom!

All the planets in the Mechanical Race territory started buzzing, as though countless things were about to break out of the ground.

"After accumulating for so long, let the world see the strength of the Mechanical Race."

Manison's eyes flashed, and his tone was cold.

"Listen to my command, leave no one alive!"

Boom!

A seemingly endless mechanical army flew out from the planets one after another, covering the sky and earth as they welcomed the World Tree fleet.

...

"It's starting, it's starting…"

Many hidden Star Alliance observers looked at the chaos in the various Star Fields and could not help but smile.

"The World Tree invaded in one night. Clearly, our intelligence has come in handy. Very good! Very good!"

The Observer Captain clenched his fists with a ferocious expression on his face, gleeful at having gotten his revenge.

This time, the result of using someone else to do the dirty work was very obvious. It successfully turned the stalemate into a chaotic battle. This was what the Star Alliance wanted to see. It would be best if both sides were heavily injured.

"This way, even if the three Universal Civilizations can fight the World Tree Civilization, it would be difficult to stop their territories from being devoured step by step. If this continues, the three Universal Civilizations would be defeated sooner or later. It might just take decades, or maybe centuries," someone said excitedly.

The Observer Captain sneered.

"Heh, this is only the first wave. In my opinion, the three Universal Civilizations won't be able to last that long. According to the deductions of the upper echelons, it's very likely that the World Tree will use the information we leaked to fan the internal suspicions of the three Universal Civilizations and disintegrate their fighting spirit. From the start of the war until now, the morale and faith of the three Universal Civilizations have been supported by belief. When this momentum is gone, it will be their defeat."

As he spoke, a look of longing appeared in his eyes, as if he could see the future of the galactic society.

"The three Universal Civilizations have been high and mighty for too long. It's time for them to taste the feeling of their homeland and their nation being destroyed! Just like us back then!"

...

On the other side, the Super Star Cluster Alliance.

The sudden full-scale invasion of the World Tree gave the Super Star Cluster Alliance a shock.

Although the Super Star Cluster Alliance had received some news from the three Universal Civilizations over the past few days, they had only asked them to strengthen their internal defenses. They did not mention anything about the inside story, so the Super Star Cluster Alliance did not know anything about the situation of the information being leaked.

The various Star Fields were attacked, and the Super Star Cluster Civilizations were naturally targeted as well. However, compared to the intense battles in the other Star Fields, the size of the World Tree fleet that invaded the Super Star Cluster Civilization was very small, as though it was just a formality.

The Super Star Cluster Civilization thought that the World Tree did not want to bite them in the first wave of attacks, they were glad.

At this moment, an important meeting was being held in the conference room.

"…Everyone, the three Universal Civilizations have lost their border line of defense, and the World Tree has completely invaded. Let's put this aside for now. The current situation is developing in the direction we're looking forward to. A once in a lifetime opportunity has appeared in front of us, and we definitely can't miss it. I think we can consider officially starting the 'Great Relocation' plan."

The leader of the Star Arc Civilization said with a deep voice. Everyone was whispering and discussing, their faces filled with joy.

Everyone felt that it was very magical. They could only passively wait for the right time, hoping for the chaotic battle to break out, but they did not expect the opportunity to come so suddenly. It was like the Goddess of Luck was on their side.

"Seconded."

"I agree."

Everyone voted one after another. They had been waiting for this opportunity for too long, and there were very few objections.

Now that the World Tree had successfully invaded, it was tearing apart the flesh and blood of the explored universe every second. With the three Universal Civilizations having failed, they would only be devoured if they stayed here.

No one wanted to lose everything, so they decided to give up the territory that would fall sooner or later and leave as soon as possible to preserve their strength.

Seeing this, the leader of the Star Arc nodded, took a deep breath, and said, "It seems like everyone's opinion is rather unified. Then it's decided. Let the three Universal Civilizations and the World Tree drag it out for a while longer. After we officially enter a stalemate, we'll start the plan immediately!"

As he spoke, he paused before continuing solemnly.

"Everyone, once we take this path, there will be no turning back. For the future of our civilization, we can no longer live under someone else's roof."

Everyone nodded slowly.

The experience of being bullied by the three Universal Civilizations over the years flashed through their minds, making them more determined.

However, just as the leader was about to give a speech to strengthen his resolve, a communication request from Han Xiao suddenly popped up on the virtual screen.

"Black Star? He wants to see us at this time?"

The eyes of the upper echelons of the civilizations froze, and their nerves tightened.

As the saying went, they had a guilty conscience. Although their escape was a result of careful consideration, they were considered deserters in the war. Therefore, just seeing Han Xiao's name made them feel an invisible pressure.

The leader raised his hand and gestured for everyone to calm down.

"Connect me to Black Star and hear what he has to say."

Chapter 1426: Negotiation And Lobbyist

Han Xiao's remote projection landed in the conference room. He looked around and saw the expressions of all the Super Star Cluster Civilizations' leaders. He could not help but smile and joke.

"Everyone, what were you talking about? The atmosphere is so tense."

"We're talking about how to deal with the World Tree's invasion," the Star Arc Leader said.

"Is that so? But from what I know, the World Tree Civilization's army did not harass your territory much. Most of your troops are still on standby." Han Xiao shrugged.

"The entire galactic society is united against a common enemy. If the other regions are attacked, it also affects our safety. As long as our homeland is safe, we will naturally help," the Star Arc Leader said.

Han Xiao's expression changed. "It's really strange of you to say that."

"The World Tree has invaded. We are already in the same boat," The Star Arc Leader nodded and said with a solemn tone.

"If that's what you think, that would be best."

Han Xiao raised his brows. He knew that the words the Star Arc Leader was saying were mostly empty and not sincere.

A leader of the Super Star Cluster coughed and said,

"Your Excellency Black Star, are you looking for us to discuss the World Tree invasion?"

Han Xiao looked at him and nodded. "You can say that, but I am here mainly for you guys."

Everyone exchanged looks. The Star Arc Leader said, "I hope you can explain it clearly."

Han Xiao raised his arms and said casually,

"The World Tree invasion is already a fact. How much do you know about the cause of this?"

"We don't know the inside story. The World Tree was originally separated from the Flickering World by the three Universal Civilizations, and the situation was very stable. However, the enemy suddenly launched a full-scale invasion. They must have used some method to obtain our intelligence, but we don't understand how they did it." The Star Arc leader frowned and shook his head.

"I can tell you the inside story. This is not the World Tree taking an initiative. Someone deliberately leaked the information about the explored universe, daringly colluding with the enemy. This kind of action is like opening the border, inviting the World Tree in to burn, kill, and loot!" Han Xiao's tone was heavy.

As soon as he said that, the expressions of the Super Star Cluster upper echelons changed. Surprise, shock, disbelief, and other emotions appeared in their eyes.

The Star Arc leader's eyes were filled with shock. He emphasized, "You mean there's a traitor in the galactic society ‽"

"That's right." Han Xiao nodded slowly and said softly, "We're still investigating the identity of the traitor."

There was a slight commotion in the room. Everyone was whispering and discussing.

The Star Arc Civilization was also confused.

"To be able to pass the intelligence to the World Tree, they must have quite good technical strength. They chose to betray us in such a dangerous situation. What are they after…"

However, halfway through his sentence, he suddenly paused and looked up at the expressionless Han Xiao.

The upper echelons also snapped back to reality. They had all realized Han Xiao's true intentions, and their expressions changed.

Wait a minute, Black Star came to our door at this time and purposely brought up this topic. Does he think we're the traitors who leaked the information ‽

Of course, the Super Star Cluster Alliance had always been at odds with the three Universal Civilizations and was the biggest suspect, but this matter had nothing to do with them!

"Are you suspecting us ‽" The Star Arc Leader's eyes widened.

Han Xiao looked around and did not reply directly. Instead, he summoned a virtual screen and said,

"According to the information I've found, you guys set up a plan called 'Great Relocation Plan' more than ten years ago. The specific content is probably to take all the people and resources and leave the explored universe while the war is still ongoing to find another territory. This plan needs an opportunity, and only when the three Universal Civilizations are at a stalemate with the World Tree will you have a chance…"

The upper echelons of the Super Star Cluster became even more solemn.

They had thought that this plan was rather secretive. Gathering the people and resources was for the sake of war in name only. On the surface, it seemed like they had a reasonable motive. At most, the others would think that they were leaving a way out if the war failed, and they would not think that they were planning to run away.

"You already know… It's no wonder. With your ability, as long as you're suspicious of us, it won't be difficult for you to find these things." The Star Arc Leader was shocked, but when he thought of Han Xiao's ability, he accepted reality and said helplessly, "So, you think that we deliberately lured the World Tree into an all-out invasion to mess up the situation and make it easier to retreat?"

"What do you think?" Han Xiao tilted his head.

Hearing this, everyone knew that Han Xiao was probably here to condemn them.

The Star Arc Leader gritted his teeth and said, "I know you think we have a motive, but we did not do this. We are not traitors!"

Although they wanted to escape, they did not want to become traitors. Otherwise, if they were targeted by the three Universal Civilizations, there would definitely be many twists and turns in the 'Great Relocation Plan'. The three Universal Civilizations would not allow a 'traitor' like them to escape easily.

"What evidence do you have to prove that you didn't do it?" Han Xiao said emotionlessly.

Hearing this, the Star Arc Leader's thoughts raced, but his mind was in a mess. He could not think of any reason to prove that this matter had nothing to do with them. How much evidence did he need?!

However, before he could reply, Han Xiao continued.

"Maybe this wasn't your idea, but can you guarantee that this wasn't done by one of the civilizations present here?"

The Star Arc leader was stunned, and his expression changed. He knew that Han Xiao was right. He could only guarantee that he was not a traitor, but he could not guarantee that the other Super Star Cluster civilizations would not do anything in private.

He slowly turned his head and looked at the other members of the alliance with a questioning look in his eyes. Everyone understood what he meant and spoke.

"It's not me, I didn't do it!"

"It's not me either. I don't know anything about this!"

Very soon, the Star Arc Leader looked at the last person. He remembered that during the meeting some time ago, it was this leader of the Super Star Cluster who suggested helping the World Tree.

The leader of this civilization was furious. "What are you looking at me for ‽ I didn't do it! We're all in this together, I won't ignore the collective interests of the alliance!"

The Star Arc Leader gritted his teeth and looked at Han Xiao. "As you can see, this has nothing to do with us…"

Han Xiao did not say anything. He only tilted his head and looked at the Star Arc Leader with a strange gaze as if saying 'are you joking with me?'

Seeing this, the Star Arc Leader fell silent.

He also knew that no one would admit it if he asked this question. It was ridiculous for everyone to deny it together. It was not convincing at all. No one knew if the members of the alliance were lying.

However, the Star Arc Leader knew very well that no matter if it was done by a member of the Super Star Cluster, they definitely could not admit it. Otherwise, they would become 'traitors'.

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and said in a more serious tone, "Don't say I didn't warn you. I'll give you one more chance. Are you sure you didn't do it?"

"Black Star, we can't produce any evidence at the moment, but we really didn't do it," the Star Arc Leader said anxiously.

"Alright, I trust you guys."

"I hope you won't jump to conclusions. If you keep watching us, the real traitor will escape. I…" The Star Arc leader subconsciously trailed off before suddenly raising his voice." Wait, you believe us ‽ "

He had just racked his brains to convince Han Xiao, but he did not expect Han Xiao to change his mind before he could even use his justifications.

However, at this moment, Han Xiao spoke again. "However, it's useless for me to believe you. The three Universal Civilizations have to believe you. You have to find a way to prove your innocence."

"You mean…"

"It is natural for you to stay and fight hard." Han Xiao spread out his hands and said, "Think about it, the three Universal Civilizations are suspecting a traitor. The moment you leave, you'll confirm your identity as a traitor. The only way is to give up on your so-called relocation plan and focus on fighting the World Tree. Only then can you clear the suspicion."

Hearing this, the eyes of many Super Star Cluster Civilizations' leaders narrowed.

The Star Arc Leader frowned and no longer panicked. He slowly said, "Your Excellency Black Star, I'm afraid this is your true purpose for coming, isn't it?"

He was not an idiot, and he immediately realized Han Xiao's true goal.

There were priorities in everything. The Super Star Cluster Alliance did not want to become traitors, but the relocation plan was more important. They would not give up the migration just to prove that they were not traitors.

The Star Arc Leader even suspected that the so-called traitor was just an excuse that Han Xiao came up with after discovering their relocation plan.

Han Xiao did not think much of it. He smiled and said casually, "Hehe, I know what you guys are thinking. Traitors really exist, and the three Universal Civilizations suspecting you guys is also true. However, I never thought that you guys were traitors."

"Why do you think so?" The Star Arc Leader was curious.

"We've known each other for decades. I know the style of your decision-makers quite well. In fact, given your situation, the possibility of you daring to collude with the enemy is quite low. However, because of your past history, you're the most suspicious. This is very similar to framing someone. My intuition tells me that this has little to do with you… Of course, this doesn't mean that you're not suspicious. I can't confirm if you're doing the opposite."

Han Xiao did not plan to eliminate all the pressure on the Super Star Cluster, so he did not reveal [Bold Explorer] to them.

Han Xiao knew that the Super Star Cluster Alliance would not give up on the relocation plan so easily. He planned to have this talk to use the suspicion of traitors as an excuse at the start. He only wanted to make the Super Star Cluster Alliance nervous and understand the situation.

"It seems like even though your big picture has been destroyed, you still have your rationality." The Star Arc leader had mixed feelings. He nodded and said, "I really don't know about the traitor, but we can't give up on the relocation plan and stay behind to fight. Since you've found the information, you should know how important this plan is to us."

Han Xiao nodded and said, "The existence of the three Universal Civilizations has limited your development. For many years, they have been using all kinds of excuses to suppress you and prevent you from entering the era of technological explosion. The top talents and resources of the galactic society have all flowed to them, and as this continued to accumulate, the gap between the two of you became larger and larger…"

"That's right! Thinking back, when the exploration era war had just ended, the three Universal Civilizations set the order. They did not have the strength to dominate all the civilizations back then, but now? So many years have passed, and they are enjoying the best resources and the biggest development dividend in the entire galactic society. There is already a generational difference in our technologies… Now, we still have some ability to resist, but the longer we wait, the bigger the gap. Sooner or later, we will completely lose the qualifications to challenge the three Universal Civilizations, and we will only become servants."

A Super Star Cluster leader said with a helpless tone.

The Star Arc Leader nodded and added, "It is precisely because we can see the distant future, that we have to constantly search for opportunities to change our fate while we can still resist. The Flickering World was an attempt, but it failed. The migration now is a better opportunity, and we will not give up."

"I understand your appeal, truly I do… but with all due respect, what you're doing is just a slow death. What you're thinking of being mutually tied down is only superficial, thinking that you'll be safe once you leave the war zone. You have nowhere to run. After the World Tree destroys the three Universal Civilizations, they will definitely find you. They have extraordinary abilities in the Information Form aspect…"

Han Xiao explained the Information Form ability of the World Tree in detail, ensuring that everyone present knew the true situation. He then paused and continued,

"Therefore, your only way out is to stay and destroy the World Tree Civilization with us… This is a very simple choice. This way, your development might not be free, but at least your civilization can survive."

The leaders of the Super Star Cluster looked at each other and discussed softly.

The Star Arc leader pondered for a while before slowly saying, "For us to send our troops into the battlefield, you have put in a lot of effort. You even personally acted as a lobbyist… Let's assume what you said is the truth, but I have a concern that needs your answer."

"Speak."

"Will the three Universal Civilizations let us go so easily?" The Star Arc leader leaned forward and asked, "Let me make myself clear. If we defeat the World Tree and win back peace, how can you guarantee that the three Universal Civilizations won't settle the score afterward? How can you guarantee that they won't give us the identity of 'traitors' and attack us rightfully?"

Everyone stared at Han Xiao with a forceful gaze.

This was not the first time the three Universal Civilizations had used 'groundless' tactics on them. Therefore, the Super Star Cluster Alliance did not have any hope of getting rid of the suspicion. Whether or not they were 'traitors' would still depend on what the three Universal Civilizations said. If they were to be labeled as 'colluding with the enemy' after this, they would not be able to turn the tables and might even face a disaster.

"Regarding that…" Han Xiao stroked his chin and said calmly," If we win this war and you guys don't leave, I can stand on your side and prevent the three Universal Civilizations from using this method. I will also try my best to help you break the development restrictions of the three Universal Civilizations so that you guys don't have to abandon your homeland to have a chance to develop freely. "

"You?" The Star Arc Leader narrowed his eyes. "You might have such an organization, but why are you doing this?"

"Don't forget, war is a huge reshuffle. The structure of the three Universal Civilizations will definitely be overturned after the war. It's rare for the three Universal Civilizations to weaken, and they will lose their firm control. This is the best time to change things… Also, helping you guys is also helping myself. Without the invasion of foreign enemies, we will all be the eyesores of the three Universal Civilizations. We have a lot of room for cooperation."

Han Xiao said slowly.

The Star Arc Leader did not budge.

"Sounds good, but how can you guarantee that you won't go back on your word like before? You have to know that your reputation isn't too good."

"I don't need to promise anyone," Han Xiao said casually. "I'm just telling you which path is of death and which path is of life. I helped you analyze the pros and cons and gave you a better choice, but I can't make decisions for you."

"What if we don't accept your suggestion?" The Star Arc Leader said with a solemn tone.

"If you insist, I will express my regret. Without the armed forces of the Super Star Cluster, our pressure will be greater, and our losses will be more exaggerated. However, our chances of winning are still very high."

Han Xiao stroked his chin, paused, and said softly,

"As for you guys… do I need to explain what will happen to deserters? With me around, we will be able to find you no matter how far you run. Don't blame me when the time comes. I've given you guys a chance."

Everyone's expression changed as they heard the blatant threat.

"Black Star!" one of the Modo Civilization's leaders shouted. "We know that you're very powerful. Perhaps no one is your match in individual strength level, but do you really think that you're invincible after entering the Transcendent Grade? Do you think you can influence the decisions of so many civilizations ‽"

However, Han Xiao shook his head and said calmly, "No, there's no such thing as true invincibility in the world. The so-called invincibility is only invincible in the current technological level environment, and the development of the world is dynamic. As the times change and the civilizations progress, more new technologies will appear. Maybe one day, all the principles of the Space Wonders will be discovered, and the Transcendents will no longer be unbeatable. Maybe it would even be possible to mass-produce Beyond Grade As and Transcendents. Any individual achievements that feel unbelievable now will eventually be duplicated by the collective civilizations, resulting in fission."

Everyone was stunned. They had thought that Han Xiao would refute, but they did not expect him to agree. They did not know how to respond. They thought that Han Xiao was trying to ease the atmosphere and take back his threat.

However, the next moment, they knew they were wrong.

Han Xiao looked at everyone and said coldly,

"However, those things will only happen in the future. At least in the foreseeable future, I am an unbeatable existence! You can see my words as a threat, or as an ultimatum. Anyway, do your best and don't make a choice that disappoints me. Otherwise, I don't mind destroying all the civilizations here. At that time, you will know that I'm more dangerous than the World Tree!"

Everyone in the room fell silent.

After a while, the Star Arc Leader seemed to have made a decision.

"If the situation is as you say, we can temporarily put aside the relocation plan and send more troops to participate in the war. However, if the losses are too great, we will definitely evacuate. No matter how much you threaten us, it will be useless."

Han Xiao's expression returned to normal, and he nodded.

"That's enough. You will know in the future that this is a wise choice."

Chapter 1427: Wuornos' Sensation

In the shallow layer dimensional base.

Han Xiao turned off the communicator and deactivated the remote projection. He rubbed his forehead and closed his eyes for a while before opening them again.

"The Super Star Cluster has reached a consensus that they will not cause any trouble for the time being."

Han Xiao heaved a sigh of relief.

He tried to reason with them, analyzed the situation for them, threatened them, and tempted them. In the end, he finally managed to persuade them back.

Of course, this was only a temporary consensus. The Super Star Cluster Alliance did not agree to give up on migrating and was only willing to stay and watch, and increase the support for a while longer. However, this was enough. If the Super Star Cluster Alliance did not give him face and ran away, even if he could make the Super Star Cluster Alliance pay the price afterward, he would not be able to stop the negative chain reaction in the war.

Currently, the armed forces of the explored universe were not lacking, and the internal division had temporarily disappeared before it even started. The Super Star Cluster Alliance would not become a 'traitor' for the time being.

Damn it, the galactic society is indeed carried by me!

Han Xiao shook his head. He opened the real-time military star map of the explored universe, and areas appeared in front of him, blue in color. Inside the various Star Fields, green spots were appearing, expanding at an extremely slow speed. This represented the invasion range of the World Tree.

"The World Tree has great momentum, but the territory of the three Universal Civilizations is too large, and even if the World Tree blossoms more, its invasion will still be slow. Although the battle is intense, the threat in the short term is still low."

Han Xiao analyzed.

A sudden change in the situation would more or less affect the mentality. The three Universal Civilizations were a little flustered when dealing with this, but Han Xiao still maintained his calm. He ignored the anxiety of the territories being continuously devoured and calmly judged the situation. After all, he had seen worse situations in his previous life, so this small situation could not scare him.

No matter how strong the World Tree was, it had to be eating slowly. It couldn't become fat in one bite. Furthermore, the resistance of the Galactic Alliance Army made it very difficult for it to 'feed'.

In comparison, Han Xiao felt that the biggest effect of the World Tree's full invasion was firstly a blow to the people and morale of the galactic society, and secondly, it affected their resource production and productivity.

According to the information that was leaked, as well as his experience from his previous life, Han Xiao could guess the World Tree's priority targets. The military factories and resource planets of the various organizations were definitely the first choices, which would reduce the speed of the three Universal Civilizations' troops mobilization.

Second would be the mother planets of some Star System or Star Cluster civilizations, governance planets, and refuge planets with large populations. This way, they could cause panic and internal chaos in the galactic society. The World Tree had invaded many civilizations, so it was clear about this trick.

Then, there were the important bases of some Beyond Grade A races and private organizations. Destroying them would cut off the wings of the three Universal Civilizations.

Of course, as the core of the galactic society, the Central Galaxy was the most important target. However, Han Xiao guessed that the World Tree would most likely not attack it for the time being because the Central Galaxy would be heavily guarded. Once they invaded, a large group battle would break out, similar to the border war.

The World Tree now had many space coordinates, and with such an advantage, it should not be willing to continue fighting with the low-efficiency frontal attack method. Instead, it chose to strike the weakest areas and focus on continuous harassment, displaying its high mobility and advantage in sustaining war with war.

"These are all areas that need to be protected. After this battle, I wonder how many more desolate universe belts there will be… It's a pity that the World Tree's mechanism is too perverse. Otherwise, I could have given it a taste of its own medicine."

Han Xiao was a little helpless.

With his individual strength, he could go to the World Tree territory and make a scene. However, more than ten years ago, he had learned a lot of information from the foreign experts of the World Tree. The World Tree's base could be retracted into its body at any time, and it could pack up and run away. There was not much use in harassing them as they could just move to another place. This would not affect the enemy's productivity much, because the World Tree itself was the largest military factory. It could directly convert resources inside, and there was no need to build countless factories like normal civilizations. Otherwise, Han Xiao would not think that it was a complementing target to [Virtual Creation (Pseudo)].

Furthermore, the Blessed Races of the World Tree were eyeing the Pivotal Snake. Han Xiao did not want to leave the shallow layer dimensions. Even if he had to reinforce the main universe, he would only send out a portion of the Mechanical Oracles. His main body would remain in the secondary dimensions to guard his 'home'.

The World Tree was not willing to sit back and do nothing. Apart from invading the territory of the three Universal Civilizations, it would not give up on killing the Pivotal Snake. He did not know what the other party's plan was, so he had to be careful.

"However, although it's not very useful, it's not bad to be able to give them trouble. With my current strength, I don't have to worry about being besieged on a large scale as I did in the past. Wouldn't it be even greater if they get agitated and fight me head-on?"

Han Xiao felt that it was worth a try.

...

Arcane Church, Temple of Ten Thousand Gods.

Wuornos walked slowly in the corridor formed by tall God sculptures of different shapes and sizes, holding a ball of spiritual light in his hand. Every time he walked in front of a God sculpture, he would use the corresponding simple ceremony to perform a ritual that was neither too fast nor too slow. He then flicked the spiritual light into the body of the statue, looking like he was feeding his pets or spreading bait to the fishes.

This was his daily ritual. Usually, he was alone, but today, there was a bunch of 'tails' behind him. A group of senior members of the Arcane Church, who were wearing priest robes and officer uniforms, followed behind him.

"High Priest, now that the World Tree has invaded, our high-level combatants are not enough. I hope you can help."

"Aren't you afraid that I'll die on the battlefield and drop the National Treasure?" Wuornos said casually without looking back.

"Of course, we don't wish to take the risk. When the border wars occurred and secondary dimensions were invaded, we did not request you to take action. It's just that the situation is urgent this time, and we need you to use some of the incarnations to help…" an officer said softly.

This was a very normal request. In the past, Wuornos would have agreed to it, but now, he was different.

"I refuse." Wuornos shook his head.

"This… why?"

"I'm only one step away from the Transcendent Grade, and I can obtain the opportunity to advance at any time. I need to maintain my peak state at all times to prevent myself from missing the opportunity. As long as the enemies don't attack the Arcane Church's mother planet, don't look at me for anything else. I don't want to waste my energy elsewhere," Wuornos said casually.

"But the other direct descendants are all fighting a bloody battle. Isn't your refusal a little…"

"You don't understand. Whether or not I can advance to the Transcendent Grade is more important than these battles. This is the independence granted to me by the Pope. I have the right to decide if I want to participate in the battle." Wuornos waved his hand casually. "Stop pestering me here. Go back."

The group of people looked at each other, clenched their teeth, and left with dissatisfaction.

Wuornos did not care.

His last advancement had failed, causing him to be heavily injured. However, there was also an unexpected benefit, which was that the Pope saw that he indeed had the possibility of advancing at any time, so he simply allowed him to decide when he wanted to join the battle.

Therefore, over the past ten years, Wuornos did not participate in the war, nor did he attempt to advance rashly. He had been recuperating and reflecting on why he had failed.

Wuornos always felt that he was missing some key elements. It was not as if he had gained nothing after searching for so long. He had vaguely discovered the mysterious ability hidden in his body, but it had yet to be fully activated. It seemed to be able to sense something unknown, and his intuition told him that this feeling was very important for Promotion.

"When I figure out what's going on, I should be able to step into the Transcendent Grade. Maybe this is the secret of Black Star's Promotion. I won't fail again this time…"

Wuornos' eyes flashed.

...

Somewhere in the Endless Nebulae, two fleets were engaged in an intense battle. One side was the World Tree invaders, and the other was the Black Star Army.

A large number of charge cabins latched onto the spaceships of the World Tree and sent out batches of army players to board the battleships. The World Tree battleships fell one after another from the inside. Many Calamity Grade players wore mechanical suits and swam around the battlefield.

Due to the sudden change in the situation, the combat missions of the players had also changed. From guarding the borders, they had gone to different areas to stop the World Tree invaders. The mission format was much more varied.

The border defense circle of the Flickering World almost transformed into a teleportation station, and the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device operated continuously, sending batches of players to the various Star Fields.

The new level cap was unlocked in Version 5.5, and many players had just entered the Calamity Grade.

A Calamity Grade that did not fear death naturally could not be underestimated. Furthermore, there was a large group of them. Although there were many Calamity Grade Supers on the World Tree's side, they were not as expendable as the players.

Everyone could revive, but the time interval between the revivals of the World Tree was longer, and the dead warriors appeared in the mother tree's body. They could not be revived on the spot like the players, and their effectiveness could not be compared at all. It was equivalent to the players' real strength being many times stronger than on the surface; one player was equal to many.

There were Immortals on both sides, and the battle was extremely intense. However, it was clear who was stronger, and the World Tree warriors were forced to retreat.

"This group of Immortals is too terrifying. With so many Calamity Grades as a suicide squad, only the main elites can fight them. We can't hold on at all."

Inside this invading main ship of the World Tree, the commander was surprised.

Ever since the World Tree obtained the intelligence of the three Universal Civilizations, this information had been shared in the mental network. From the Tree King to the grassroots soldiers, they all understood the Super classification of the three Universal Civilizations, as well as the Immortals and other strange existences.

"There seems to be a limit to the revival of these Immortals. If we kill them multiple times in a short period, they won't be able to revive for some time," the aide-de-camp said.

The commander murmured, "I wonder what kind of existence this is. What kind of power did their revival come from…"

The aide-de-camp shrugged and said, "Maybe they have a World Tree too? Who knows?"

...

A few days later, somewhere in the World Tree territory.

A wormhole slowly opened, and a mechanical body came out. It was Han Xiao's Lord's Avatar.

Han Xiao twisted his neck and activated the self-inspection device. The outer armor opened and closed like scales, revealing fine cracks. He felt the exquisite feeling of the mechanical body and let out a comfortable groan.

Due to the [Energy Base—God of All Machines], the Transcendent Grade Lord's Descent had improved in perception aspect.

With the Lord's Descent of a Beyond Grade A, there was still a barrier between his senses and the Lord's Avatar body. Although he could control it like his arm, he could clearly tell that it was not his body.

But at the Transcendent Grade, the feeling of the Lord's Avatar was almost the same as the main body. It was not like a mechanical avatar but more like a main body. The control was fine and smooth.

If an example was to be given, a Beyond Grade A's Lord's Descent was like the remote control of a virtual reality. It was very real, but deep down, he knew it was fake. The feeling of a Transcendent Grade's Lord's Descent was like he had been reborn…

"This feels good. The avatar's power capacity has reached more than 94%. Not bad."

Han Xiao clenched his fists. He could feel the rhythm of every alloy, every part, and every biochemical tendon in his body. He nodded with satisfaction, then looked up at the sky full of stars in the World Tree territory.

"More than ten years ago, I was heavily injured by you guys and almost died in your base camp. Now is the time to settle the score!"

Chapter 1428: Unexpected Discovery

The mechanical army swarmed out like a black tide and gathered together, covering the Lord's Avatar. It quickly combined and turned into a huge Mechanical Deity that spanned across the galaxy.

Han Xiao controlled the gigantic Supreme Heavenly Venerate and cruised through the galaxy of the World Tree territory, heading toward the dazzling starlight.

Not long after, a planet wrapped in roots appeared in his sight, getting closer and closer.

Without saying a word, Han Xiao raised his palm, and a strong psionic light appeared in his palm. The next moment, a thick beam of light shot out and penetrated the planet like a spear.

A hole was left on the surface of the planet, and the internal structure of the planet was exposed through the hole. The crust, the mantle, and the core of the planet were clearly separated, like the layers of a cake.

After a moment of stagnation, the planet suddenly collapsed inward toward the opening. Its crust shattered and turned into a molten stream. The mantle surged violently, and the brightness of the planet's core increased. Powerful light burst out from the center, and the next moment, the entire planet exploded, turning into an expanding ball of light.

Han Xiao's body did not move at all, and his shield automatically blocked the strong shockwave of the planet's explosion. The electric arcs were not damaged at all, as though there were layers of energy hurricanes surrounding him.

This time, he was here to cause trouble. He did not need to be as cautious as he had been more than ten years ago. What he wanted was to create a huge commotion.

The next moment, the information state alarm was triggered. Not long after, the entire World Tree Civilization knew that Han Xiao had suddenly appeared and destroyed a planet.

Han Xiao had not gone far when the space around him fluctuated. Group after group of World Tree fleets passed through the World Tree Express and headed toward the area of the explosion. Without hesitation, they opened fire on the planet-sized Supreme Celestial Body.

A dense rain of light rained down on the Supreme Heavenly Venerate's shield. However, while the thunder was loud, the resulting rain was small. It could only create large sparks of energy, unable to break through the seemingly indestructible shield.

Han Xiao raised his hand and clenched his fist. Energy gushed out and crushed the battleships. Although he was surrounded by the fleet, he seemed to be the one surrounding all the enemies instead.

Very soon, more World Tree fleets arrived at the battlefield with the help of the World Tree territory's rapid descent channel. They all joined the battle, and more and more battleships surrounded Han Xiao.

In the Tree King Palace on the other side, both the Ancestral Tree King and the Fortitude Tree King were paying attention to Han Xiao's actions through the mental network.

"Why did this guy suddenly come here?" The Fortitude Tree King was shocked. "Is he planning to attack our territory alone?"

"Looks like it." The Ancestral Tree King narrowed his eyes.

"Should we stop him?

When the Ancestral Tree King heard this, he shook his head firmly. "There's no need. He's very difficult to deal with. Human wave tactics are very inefficient against him. We don't know how many troops we'll have to invest to stop him. We'll also have to send a portion of the invading troops back. That's exactly what he wants. He wants to divert our attention and obstruct our progress."

"Then what should we do? Just watch him wreak havoc in our territory?"

"Since we can't stop him, we won't. Let the Mother Tree retract its territory and change its base. We'll leave this place to him."

The Ancestral Tree King spoke without hesitation.

There was another method, which was to use the Tree God's Descent to fight a Transcendent Grade. However, after the last battle, the Ancestral Tree King felt that the incomplete Tree God's Descent would not be able to defeat Black Star, so he decided not to waste the time and simply abandoned the area.

Due to the connection of the mind network and the unique parent tree mechanism, the World Tree Civilization had a huge advantage, which was its astonishing executional ability. As soon as the Ancestral Tree King gave the order, the enormous World Tree territory immediately began to alter itself.

In the starry sky, the roots of the World Tree could be seen moving slowly, as though they were uprooting themselves. The 'land' that carried the World Tree was the universe of the territory. Usually, these roots were hidden, but now, they appeared one after another.

The planets turned into liquids and fused into the World Tree Root. The World Tree Root also retracted, and the space crack outside the planet disappeared.

For a time, the countless stars dimmed until they disappeared. The originally prosperous and bright galaxy slowly turned into a desolate universe. As the World Tree retrieved the planets, the Star Field was quickly recovering its original appearance. It was desolate, cold, and dark. Not a single blade of grass grew here.

Han Xiao, who was slaughtering the World Tree fleet, also noticed the abnormal changes in the universe space. This was also the first time he had seen the World Tree migrate its base. He gazed at the universe filled with tree roots, revealing their 'uprooted' state.

"You're planning to move the moment you see me? How decisive."

Han Xiao was surprised.

Without the ability of the roots, the World Tree fleet could not be deployed. The World Tree fleet present received the order and immediately ended the siege. They took advantage of the last moment to quickly teleport out, planning to retreat.

Han Xiao crushed another fleet. Suddenly, he activated the Tree God's Character Summon Card.

Swoosh!

The next moment, space cracks suddenly appeared around the Supreme Heavenly Venerate. Roots shot out and swept across the fleet, swallowing the battleships.

The roots that he had summoned with his Character Summon Card flowed with blue light, completely different from the green World Tree itself!

"How can he use the power of the World Tree?!"

The Ancestral Tree King had been paying close attention the entire time, and he was stunned upon seeing this.

Could Black Star be a member of the World Tree?! Their kin?!!

That's not right. How is this possible?

At the same time, the Mother Tree's consciousness also reacted, and the Ancestral Tree King could sense the shock within.

The World Tree itself was also confused, wondering why a life form that was not controlled by it had the same power.

Han Xiao was controlling the summoned roots to attack the fleet, and he was enjoying this novel feeling. Suddenly, he owned a bunch of 'tentacles', and he finally experienced the joy of being a Tree King.

Right at this moment, a wave of mental fluctuations suddenly transmitted over, bringing along the Ancestral Tree King's shocked voice.

"Black Star! How do you have the power of the World Tree?!"

'"Guess?"

Han Xiao raised his brows.

He activated this Character Summon Card on a whim mainly to test if the root he summoned was connected to the World Tree.

After this attempt, he was certain that the roots of the Character Summon Card belonged to him and would not be controlled by the World Tree.

Even if he devoured the matter, he could only disassemble it into energy to replenish his own, unlike the World Tree, which preserved the information form and converted it. When the Character Summon Card's effect ends, these temporarily summoned roots would automatically disperse, and the things he devoured during this period would vanish as well.

However, in the eyes of outsiders, these blue roots used him as the source. Their strength was extremely similar to the World Tree, but they were an independent entity. This made the Ancestral Tree King's imagination run wild.

At this moment, information about the revivors and Immortals of the explored universe flashed through his mind. The Ancestral Tree King's eyes widened, and he felt that he had found the truth.

"I understand! There's actually another World Tree in the universe, and it's on you!"

The information leaked by the Star Alliance included Han Xiao's life. The Ancestral Tree King had always been surprised by how short Han Xiao's rise had been. At this moment, he felt enlightened and found an explanation.

The undying characteristics of those Immortals were very similar to the members of the World Tree. If those Immortals were members of another World Tree, it would make sense. Black Star had been pretending that he had nothing to do with them, but he was secretly making a fortune. He was the one behind this!

"Two World Trees? You really dare to fantasize."

Han Xiao could not help but laugh at the Ancestral Tree King's imagination.

Just as he was about to say something, many spatial tunnels suddenly opened up around him, and green roots of the World Tree extended out, wrapping around Han Xiao's blue roots. They twisted together like snakes, slowly wriggling, squeezing, pulling, and sticking.

Seeing this, Han Xiao paused, and his expression suddenly became strange.

This scene, why does this look like a tongue kiss…

It was a little painful for the eyes to see…

The corner of Han Xiao's eyes twitched. He could even feel the emotions of the World Tree from where the roots were intertwined. It was an extremely passionate and yearning thought that contained the desire to become one.

The power of the World Tree flowed along with the roots and into the blue roots. It was actively transferring its energy as if it could not wait to share the good stuff. The World Tree was also moving the power contained in the blue roots out of it as if it wanted to make a special 'body fluid' exchange.

"Is he treating the root I called out as a spouse?!?!"

Han Xiao's eyes widened in shock, his body frozen stiff.

He had thought that when the original World Tree saw him, the blue version, they would be hostile to each other and would fight to the death. He did not expect that not only would they not fight, but the World Tree would take the initiative to 'communicate' with him. It did not have any hostility and was very passionate.

Could it be that… this was because the original World Tree had always been a unique existence that was lonely? Now that it had finally found someone of the same species, its mating habits were ignited, and its thirst unbearable. Its instincts claimed the upper hand?!

"The ancients did not lie to me. Two tigers cannot share one mountain unless it's one male and one female."

Han Xiao's interest was piqued.

On the other side, the Ancestral Tree King was completely dumbfounded. As the Tree King, he could feel the joy and excitement from the mother tree's consciousness. Even his gaze toward Han Xiao was affected.

Han Xiao, who was supposed to be his enemy, suddenly became friendly in his eyes.

F*ck, we were about to fight to the death, why did Her Majesty surrender first?!

The Ancestral Tree King hurriedly shook his head to get rid of the influence of the Mother Tree's consciousness. "What's going on?"

Han Xiao came back to his senses, chuckled, and said with a teasing tone, "Didn't you say there were two World Trees? I'm a male version, yours is a female, what do you think will happen?"

The Ancestral Tree King was furious. "Bullsh*t! Why is it that when a female sees a male, the female loses all will to fight? Shouldn't it be the other way around?!"

"Woah, I didn't expect you to be so opinionated. To think you're actually good at both fists and words."

Black lines appeared on Han Xiao's forehead. He turned around to look at the blue and green roots that were entangling him. Suddenly, he chuckled.

"This is too proactive. By the way, your mother tree is amazing!"

"..."

Although the Ancestral Tree King did not understand Han Xiao's teasing, he knew that it was not a good thing. He felt a sense of sourness, and the green light on his body seemed to have become brighter.

He deactivated the telepathic communication, suppressed his anger, and ordered the troops to evacuate quickly.

Not long after, the World Tree finally returned to its base. The fleets that surrounded Han Xiao were either fleeing or dying and the World Tree Root, which was frantically looking for a mate, also reluctantly returned to the space channel. No matter how it teased, the blue root that Han Xiao had summoned with his Character Summon Card did not respond.

In reality, it was because the blue root was a temporarily generated rootless tree. It was akin to a castrated version of the World Tree. Since it was completely controlled by Han Xiao, it did not have any self-awareness, nor the ability to procreate.

Not long after, the time for the Tree God Character Summon Card ended. The blue roots shattered inch by inch, turning into light fragments that dissipated. Only the Supreme Heavenly Venerate was left floating in the desolate universe.

The World Tree had already abandoned its territory, and all the planets and individuals had returned to the mother tree. They had completely evacuated. It was as if they had been frightened by Han Xiao alone and did not even want their base anymore. They had moved overnight… and that was the truth.

It was just two words, having face!

"Tsk, unknowingly, my deterrence is already so strong."

Han Xiao shook his head and laughed.

If it was anyone else, they would most likely have run away because they would not want to lose face. A civilization as large as theirs would not be scared to the point of abandoning their homeland by him alone. At the very least, they would have to send enough troops to fight until they suffered heavy casualties and felt that they could not take it anymore. Only then would they have a reason to retreat. However, the World Tree did not care about such things and did not feel embarrassed at all. He had not even gone all out yet, and they had already retreated. Such enemies were the hardest to deal with.

"Although forcing the World Tree to move will give them some trouble, it won't solve the root of the problem. However, this trip was worth it. I seem to have discovered something interesting."

Han Xiao smiled. He did not expect the Tree God's Character Summon Card to have such a miraculous effect.

"Now that I've used it for an experiment, this Character Summon Card has three more uses. It might be effective at the right time."

Chapter 1429: Premeditated Assassination

The World Tree moved overnight, and the thought of causing a huge ruckus naturally fell through. Han Xiao left behind a group of mechanical troops in this Star Field that had once again become empty and lonely, then took back his Lord's Avatar.

As long as the World Tree's mechanism was not disturbed, its base could be built anywhere in the universe. They had wiped out many civilizations over the years and had the coordinates of many areas. They could just find a place that they had turned into a desolate universe belt and migrate there.

The migration process had a certain impact on their invasion at the frontlines, which caused a slight gap in support. Han Xiao told the three Universal Civilizations about this.

After learning that the World Tree had been frightened by Han Xiao alone, the three leaders were shocked and also ordered the strategic command center to make adjustments.

The flames of war raged across the entire explored universe, and a month passed very quickly. Under the Galactic Alliance Army's attack, the World Tree's first full-scale invasion finally stopped.

Although the World Tree's aggressive arrival had caused quite a bit of panic in the galactic society, in terms of practical benefits, the World Tree's first wave of invasion did not cause too much damage. Most of the invading teams were intercepted by the Galactic Alliance Army. Although they had devoured some planets, this number was just a drop in the ocean for the entire explored universe. Furthermore, they were scattered everywhere and did not have much development potential.

Although the three Universal Civilizations did not have a powerful home defense system like the Information Form Warning Network and the World Tree Express, the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device was just as amazing, allowing the galactic alliance army to have extremely strong military mobility. As long as an invader appeared, they would be able to send reinforcements in an instant.

If it were any other civilization, they would be extremely passive in the face of the World Tree's unpredictable harassment and invasion. This was the battle of attrition that the World Tree was good at, but the technologies of the three Universal Civilizations countered the usual tactics of the World Tree, preventing it from achieving the best results.

Of course, although the first wave of the World Tree fleet was repelled, there were still quite a few World Tree fleets left in the galactic society, hiding in the dark. This was the weakness of the three Universal Civilizations. Without sufficient monitoring devices, although the reinforcements were fast, as long as the World Tree fleet hid and did not appear, it would be difficult for them to lock onto the enemy within their territory.

After resolving the current emergency, the upper echelons of the Galactic Alliance Army invited the various officers and the Beyond Grade A Association upper echelons to hold a strategic meeting to analyze the current situation and discuss the subsequent actions.

"…Although the traitor leaked the information and caused the World Tree to invade the entire realm, our current situation is not as bad as we thought. The vast territory and the rapid reinforcement speed are two of our greatest strengths in maintaining the situation. It has already shown a significant role in the war."

Teny pointed at the 3D star map on the table and summarized the current situation.

The same star map model was floating in front of the participants, displaying the current strategic deployment.

"According to the statistics, most of the World Tree's targets are military facilities, resource planets, civilizations' mother planets, and Beyond Grade A race territories. From this, it can be seen that the World Tree's main strategy is to destroy our productivity and social stability. However, at present, the World Tree has only succeeded a few times. We have already secretly relocated the important facilities in the early years, and part of the information leaked by the traitor is outdated."

Teny spoke with confidence.

The way the Star Alliance Observers hid was too low-profile, causing them to only be able to obtain general information from the internet. As such, the information was lagging. Thus, the Star Alliance Observers naturally had no way of knowing some confidential information of the advanced civilizations. The most valuable information they leaked to the World Tree was the star map and spatial coordinates.

"Does this mean that the traitor's position isn't high?" an officer asked.

"Not necessarily. Maybe it's just a disguise," another person retorted.

Teny interrupted the two of them, coughed, and said, "Ahem, regarding the traitor, we have someone else to take care of them. We don't need to discuss this matter, let's get back to the main topic… Our intercepting efficiency is quite good, and it's all thanks to the support of His Excellency Black Star and the Beyond Grade A Association. Otherwise, the high-level combatants of the World Tree would have been able to wreak havoc for a long time."

Hearing this, the officers turned around and nodded at the representatives of the Beyond Grade A Association.

Han Xiao nodded and said, "We wiped out quite a number of World Tree experts this time. They will need at least a year or two to make a comeback."

His Mechanical Oracles had worked together with the Beyond Grade As of the Association, direct descendants, and Holy Accord, eliminating a large number of high-level combatants of the World Tree. They had sent at least two to three hundred people back to be watered in the World Tree, so they would not be able to return anytime soon.

A portion of the experts from the other races encountered Han Xiao's Lord's Avatar and was hit by [Virtual Purification—Restore]. They exploded on the spot and turned into fireworks.

Other than dying in a normal battle, some of the high-level combatants of the World Tree had been used by Han Xiao to test the effects of [Information Form Obliteration], or they had been sealed by the Spacetime Amber and turned into his collection. There were about thirty of them, and the World Tree had lost these powerful individuals forever.

Due to the division of the battlefront, some Beyond Grade As from the three Universal Civilizations also died. They were logged in the Soul Comfort Monument that the three Universal Civilizations had set up and had recorded a new number of deaths.

Teny then turned to look at Manison and said with a deep voice, "This time, the Mechanical Race's territory was also the main focus of the invasion. We did not arrive in time. Luckily, His Excellency Mechanic Emperor defeated the enemy. We offer our apologies."

"It's just a small matter, not worth mentioning." Manison waved his hand and said calmly.

Everyone was surprised.

Manison's force was one of those which showed an astonishing performance against the invasion. He had hidden an astonishingly large mechanical army in the Mechanical Race's territory and wiped out the World Tree invaders without the aid of the galactic alliance army. The military strength he displayed was shocking.

Although Manison was no longer the authoritative figure of the Mechanic class, the foundation that he had built over the years was not just for show. Among the Beyond Grade As, he still had a lot of weight.

This time, an officer suddenly said thoughtfully, "Speaking of which, the Super Star Cluster Alliance had also sent out a lot of troops to provide support."

"Now that you mention it, I thought of something unusual. The World Tree's invasion seemed to have avoided the territory of the Super Star Cluster Alliance, and it was at most a small-scale harassment. That's why the Super Star Cluster was able to help."

"It is indeed a little strange…"

All the officers had strange looks on their faces.

In their eyes, the World Tree did not treat the Super Star Cluster Alliance as an invasion target. It was a little strange, giving them the feeling that they were in cahoots with each other. The suspicion of them being the traitor was quite high. However, the Super Star Cluster Alliance did not just stand by and watch but took the initiative to send troops to support the Galactic Alliance Army. This was a good action, which confused many of the upper echelons of the military, reducing their suspicion.

The Super Star Cluster Alliance did this to fulfill its agreement with Han Xiao. If they had not taken the initiative to provide support, the three Universal Civilizations would have been even more suspicious of them. But now, they were more confused than doubtful, and there were no signs of internal conflict for the time being.

Listening to everyone's discussion, Han Xiao's expression remained the same. He had convinced the Super Star Cluster Alliance, barely suppressing the suspicion within. However, he did not intend to speak of his contribution.

At this time, Commander-in-chief Simon took over the conversation and pulled it to the main topic.

"Currently, there are two things that we need to pay attention to. The first is to clean up the dormant World Tree invaders. Their main force has been chased away, but there are still a small number of troops within the borders. This is a hidden danger, and it has put quite a bit of mental pressure on the galactic society. What do you guys think?"

The three Universal Civilizations had neutralized the first wave of invasion, but the aftereffects were severe. Because their line of defense was suddenly breached by the World Tree, the people were panicking, and chaos broke out everywhere. The three Universal Civilizations had no choice but to take out more energy to deal with the refugees.

In this regard, the three Universal Civilizations were no different from normal civilizations. The World Tree was one of the few civilizations that did not have any internal conflicts.

After some discussion, the result was only to strengthen the strict military control. Now was not the time to talk about freedom.

Seeing this, Simon continued, "In addition, we have to figure out the World Tree's next move and make some preparations in advance. They did not invade the Central Galaxy this time, but they will take action sooner or later. They are in a race against time, so they won't be able to wait long."

The upper echelons of the military began discussing this topic.

Han Xiao and the others did not participate and listened quietly.

After some discussion, the military finally came to a consensus. The meeting temporarily ended, and the participants passed down the order.

...

Secondary Dimension World, World Tree Blessed Race territory.

The roots of the trees formed a spiral-shaped pagoda that stood in the middle of the ground. Surrounding the pagoda were buildings formed by huge trees that formed a tree city. Countless members of the Blessed Race lived there.

Space cracks opened from time to time, and the battleships of the Blessed Race came and went.

Two figures floated in the blue-green sky, looking down at the tree city below. One was the Ancestral Tree King, and the other was a female figure in a gorgeous robe. Her skin was like tender leaves, glowing with jade green light. Her long white hair was spread behind her back, and there was a complicated and mysterious mark on her forehead. She was one of the 13 Ancestral Spirits, Hayleen.

"Your Excellency Tree King, why are you looking for me?"

"I have a mission for you."

"Please speak."

"The Secret Tree King is not coming back. His crown needs a new master, and we also need a new Tree King. Are you interested?"

Hearing this, Hayleen could not help but look at the Ancestral Tree King with surprise in her eyes.

"Am I qualified to become the Tree King?"

"Of course, your magic strength has already reached the standard for this position." The Ancestral Tree King nodded.

Hayleen narrowed her eyes. "I am indeed interested… but there are more powerful mages than me. Why me?"

"I only said that you are qualified, not chosen," the Ancestral Tree King said calmly. "Under normal circumstances, the position of the Tree King will not be yours. What I mean is, if you want to become the Tree King, I can give you a chance. As long as you complete one objective, you will be able to inherit the crown of the Secret Tree King. The magic left behind by generations of Tree Kings is stored in there, and I believe you will be interested."

"…What do you want me to do?"

"I know that your genes mutated in your early years, fusing with your own magic power, and you entered a rare 'Warlock' branch, forming some strange innate spells. You can use a very strange method to hide your existence, and you're very good at stealth and assassination… Now that the civilization is facing an unprecedented threat, we need your ability to assassinate the Pivotal Snake's infant protected by Black Star," the Ancestral Tree King said with a deep voice.

"Are you asking me to die?" Hayleen frowned.

The Ancestral Tree King shook his head and raised his palm. A black-green liquid substance suddenly seeped out from his palm and floated in midair. Following that, the phantom of a golden leaf appeared beside him, and the two objects circled his palm.

"These are two key items to carry out the mission. One is a lethal poison that the mother tree specially synthesized to restrain her natural enemy. As long as you give it to the Pivotal Snake, it can quickly deprive the other party of their life force. Be it through injection or poisoning the food, it will be effective. This golden leaf is a child treasure derived from the mother tree, called the Leaf Concealment Robe. It can hide your tracks on all levels and enhance your stealth ability."

Hayleen's expression changed, and she took the two items hesitantly.

Seeing this, the Ancestral Tree King said indifferently, "The growth of the Pivotal Snake is very fast, and the mother tree's perception of it is becoming clearer. Follow its guidance and you will be able to find its traces. As long as you can kill the Pivotal Snake, you will be the hero of the civilization. When you return, this tree crown will be yours!"

Hayleen played with the two items for a while and finally nodded.

"…I can try."

Chapter 1430: Harrison's Determination

In a desolate universe belt in the explored universe.

The lurkers of the Star Alliance were paying attention to the progress of the battle on the news and were somewhat dissatisfied with the current situation.

"The three Universal Civilizations managed to repel the World Tree's first wave of invasion, and also managed to stabilize the situation despite the sudden chaos. As expected of the three Universal Civilizations, they're not that easy to deal with."

"The World Tree's attacks are a little weak… No, I should say that the three Universal Civilizations' resistance is too strong."

They had leaked the information because they wanted to see the World Tree invade and bring despair to the three Universal Civilizations. However, the current situation was far from their expectations.

"The good news is that although the progress of the World Tree devouring the territory is slow, it will eventually cause the three Universal Civilizations to fall into a hopeless situation with no chance of turning the tables."

"That's right. The resistance of the three Universal Civilizations will gradually weaken and die."

"I hope to see that day before my life ends."

The members of the Star Alliance calmed down and gathered their confidence.

In their eyes, this was a long-term war that might last for decades or even centuries. They decided to wait patiently. No matter how long it took, they had to witness the three Universal Civilizations' defeat.

...

Under the harassment of the World Tree's full invasion, the lives of the galactic residents were extremely tough. Half a year passed in the flames of war.

The World Tree had launched a large-scale invasion of the various Star Fields on more than one occasion, and the three Universal Civilizations had been resisting nonstop. Both sides had fought back and forth for more than half a year, and hundreds of thousands of battles of various sizes had erupted in the cold universe.

The strategic command center calculated the losses. The total area of the planets lost and swallowed by the World Tree was about three and a half Star Systems. Compared to the Star Fields that had hundreds of Star Systems, this loss was not much. There were more than ten Star Fields in the explored universe, and the planets that the World Tree had taken away were just a drop in the ocean.

According to this trend, the World Tree theoretically needed hundreds or thousands of years to defeat the Galactic Alliance Army and devour the entire explored universe.

However, the three Universal Civilizations would not relax because of this. They would fight for every inch of land. The players followed the fleets to fight the invaders, and their experience quickly accumulated. The number of players who stepped into the Calamity Grade increased.

On the other hand, Karlot, Evans, and the other new Beyond Grade As were also rushing around the battlefields. They did not usually have so many combat opportunities, so their strength was growing rapidly.

Han Xiao was always guarding the shallow layer dimensions alone. In the past half a year, the World Tree Blessed Races had invaded seventeen times, big and small. They all either got killed or fled, unable to shake the secondary dimension defense line that he was guarding.

Other than that, Han Xiao had been focused on cultivating the Pivotal Snake, trying to find a way to make it grow and mate with the secondary dimensions to produce an embryo.

Originally, he did not have much hope, the Pivotal Snake infant was a baby after all. Reproduction was a pressure that it should not bear at its age.

However, what Han Xiao did not expect was that this experiment actually succeeded. Not only did the Pivotal Snake infant stick it up, but it was also very strong. It eagerly destroyed three secondary dimensions that gave birth to ignorant consciousness, leaving behind three embryos.

However, after studying the 'snake p*rno' that was specially recorded, Han Xiao also found the reason.

Due to the pursuit of the World Tree and the dangers of the secondary dimension environment, the life of the Pivotal Snake was extremely difficult. Therefore, mating as soon as possible and giving birth to offspring might be an instinct carved into their genes. Their reproductive ability was naturally mature, and they did not need to wait until they reached adulthood to give birth.

With the three embryos, he had finally opened the door to the breeder job. Han Xiao had spent most of his time on this, making the Stockman Realmless King bleed.

However, he did not turn the Pivotal Snake infant into a Virtual Life Form because of this. He planned to wait for the embryos to mature. After he had the second and third Pivotal Snake, he planned to try this.

On this day, Han Xiao received news from Oathkeeper and Kasuyi. They planned to visit him together, so he invited them to visit the base.

In the circular corridor of the observatory, three people walked slowly side by side, chatting. The dazzling aurora outside the window left mottled shadows on the three of them.

Han Xiao smiled and said, "How do you have time to visit me today? How's the battle in the main universe?"

"The Galactic Alliance Army has repelled another wave of the World Tree invasion. We can take a break, so we came to see you." Kasuyi smiled.

"What about him?" Han Xiao turned to Oathkeeper. "When did you guys get together?"

"Are you even going to care about who I make friends with? Such a great superior," Oathkeeper said with his hands behind his back.

"What are you talking about? I'm just afraid that you'll be led astray by Kasuyi. He's a veteran two-faced actor." Han Xiao snorted.

"You have no right to say that about me." Kasuyi inwardly rolled his eyes.

The three chatted for a while before getting down to business.

"Speaking of which, some of the Beyond Grade As have died in this battle. When do you plan to revive them?"

Han Xiao shook his head. "Not at the moment. Although my authority is high, I will have to spend two to three months in the Sanctum. If I don't stay here, it will be easy for accidents to happen. Protecting the Pivotal Snake is more important now, so I can't leave yet."

Oathkeeper nodded and suddenly changed the topic. "When the war is over, I will leave the explored universe. I will leave the Holy Accord to you."

Han Xiao was stunned.

What are you doing? What enmity do we have? Why are you suddenly sticking a flag in my face? You are making me panic!

At this moment, Kasuyi smiled and said, "Me too. After this battle, I'll leave with him."

What? Are the two of you eloping?

Han Xiao had a strange expression.

"This is what you came to talk to me about today? What are you doing? Why do you want to leave when everything is alright?"

Kasuyi shrugged. "It's just a long journey. Although it's convenient to stay in the galactic society, this is just a corner of the world. The universe is so big, I want to take a look."

…So capable? The Underworld is huge too. Do you want to take a look?

Han Xiao criticized inwardly.

"You can go if you want to. It's not like I won't let you go. Or do you want to see if I will make you stay?"

Oathkeeper said, "That's not the case. The unexplored universe is filled with unknown dangers. We came to inform you in advance. We hope that every time you enter the Sanctum, you will use Revive on us. If we are still alive, there will naturally be no effect. If we unfortunately die and no news is sent back, you will be able to revive us."

"That's it? So, you guys are going out to have fun, and you want me to back you up at home?" Han Xiao said.

"That's about it." Kasuyi was not embarrassed at all.

Han Xiao was speechless. He waved his hand and said, "Alright, I'll remember this… but aren't you guys talking too early? The war is not over yet. Didn't you hear the analysis of the Military Strategy Department? They predicted that this war would take another 200 to 500 years under normal circumstances."

Kasuyi laughed. "That's for the average person to see. How can we, the upper echelons, not know? As long as your Pivotal Snake matures, it will be time for us to officially counterattack. It won't take that long."

"That's hard to say." Han Xiao shook his head and said, "The Pivotal Snake is similar to most creatures. It has six stages of growth, namely the embryo stage, infancy, childhood, adolescence, adulthood, and old age. Although the Pivotal Snake infant is growing quickly, it has only been less than a year since it broke out of its shell. At most, it is still in the infant stage, and it is still too far from adulthood."

"No matter what, the Pivotal Snake won't take a few hundred years to reach adulthood. I estimate that it will take at most ten to thirty years," Oathkeeper concluded.

"That isn't short." Han Xiao spread out his hands. "Therefore, the expeditionary army still has to continue moving. We have to search for the World Tree's main body together. Now that we know each other's strengths, we don't have to worry about leaking information. The expeditionary army doesn't have to be as secretive as before."

Kasuyi suddenly thought of something and said, "By the way, is there someone called Harrison among your subordinates?"

"You know him?" Han Xiao was surprised.

"I went to reinforce a battlefield not too far away from Planet Aquamarine's refuge planet, so after the battle, I went to Floating Dragon to take a look. Ames was not at home, and her manager, Jenny, received me. She knows about our relationship and wanted me to pass you a message."

"What is it?" Han Xiao was curious.

"She said she's pregnant." Kasuyi's tone was playful.

"F*ck!" Han Xiao was shocked. "It's not mine! I've never mated with her! Don't talk nonsense!"

"What are you thinking?" Kasuyi raised his brows. "She said the child's father is Harrison, not you. Why are you so agitated?"

"Phew, that's good… Can you finish your sentence in one breath next time?"

Han Xiao heaved a sigh of relief.

If Ames misunderstood that he had something going on with her sister, things would get interesting…

Kasuyi sized him up from head to toe and laughed. "How can a Transcendent be afraid of a mere Ames?"

"What do you mean scared? What do you know? No matter how strong you are, strength is not used to intimidate your family. This is called protecting the harmony of your family." Han Xiao said with disdain.

Kasuyi did not comment and continued, "Anyway, Jenny told me to tell you that she hopes you can persuade Harrison to give up his position in the expeditionary army and not take the risk again. She doesn't want her child to lose his father the moment he's born."

Hearing this, Han Xiao also stopped joking and told Phillip to check on Harrison's current situation.

He did not have the time to dig into his subordinates' privacy, and he only found out about this today. In the past, he only knew that the two of them had some ambiguous relationship, but he did not confirm their relationship. After some investigation, he realized that the two of them had only officially gotten together half a year ago.

In the past decade or so, Harrison had been participating in the expedition in the secondary dimension and rarely contacted Jenny. He had originally thought that he would not be able to take care of her feelings, but Jenny did not know if it was because no one wanted her or because she was old and did not want to be alone anymore. Not only did she not have any complaints about this, but her feelings for Harrison also grew deeper instead.

More than half a year ago, the expeditionary army outpost was breached by the World Tree Blessed Race, and the expeditionary army suffered heavy losses. Harrison escaped with his life, and when the expeditionary army reassembled, he finally had the time to return to the main universe. He had escaped death, and Jenny was burning with passion. The two of them finally did it, and the long-distance relationship had come to fruition. They seemed to have made up their mind to reproduce, and they did not take any safety measures.

A month ago, Harrison returned to the expeditionary army and left Jenny's side.

Han Xiao looked at the file and said, "No one seems to have recruited him. He returned to the expedition army voluntarily."

Because of the Pivotal Snake, Han Xiao did not continue to force Harrison to participate in the subsequent expedition. Now, he realized that it was Harrison's own doing.

"Why is this guy so proactive?"

Han Xiao was curious. Using the Realmless King as a transit station, he contacted Harrison, who had been branded.

A few seconds later, the call connected.

"Your Excellency Black Star."

Harrison's remote projection appeared and greeted Han Xiao respectfully.

"There's no need to be so polite. It's like this. Jenny is pregnant, and she told me to persuade you not to take the risk with the expeditionary army. Furthermore, you're not the only one in the army. How about it? Do you want to go back?" Han Xiao went straight to the point.

Harrison shook his head. "I appreciate her kindness, but I won't go back."

"I noticed that you joined the expedition willingly. What were you thinking?" Han Xiao asked.

Harrison was silent for a moment before slowly saying,

"When I was on Floating Dragon Island, I came into contact with many refugees. Do you know their current state? They live in panic every day. Many of them can't take the pressure and choose to free themselves, while those who are alive fear the unknown tomorrow. No one knows if they will one day become the target of the World Tree invasion. New religions are popular, and countless people are looking for comfort. Everyone is praying for the war to end soon.

You said that my luck is very good, and it's very suitable for me to find things. I don't know if it's true, but I hope you're right. I hope that this illusory luck will be of use and contribute to the end of the war as soon as possible."

Han Xiao raised his brows and chuckled.

"Not bad, you've made me feel a little respect for you… However, you should know that we have a very high chance of winning now that the Pivotal Snake is in our hands. The expeditionary army is no longer the only way, and it might not be of any use. You're not the only one in the army, and your actions might just be a waste of effort and a risk to your life. Why not go back and accompany your unborn child?"

Harrison shook his head. "I don't want to enjoy myself under your protection for these reasons. My colleagues are here, and I don't want to run away. Please don't persuade me anymore. I've made up my mind."

"Alright, I won't persuade you then. Be careful." Han Xiao nodded.

"…If possible, please tell Jenny that I love her."

Little brother, do you know that the moment you say this, your death omen is flashing?

"Tell her yourself. Who do you think I am? Your mouthpiece?"

Han Xiao clicked his tongue and hung up before Harrison could reply.

Little brother, don't thank me. I'm helping you pull out the flag to save your life!

Kasuyi listened to the whole conversation from the side and sighed. "You have a good officer."

"He wasn't like this in the past. He was at most a curious child, but now it seems like he's already an adult."

Han Xiao paused and smiled.

"This person might be a little stupid, but the world needs some idiots like him. Maybe he can really give me a surprise."

Chapter 1431: Rescue and Waiting For A Miracle

More than ten refugee transport ships were speeding in the planetary space, and there was a World Tree fleet chasing after them.

The atmosphere in the cabin of the carrier was tense. Many refugees were panicking, especially the ship that was the most heavily damaged, White Mountain. You could almost see the word 'despair' written on the refugees' faces.

"The reinforcements haven't arrived yet… If this continues, we'll be caught."

The captain of White Mountain was sweating profusely as he stared at the ship inspection report on the virtual screen. On the three-dimensional virtual model of White Mountain, the functional modules of the ship were all red, showing malfunction issues. The entire ship was on the verge of collapse, and one-quarter of the 28 propulsion engines were damaged. The power of the energy core had also decreased to 74%.

Because some areas were frequently invaded by the World Tree and became dangerous areas, some of the refugee planets were no longer safe. The galactic alliance army formed a transport team to migrate the refugees in these areas, and this small fleet carried this mission to transport some refugees.

However, halfway through the journey, they happened to meet the World Tree fleet that was hiding in their territory. An encounter broke out, and the smaller fleet was wiped out. Most of the transport ships were destroyed on the spot, and the remaining ships fled in panic, still being chased by the World Tree fleet.

As for the White Mountain transport ship, it was the most damaged among all the existing starships. Its modules were malfunctioning, and its speed gradually decreased, slowing down the entire fleet.

"At most, at most ten minutes, the engine will shut down. There's a desolate planet with a serial number in front of us. Should we land?"

The vice commander's trembling voice sounded. The captain of White Mountain clenched his fists and hesitated.

If they were forced to land, the people on the entire ship would have no way to escape. They could only let the guards on the ship hide on the planet with the refugees and wait for reinforcements.

The suggestions of the other captains came through the communication channel.

"White Mountain, land. Your ship is no longer able to keep up with the speed of the main fleet. We can't slow down and wait for you."

"You will be alone sooner or later. Instead of being paralyzed in space, it's better to hide on the planet. At least there's a chance of survival."

"Leave the White Mountain behind and buy us some time to save more refugees."

Some stood on the side of rational analysis, while others made blatant requests, trying to persuade the White Mountain to stay.

"I understand…"

The captain of White Mountain had a helpless look on his face.

He understood that it would be better for them to stay behind and stall for time for the refugees on the other ships.

Even so, he felt very guilty. In the report, this batch of refugees was just a cold number, but they were all alive at the moment. Using his own ship of refugees to help more refugees might be in line with the calculation of benefits, but he could not bear to do it logically. These refugees were not soldiers, and they had no intention of sacrificing themselves. Furthermore, he could not possibly make this decision after discussing it with the refugees, or it would most likely cause a mutiny. He could only silently lead them to stay behind to cover their retreat while others still had hope and believed in the captain. This made him feel very uncomfortable.

Just as he was trapped in a dilemma, the desolate planet appeared in front of the transport fleet. The eyes of the many captains immediately lit up, and they saw a small armed fleet without a symbol docked on the surface of the planet. Only when they got close did the radar detect the presence of the other party.

"There's actually a fleet lying in ambush here? They don't look like they're from the World Tree."

"Are they our reinforcements? Forget it, no matter who they are, they're all part of the galactic society."

"Quick, contact the other party and send a signal!"

All of a sudden, the captains were overjoyed. They thought that reinforcements had arrived and hurriedly sent out a request for help.

On the other side, Pangon and the others, who were resting on this desolate planet, started discussing.

"This seems to be an escaping refugee fleet. The World Tree fleet is chasing after them."

"They're asking us for help. What should we do? Should we help?"

"Don't help. The lives of the galactic residents under the three Universal Civilizations have nothing to do with us. Let's go, don't involve ourselves in their affairs."

Everyone quickly exchanged their opinions and reached a consensus.

This group of avengers was not on the side of the three Universal Civilizations. Even if the World Tree invaded completely, it would have nothing to do with them. It would be extremely benevolent of them not to add insult to injury.

Pangon was silent for a while before speaking.

"In that case, reject all their contact requests and leave immediately."

The captains of the transport fleet were looking forward to the reply of this unfamiliar armed fleet, but all their communication requests were useless.

The next moment, their expressions changed. This unfamiliar armed fleet rose into the sky and ignored the distress signal, heading in another direction. It was obvious that they were heading away, meaning they did not want to provide support.

"They're gone, not our reinforcements."

"Looks like I can't count on this group…"

The many captains' hopes were dashed.

Seeing that there was no turning point, the captain of White Mountain gritted his teeth and finally made up his mind.

"Attention all units. Separate the ship's cargo hold, load all the crew, and carry out orbital suppression. Set up the process of turning back to face the attack. Cover the departure of the brothers."

Hearing this, everyone's expression turned solemn. They knew that the White Mountain had chosen to sacrifice.

Although they hoped that would be the case, they were not too happy when it actually happened.

Very soon, the group split up. The majority of the troops continued to flee into the distance, while White Mountain slowed down and left the troops. It turned around and flew toward the desolate planet. It looked like a lone stream of light in a sea of shooting stars.

In outer space, White Mountain quickly completed its transformation. The thick armor shell was no longer locked onto each other, and mechanical parts started moving one after another. The entire carrier arched like a shrimp, and the cabin on its abdomen separated, turning into an iron-gray escape ship. Its body shrunk a lot, and it had practically no armaments as it descended toward the planet.

As for the spaceships that remained in place, they were like a hollow armor shell that operated on its own. The cannons on the spaceships fired fiercely toward the back, trying to stop the World Tree fleet that was gradually approaching.

Bang!

The escape ship landed heavily on the planet's surface, creating a crater.

All the hatches opened simultaneously, and the refugees who had been forced to change their life support equipment rushed out of the cabin. They looked up at the sky with despair and panic in their eyes.

The World Tree fleet had already arrived in outer space, and a round of fire destroyed the armor shell that they had left in outer space. It slowly descended and expanded before everyone's eyes like a shadow.

"Why did you stop?!"

"Why are you landing here? You've caused us to be surrounded!"

The refugees were in an uproar. They glared at the guards beside them with hatred and anger. Without their knowledge, the captain had ordered the spaceship to land, turning their chance of escape into zero.

"Everyone, listen up. Split up with the ship's warriors."

The captain of the White Mountain did not explain. Now was not the time to say more. He could only give the order with a stern face.

He knew that everyone's chances of survival were close to zero after being forced to surrender, but he still wanted to make a final effort and hide with the refugees.

However, the next moment, when he saw the actions of the World Tree battleships clearly, he finally fell into despair. He saw that the cannons of the World Tree fleet were aimed at the planet's surface. They were planning to save time and cleanse the planet.

"I'm dead for sure… However, letting the World Tree fleet shoot here for a few rounds would delay them. I've fulfilled my mission…"

The captain of the White Mountain clenched his fists tightly. His expression changed rapidly. He was both unwilling yet relieved.

However, just as the people raised their heads and looked at the Planetary Obliteration Cannon that destroyed them with fear, a bright light suddenly shot from another direction in the starry sky and penetrated several World Tree battleships, blowing them up like fireworks.

Everyone looked over in shock, only to see a shooting star covered in thick flames rapidly approaching. Powerful Pugilist flames shot out like heavy cannons, bombarding the World Tree fleet one after another, blowing the battleships into pieces.

Behind Pangon was the armed fleet that had just left. In the blink of an eye, they had destroyed the World Tree fleet.

The battle did not last long. Under the watchful eyes of the crew of the White Mountain, Pangon led the Avengers fleet and quickly wiped out all the enemy spaceships in the sky. The huge World Tree fleet was only left with wreckage and parts floating in outer space.

This wave of escape from death made many refugees unable to control their emotions, and the crowd cheered wildly.

The captain of the White Mountain seemed to have woken up from a dream. He hurriedly asked someone to contact this armed fleet to express his gratitude. However, the other party did not reply to him even after they had finished fighting the World Tree fleet. It was as if they had only done him a small favor and did not even bother to clean up the battlefield.

"These obviously are not the people of the Galactic Alliance Army. What kind of army is this…"

The captain of White Mountain looked at the departing Avengers and mumbled to himself.

At this time, Pangon returned to the main ship. His other comrades surrounded him with strange expressions.

"You're really something. You promised not to get involved in the war, but you suddenly made us turn around and fight."

"If we are targeted by the World Tree because of this battle, it will be troublesome. It will not be beneficial for us to accumulate our strength."

"Whose side are you on?"

The attitude of the few of them was as though they were interrogating him.

Pangon did not mind and waved his hand expressionlessly. "I've changed my mind. Although we won't take the initiative to participate in the war, if we encounter something like this again in the future, we'll save them if we can. Our target of revenge is the regime of the three Universal Civilizations, and the ordinary galactic residents have no grudges with us."

"This is exposing our existence," one of his comrades said with dissatisfaction.

"To Black Star, our existence is not a secret to begin with. If we cause any adverse effects to the war, he can tell the three Universal Civilizations about us at any time. After all, we have never been on the same side." Pangon paused for a moment before continuing, "Furthermore, more than half of the galactic society has guessed that the World Tree's full invasion is because a traitor leaked the information. Do you think Black Star won't suspect us?"

Everyone was stunned.

"In his eyes, we have sufficient motive to do so. If we don't express our goodwill and let Black Star think that we did it, even if we don't participate in the war, we can't stay out of it," Pangon explained.

Hearing this, the few of them looked at each other, slightly shaken.

"You're clearly just a Pugilist, but why do we feel that what you say makes sense every time you trick us?"

In a certain place in the secondary dimension.

A spatial rift opened, and Hayleen flew out from within.

Under the enhancement of her special talent spell and the Leaf Cloak, her current state was almost 'outside the Three Realms and not within the Five Elements'. She could not be observed normally.

"The whereabouts of the Pivotal Snake are mysterious. The mother tree only has a rough direction and range, and there's no clear location. What should I do…"

Hayleen was troubled.

After accepting the mission of the Ancestral Tree King, she had been searching for information about the appearance of the Pivotal Snake for the past half a year, but she had never found an opportunity to assassinate it.

Furthermore, it seemed like Black Star had always been by the side of the Pivotal Snake. To her, that was the most dangerous place in the universe. She held onto the principle of not taking risks if she could and never dared to go near it.

After thinking about it, the only feasible method that Hayleen could think of was to add a 'snake-killing agent' made by the mother tree to some secondary dimensions where the Pivotal Snake often appeared. Then, they would wait patiently. If the Hub Serpent ate one of the secondary dimensions, it would be poisoned.

Although this method was very random, she did not have a better idea for the time being. After all, she could not control the source of food for the Pivotal Snake, so she could only spread her net and try her luck.

The only advantage of this method was that it was safer, and she did not have to take the risk of being exposed to get close to Black Star, giving her a lot of opportunities to test her luck.

Hayleen raised her hand, and a dark green liquid appeared. It was the 'Snake-killing agent' that the Ancestral Tree King had given her.

With a flick of her finger, a small drop of dark green liquid separated and fused into the ground of this secondary dimension.

"I hope this method works…"

Hayleen muttered to herself, not knowing how to proceed.

Chapter 1432: Reverse Halo

An expedition fleet cruised through the secondary dimensions, passing through space cracks.

The strange scenery outside the window flashed past Harrison's eyes one after another. He focused on the star map, and the coordinates of the secondary dimensions lit up one after another, drawing the trajectory of the fleet. Behind him, the other crew members did their jobs.

The aide-de-camp stood at the side, pointed at the star map, and said softly, "Following this route, we will cut into the area controlled by the World Tree. Although His Excellency Black Star killed the World Tree's Blessed Race and caused a gap in their internal defenses, it is still very dangerous for us to go deeper."

"I know, but only by going deep into the enemy's territory will we be able to find the World Tree's main body. Without risking our lives, how can we possibly find anything?" Harrison replied without hesitation.

The aide-de-camp pursed his lips and could not help but say, "Sir, why are you working so hard? With your relationship with His Excellency Black Star…"

"Alright, don't say such things anymore. You don't have to persuade me."

Harrison did not even look up.

The aide-de-camp smiled bitterly.

Do you think I care about you? The main thing is that if you shrink back, we can use your relationship to go back and rest…

The aide-de-camp said with resignation, "I think we'll give free kills."

"If you have the time to worry, you might as well pray that we're safe and sound," Harrison replied casually.

"If praying is useful, what's the point of having an army?"

The aide-de-camp muttered softly.

Harrison glanced at him and was about to say something when he suddenly frowned and looked out of the window.

"Something's wrong…"

"What's wrong?" The aide-de-camp was curious.

"I feel uneasy," Harrison whispered.

"…Quick! Weapon charge, prepare for battle!"

The aide-de-camp and the rest of the crew panicked. They immediately yelled and ordered the fleet to enter combat mode.

They had no choice but to take it seriously. Last time, when Harrison was feeling uneasy, the expeditionary army outpost was gone. In their eyes, Harrison was a jinx. If he had any headache or fever, it meant that they were going to suffer together.

Harrison looked at the radar screen vigilantly, but there was no abnormal reaction. The uneasiness in his heart gradually disappeared, and his brows relaxed.

"Could it be an illusion…"

Harrison was a little confused, but he shook his head. Since he did not discover anything, he was not sure if his senses had gone wrong.

"Sir, don't scare us!"

Hearing this, everyone secretly heaved a sigh of relief, their faces filled with helplessness. They thought it was his bad taste.

The expedition fleet quickly disappeared along the space crack. After they left, a translucent figure appeared in this secondary dimension. It was Hayleen.

"The exploration team of the three Universal Civilizations…"

Hayleen looked in the direction where the fleet disappeared. Her expression changed a few times, but she did not attack in the end.

During this time, she had been searching for suitable secondary dimensions to add the snake-killing agent. Occasionally, she would meet the troops of the three Universal Civilizations.

As the World Tree currently did not need to steal intelligence, she did not make a move. After all, there were other World Tree Blessed Races to deal with these people, and she did not want to alert them and expose herself. Her mission was more important.

However, the expeditionary army was also useful to her. According to the routes of some fleets, together with the mother tree's reaction to the Pivotal Snake, Hayleen had screened out areas that might be frequented by the Pivotal Snake during this period, as well as some secondary dimensions that might be chosen by the Pivotal Snake as food. All of them were injected with the snake-killing agents.

This time was no exception. Hayleen silently activated her space magic, found the traces of Harrison's fleet, and flew toward their direction. Very soon, she arrived at a strange, rocky secondary dimension. The violent radiation dust storm turned into tornadoes, and there was no sign of life in the entire dimension.

"This place isn't bad."

Hayleen nodded. As far as she knew, this type of secondary dimension that did not give birth to life but had different substances was the favorite food for the Pivotal Snake. The pure energy type secondary dimension was not liked by it. Maybe it was because of the texture, after all, those with substances were very crispy.

She popped out the snake-killing agent and watched it integrate into the secondary dimension. Only then did she use a teleportation spell to leave and find her next target.

Half a month later.

The Realmless King led the Pivotal Snake through the secondary dimension world. The dense mechanical army protected them like a black cloud.

As they passed by the secondary dimensions, everyone would stop for a while to observe the reaction of the Pivotal Snake. If the Pivotal Snake did not start eating, they would continue to go to the next place.

Although all secondary dimensions were food, the Pivotal Snake would not stuff all of them into its mouth. After all, its appetite was limited, and it needed time to digest after eating.

As long as it was not extremely hungry, the Pivotal Snake would only start to eat when it met a secondary dimension that suited its taste. As the saying went, it was easy to go from frugal to extravagant, but it was difficult to go from extravagant to frugal. It did not need to find its own food, so its taste was getting more and more picky.

After a while, they arrived at a strange, rocky secondary dimension. The Pivotal Snake immediately started twisting and turning. It took a fancy to this food, and without caring about the others, it started to feast on it. The white fog on its body spread out, and everywhere it passed, the matter was ground and swallowed.

Seeing this, the Realmless King and the mechanical army retreated to the side and did not disturb the Pivotal Snake's meal.

Seeing that the Pivotal Snake was eating happily, the Realmless King sighed in his heart.

"It's getting more and more troublesome."

The Realmless King yielded to Han Xiao's tyrannical power and unwillingly became the stockman of the Pivotal Snake. Even though his lifespan was almost infinite, he felt like his life had given him a heavy blow when he thought about the fact that he would still have to rear the Pivotal Snake for decades. His b*lls hurt so bad… although he did not have this part.

The most terrifying thing was that Black Star still had three embryos. When all of them were hatched, wouldn't it be four times the happiness for this stockman?

Furthermore, Black Star would definitely force them to give birth to little snakes. One begets two, two begets three, and three begets all things; there would be unlimited offspring…

Damn it! When will these days end?!

The Realmless King felt as if he could see his own bitter future, and he shuddered.

Just as he was feeling sad for his fate, the Pivotal Snake that was eating suddenly stopped and twisted violently, collapsing mountains one after another. It looked in extreme pain as if someone had suddenly stuffed a spoon of mustard into its mouth while eating.

"What's going on?"

The Realmless King was shocked, and he hurriedly came forward to control the Pivotal Snake. The mechanical troops also quickly surrounded it.

However, the Pivotal Snake that was restrained by everyone was still struggling with all its might, like a lively fish being pressed onto a chopping board.

Psionic Prime quickly scanned the vital signs of the Pivotal Snake and said coldly, "Something's not right. The life force of the Pivotal Snake is rapidly withering, and some unknown compound has already spread in its body. It seems to be a genetic toxin specifically targeted at it, and it has already caused irreversible damage. The damage is still increasing, so it should have been plotted against!"

"There are enemies nearby?" The Realmless King was shocked. He immediately released all his senses, but he did not discover anything.

"Our radar can't find him either. I've already summoned the Lord. He'll be here soon."

The moment Psionic Prime finished speaking, a light appeared beside him. It was Han Xiao.

"What's going on?"

Han Xiao immediately noticed the abnormal situation of the Pivotal Snake. His expression changed slightly, and without hesitation, he poked the Pivotal Snake. The combat information immediately popped up on the interface.

This time, Psionic Prime and the other Mechanical Oracles walked up to him and said with guilt, "We are sorry, we fell into the enemy's trap unknowingly. This is our negligence. Please punish us…"

"Alright, take your leave."

Han Xiao did not have the time to care about them. He waved his hands and looked at the interface.

At this time, in the status bar of the Pivotal Snake, there was a negative status of [Heavy Poisoning]. It was introduced as the genetic toxin specially concocted by the World Tree, and it was only targeted at the Pivotal Snake Race. Once it entered the body, it would cause the gene sequence to shatter. It was completely irreversible, causing the Pivotal Snake's health to decrease at a rate of 1.5% per second, and its maximum health decreased at a rate of 0.5% per second.

He released his senses and scanned the area, but he did not sense the presence of any outsiders. He asked about the situation just now and roughly guessed how the Pivotal Snake was affected.

'"Damn, they tampered with the meal and happened to pick the correct target. What kind of luck was this…"

Han Xiao's eyes twitched.

With so many secondary dimensions and the random selection of food by the Pivotal Snake, it just had to hit the jackpot. What kind of probability was this?

Could it be that so many mascots could not slightly dilute my Heavenly Execution Grade luck?

Han Xiao thought to himself. Seeing how much health the Pivotal Snake had lost, he took out a tube of Aurora Potion and injected it into the Pivotal Snake's body. The effect was immediate, and its health immediately recovered.

However, the effect of being poisoned did not weaken. It still hung on its stats window. Although its health bar was full, the upper limit was still falling.

Seeing this, Han Xiao injected a few more shots of Aurora Potion into the Pivotal Snake. The HP regeneration was the same, but it could not get rid of the poisoned status.

"This poison is quite powerful…"

Han Xiao's eyes narrowed.

If he was given some time, he would be able to try and crack it. However, with the speed of losing HP in this poison state, it only needed 200 seconds to clear the upper limit of the Pivotal Snake's health. This amount of time was not enough.

"Alright, let's experiment with my previous idea."

Han Xiao activated [Life Transformation—Virtual] on the suffering Pivotal Snake.

Now that he had three embryos in his hands, with the cost of trial and error, he originally wanted to experiment on the newborn baby. He did not expect this Pivotal Snake to have an accident, so he might as well try this idea on it.

Streams of data flashed across the body of the Pivotal Snake, and it slowly began to turn incorporeal. Its pain also began to decrease rapidly. The World Tree's toxin targeted the biological genes. At this moment, the life form of the Pivotal Snake began to change, and it gradually became immune to the toxin effect.

During this process, because the body of the Pivotal Snake was turning incorporeal, the toxins in its body automatically came out and condensed into a drop of black-green liquid that floated in midair.

Seeing that the situation had stabilized, Han Xiao raised his hand to collect this drop of poison. He narrowed his eyes and activated [Bold Explorer] without hesitation.

"Although I'm not afraid of such methods, since you dared to send people here to do something, I can't let you escape so easily."

Chapter 1433: Going for Wool and Coming Home Shorn

At the same time, somewhere in the secondary dimension world, Hayleen was wandering around, choosing a new target.

Very soon, she arrived in a blue liquid world. She popped out the snake-killing agent and watched it dissolve in the liquid. As she worked, her thoughts drifted away.

"I wonder if the poison I planted earlier worked…"

Hayleen murmured.

She could only plant the poison everywhere, but she did not dare go back to check. If the Pivotal Snake was infected, Black Star would definitely be waiting nearby. If she went over, there might be some risk.

The only way to determine if the plan was successful was to determine the status of the Pivotal Snake based on the mother tree's reaction. If the mother tree's reaction to the Pivotal Snake weakened or disappeared, it would mean that the Pivotal Snake was dead. In that case, she would not have to check which trap the Pivotal Snake had fallen into.

Therefore, Hayleen felt that she was still in a safe situation. All she needed to do was to set up the traps. As long as the mother tree gave her feedback, she would be able to retreat.

After adding the snake-killing agent to the blue secondary dimension in front of her, Hayleen was about to turn around and leave. However, at this moment, the voice of the Ancestral Tree King suddenly came from the mental network, bringing good news.

"The mother tree's connection to the Pivot Snake is rapidly weakening. Your method should have succeeded."

"It really succeeded? So fast ‽ The chances are so low, I thought it would take at least a few years for the Pivotal Snake to choose the secondary dimension that I tampered with…"

Hayleen's eyes lit up with joy.

She had thought that she might need to spend two to three years planting snake-killing agents in enough secondary dimensions so that the Pivotal Snake would have a higher chance of falling for it. However, the plan had only started half a year ago. There were not many secondary dimensions that were injected with the poison, but the Pivotal Snake had chosen one so quickly. What kind of probability was this? What kind of luck was this ‽

In less than a year, she had successfully resolved the biggest threat to the World Tree. It was a pleasant surprise!

The Ancestral Tree King was also in a good mood. He had planned to let Hayleen carry out this mission for a long time, and had not expected it to work so quickly.

Don't ask why, but if you had to ask, it was God's will!

This was definitely the blessing of the Goddess of Luck!

"Come back. When the Mother Tree confirms that the Pivotal Snake is dead, the position of the Tree King will be yours."

"Alright, I'll go back now!"

Suppressing her excitement, Hayleen was about to open the transportation door and return.

However, just as she was about to return with excitement, the Ancestral Tree King suddenly interrupted her.

"Wait a minute, the mother tree's reaction has changed…"

"What now?"

"The mother tree's connection with the Pivot Snake has stopped declining, and it's becoming stronger instead… Strange, this is too abnormal. What happened?" The Ancestral Tree King's tone became heavy.

The stronger the World Tree's reaction to the Pivotal Snake, it signified the more mature the Pivotal Snake would be. Right now, it was only a rough perception range, and they could only accurately determine each other's location when it reached adulthood.

Just a moment ago, after the signal of the Pivotal Snake weakened for a while, it suddenly rose in reverse and quickly exceeded its previous limit, still rising.

Hayleen paused in shock.

"Why is this happening ‽"

"You didn't do anything unnecessary, did you?"

The intensity of the sense was still increasing. The Ancestral Tree King felt that something was wrong, and his tone was filled with doubt.

"Absolutely not! I've always been focused on setting traps. Even when I coincidentally met the three Universal Civilizations' fleets, I never took action!"

Hayleen was so anxious that she almost swore an oath and shared the relevant memories on the mental network.

The Ancestral Tree King quickly scanned through her experiences over the past half a year, but he did not find anything out of the ordinary. With a grave expression, he said, "There's only one explanation. Black Star used some method to save the Pivotal Snake, and he even sped up its growth…"

Before he finished his sentence, the mother tree's consciousness suddenly became agitated, as if it was feeling intense panic.

However, the sensitivity of the Pivotal Snake seemed to have broken through some kind of restriction. A large area of its detection range suddenly disappeared, turning into a precise coordinate in the blink of an eye!

The Ancestral Tree King's eyes widened in shock, and his mind went blank.

The connection between the World Tree and the Pivotal Snake was two-way. When the World Tree could accurately locate the Pivotal Snake, it meant that the Pivotal Snake had entered adulthood and could locate the precise coordinates of the World Tree.

This meant that… the mother tree's location had been exposed!

If he had not confirmed that the mother tree would not lie to him, he would have suspected that the poison that the mother tree had concocted was actually the catalyst for the maturation of the Pivotal Snake.

The Ancestral Tree King was confused.

I sent people to assassinate the Pivotal Snake. Even if she failed, they would only lose one high-level combatant. Why did it cause the Pivotal Snake to mature?

Not only did we not solve this threat, we even shortened the time it took for this hidden danger to erupt… We originally had a few decades to deal with it, but now, this little bit of buffer time is gone. We are now facing imminent danger without any mental preparations.

What should I do ‽

"How could this be…"

Hayleen was stunned as well.

Before the two of them could recover from their shock, a space crack suddenly opened in this secondary dimension. Han Xiao stepped into the void and slowly walked out.

Han Xiao looked around and quickly locked onto a seemingly empty area. It was actually where Hayleen was hiding.

"Do you want to come out yourself, or do you want me to invite you?"

Hayleen was shocked.

The series of unforeseen events had already thrown her into chaos. She did not expect Black Star to find her so quickly, and with just a glance, he had already seen through the stealth effect of the Leaf Concealment Robe and locked onto her location.

"Stop hiding. You can't escape from my senses."

Han Xiao did not wait. Beams of mechanical particles flowed along his arm and turned into a circular device, releasing an invisible force field toward Hayleen.

In the empty space, Hayleen's figure suddenly appeared and rippled.

Seeing that her position was exposed, Hayleen was shocked and hurriedly opened the transportation door to retreat.

However, at this moment, Han Xiao raised his hand and grabbed it. A mechanical disc rose from the back of his head like a crown of light, freezing the space and shattering her teleportation spell.

Following this, a bunch of Mechanical Oracles surged out from the Mechanical Force and surrounded Hayleen, but they did not attack immediately.

"Crap…"

Hayleen felt despair in her heart. The difference in strength was too great. She could not fight a Transcendent alone. She clenched her teeth and made up her mind to fight to the death.

However, at this moment, the shocked voice of the Ancestral Tree King suddenly sounded in her mind.

"Wait a minute, why is the mother tree's coordinates of the Pivot Snake on Black Star?"

Hayleen was stunned. She took a look and was shocked.

The mother tree had locked onto the Pivotal Snake coordinates, and it was Black Star… what was going on ‽

This time, Han Xiao did not make a move immediately. Instead, he looked at Hayleen with interest and said, "Your idea of ambushing the Pivotal Snake was quite good, but it's useless. I know that you have the mental network to contact each other regardless of distance. Help me send a message to the Ancestral Tree King. I already know the location of your World Tree's main body. You've already lost this battle."

"What did you do…" Hayleen could not help but ask.

"Are you referring to how I got rid of the genetic toxin you guys released?"

Han Xiao smiled. He raised his hand, and a translucent snake appeared in his palm. It was the Pivotal Snake that had been transformed into a Virtual Life Form.

The Pivotal Snake had transformed into a Virtual Life Form, and Han Xiao had instilled a large amount of data into it, nurturing it through artificial intelligence.

The result made him overjoyed. His previous idea was correct. The Pivotal Snake in the Virtual Life Form had escaped the limit of normal growth, and it could mature quickly this way. The connection between the Pivotal Snake and the World Tree in the Information Form did not disappear because of the Pivotal Snake's life form change. Both parties still had a two-way connection.

From [Bold Explorer], Han Xiao saw the World Tree's assassination plan. He originally thought that he was unlucky, but after seeing the short interaction between Hayleen and Harrison, he was a little uncertain and had a bold guess.

Maybe it was the effect of Harrison's Halo that made Hayleen choose the food of the Pivotal Snake, which indirectly led to the Pivotal Snake turning into a Virtual Life Form, maturing in advance and sensing the coordinates of the World Tree… Although it did not sound probable, Han Xiao felt that anything was possible to a protagonist-type character.

Because the Virtual Life Form was controlled by Han Xiao, he simply stored the Pivotal Snake in the Godly Stronghold and turned it into a tool. This way, even if the World Tree could lock onto the Pivotal Snake in reverse, the coordinates would only be his location. There was no way to avoid him no matter what they did.

Seeing this through the mental network, the Ancestral Tree King's face turned ashen. He immediately understood the current situation.

I'm afraid we no longer have the chance to remove the threat of the Pivotal Snake…

At this time, Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and said to Hayleen,

"Although you're here to assassinate the Pivotal Snake, you did me a favor. You could be considered a hero of the three Universal Civilizations. I'll make an exception and give you a chance to live."

"…What are you going to do?"

"I will seal you up. Maybe after we get rid of the World Tree, you would still have a chance to survive. You have nowhere to run now, so you might as well accept the seal. Don't make me waste my energy." Han Xiao raised his brows.

"I…"

Hayleen sounded hesitant as if she was conflicted.

However, the next moment, she suddenly jumped up and retreated. A series of instantaneous spells were thrown out, creating a path in the mechanical army.

However, before she could do anything, the Mechanical Oracles around her attacked together and suppressed Hayleen instantly. Han Xiao moved closer to Hayleen and grabbed her neck with one hand.

"Looks like you won't give up until you see your coffin."

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and put strength in his hand to crush her protective spell, and threw her toward the Mechanical Oracles.

An intense battle immediately broke out, but there was no suspense in the battle. The one-sided battle did not last long. Hayleen, who was at the end of her rope, was crushed by the group of Mechanical Oracles until she was almost paralyzed.

Seeing this, Han Xiao floated in front of her, pressed down on her head, and activated his ability.

Not long after, the Spacetime Amber took form, and Hayleen's sorrowful and humiliated expression froze.

"Congratulations to the Lord for catching the culprit. Nothing in this world can hide from your eyes," Psionic Prime said.

"Alright, you're not suitable for flattery. Go back."

Han Xiao waved his hands and felt relieved.

If not for the World Tree's plot, he would not have been able to make up his mind to experiment on the Pivotal Snake so quickly. The World Tree was just throwing stones at its own feet.

"Since the coordinates are already in my hands, I'll call Harrison back… Speaking of which, I think I've taken advantage of his halo."

Han Xiao thought about it and called the Realmless King to act as a transit station to contact Harrison.

Before long, Harrison's remote projection appeared.

"Your Excellency Black Star, what can I do for you?"

"Don't participate in the expedition. Come back."

Harrison was a little surprised. "Huh? Didn't we talk about this before? I remember you promised not to persuade me. I've decided to contribute to the galactic society…"

Before he could finish, Han Xiao interrupted him and smiled.

"Things are different now. The situation has changed. I have already grasped the exact coordinates of the World Tree's main body and no longer need the expeditionary army. You don't have to take the unnecessary risk."

Harrison was stunned. "Your Excellency Black Star, are you trying to trick me into going back? How long has it been?"

Han Xiao smiled and said, "It's all thanks to your luck this time. If not for you, I might not have been able to determine the location of the World Tree so quickly. Strictly speaking, part of the credit belongs to you. You've already made a huge contribution to ending this war, so you can leave now. It's decided. I'll teleport over later and bring you back."

With that, he hung up.

On the other side, Harrison scratched his head in confusion.

No, what did I do? How did I make such a huge contribution? Why don't I know about it ‽

...

Chapter 1434: The Horn of Counterattack

Secondary Dimension World, World Tree Civilization Control Area, Tree King Palace.

The moment his mental connection with Hayleen was cut off, and the Ancestral Tree King knew that she had been sealed by Black Star. He closed his eyes silently with a gloomy expression.

"What should we do?" The Fortitude Tree King looked over and asked with a complicated tone.

The Ancestral Tree King pressed his brows as his expression changed. There was frustration, disappointment, and regret.

After a moment of silence, he opened his eyes again and spoke with a helpless and weak expression.

"…Retract all the troops outside and return to the secondary dimensional zone. All troops are to protect the mother tree."

"Are we giving up on the invasion?"

"Now is not the time to consider how to invade the enemy. It's time to guard against the enemy's counterattack."

The Ancestral Tree King's expression was grave, and a hint of unwillingness flashed through his eyes.

The coordinates of the mother tree's main body had been exposed. If it had been an ordinary opponent, the World Tree Civilization would not have been so flustered. They could have sealed the dimension and deployed a large number of troops to guard it. Even if the enemy wanted to attack the mother tree's main body, they would have to cross countless lines of defense.

However, the three Universal Civilizations happened to be able to counter this tactic. The Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device could ignore any space blockade and pass through any defensive line. Once the coordinates of the mother tree were exposed, it would give the three Universal Civilizations a chance to raid their home.

The Ancestral Tree King did not dare take the risk and had no choice but to withdraw all his troops to protect the mother tree's main body. The attack and defense had already changed, and now it was his turn to worry about the three Universal Civilizations' invasion.

In the eyes of the Ancestral Tree King, this method was like quenching his thirst with poison. Even if he could defeat the armies of the three Universal Civilizations time and time again, the Pivotal Snake was completely controlled by Black Star and could locate the mother tree's body at any time. It was equivalent to the World Tree never having a day of peace. The Ancestral Tree King could not think of a way to turn the tables. The civilization had been growing for so long, and he did not know how long it had been since they fell into such a desperate situation.

After hunting so many civilizations, they had finally met a tough opponent.

"Is there really no other way?" the Fortitude Tree King asked softly.

"Yes, and it's very simple. As long as we kill Black Star, everything will be solved." The Ancestral Tree King was expressionless.

"…If I could kill him, I would have done so long ago." Fortitude Tree King had a bitter expression.

"Therefore, the war is no longer in our hands. The long-term strategy has already lost its executional environment. The only thing we can do now is to react accordingly."

The Ancestral Tree King's tone was bitter.

At this point, he did not know where his fate was going.

...

The order of the Tree King was transmitted to all the officers through the mental network. Regardless of whether they were shocked, panicked, or unwilling, all the officers obediently followed the order.

The World Tree fleet that had stirred up trouble within the three Universal Civilizations retreated in batches, and the army stationed outside the Flickering World also abandoned their strongholds and left using wormholes.

The sudden withdrawal of the World Tree left many reinforcements of the Galactic Alliance Army in dismay. Many people were confused and did not know what the World Tree was doing.

This information was quickly passed on and attracted the attention of the upper echelons.

In the Strategic Command of the Galactic Alliance Army, an emergency meeting was underway.

The remote projections of the three Universal Civilizations' leaders were present. They received a report from the Adviser Department and were very surprised. They attended the meeting together and listened to the military analyze the reason for the World Tree's withdrawal.

"The World Tree clearly had the initiative and could harass and devour our territory as much as they wanted, but now, it suddenly stopped invading. Not only that, even the armies outside the Flickering World border have been retracted. This situation is quite strange, and we don't know the reason. What do you guys think?"

Commander Simon's tone was grave.

Everyone present had a serious look on their faces as they stared at the virtual strategic sand table.

They would not be optimistic that the World Tree retreating was a good thing. From their perspective, there had to be a reason behind such an unreasonable action.

From the military's perspective, the World Tree was most likely going to cause trouble, but they did not know the enemy's target, so the atmosphere was rather tense, and the air was filled with anxiety.

Teny knocked on the table and said with a deep voice, "According to the calculations of the General Staff, the sudden withdrawal of the World Tree might be a ploy to mislead our judgment. An unknown large-scale military operation is brewing behind our backs, and the target is likely to be our Central Galaxy, the mother planet of the three Universal Civilizations!"

Hearing this, everyone's expression became even more serious.

"In that case, we must continue to strengthen the defenses of our mother planet! The World Tree has retreated at the edge of the storm, and the plan they have is definitely not a simple formality. If we relax, they might really succeed!"

Simon's expression was solemn, and his voice was firm.

This time, an Arcane Church's officer hesitated for a moment before saying, "Does no one think that something might have happened within the World Tree?"

The Pope turned to look at him and solemnly replied, "We cannot place our hopes on the enemy's own problems. We have to consider the worst-case scenario first."

At this moment, the President of the Federation, Louis, pondered and said, "There must be a reason for the World Tree to retreat. Could it be that the traitor secretly leaked some information to the World Tree, causing them to make a new decision?"

As soon as he said that, the expressions of all the officers turned solemn.

In the past half a year, the three Universal Civilizations had been resisting the invasion of the World Tree while investigating the traitors internally. There were many suspects, but there was no way to confirm the culprit.

Under the pressure of the enemy, the three Universal Civilizations did not dare to wantonly engage in the senseless slaughter of those suspected. The cooperation between the Galactic Alliance Army was not easy to come by, and they were also afraid of causing internal unrest by wrongly accusing their innocent allies.

Marbruce agreed. "This is also a possibility. The existence of traitors is still an unstable factor, and it's most likely to lead to all kinds of variables."

"We still have to come up with an effective method to expose the traitor," the Pope emphasized.

Just as everyone was discussing, another remote projection suddenly appeared in the conference room.

Everyone turned around and saw that it was Black Star.

"Yo, the meeting has already started. Looks like you guys didn't wait for me."

Han Xiao looked around and nodded in acknowledgement to everyone. They nodded back in return.

As one of the pillars of the war, he naturally received an invitation to the meeting. However, in order to confirm the coordinates of the mother tree that the Pivotal Snake sensed, he was delayed for a while.

"You're late," Marbruce said helplessly.

Han Xiao waved his hands.

"Don't worry about the details. What were you guys talking about?"

Simon took the initiative to explain.

"The World Tree suddenly retreated and stopped the invasion. We're guessing their motive for doing this… The most likely possibility is that the World Tree is preparing a large-scale military operation against the mother planet of the three Universal Civilizations. Also, the traitor might have leaked new information."

"Oh? Has the World Tree retreated?"

Han Xiao blinked. He only knew about this now.

He thought about it and understood the motive of the World Tree Civilization.

"Alright, don't scare yourselves. The World Tree retreated because they were afraid."

"Afraid?"

Everyone looked at each other, not understanding what Han Xiao meant.

The Pope coughed and said, "Black Star, stop joking. This is a very serious matter."

"Who has the time to joke with you?" Han Xiao clicked his tongue. "I've managed to get the Pivotal Snake to mature, and now I've grasped the precise coordinates of the World Tree's main body. The World Tree sensed this through a two-way connection. They retreated because they were afraid that we would attack them directly. They went back to defend. There's no other possibility."

"You found the location of the World Tree? Really?!"

The three of them were stunned. Suddenly, they were overjoyed but also a little terrified, afraid that this was fake news.

Everyone's body trembled, and their expressions changed drastically. They stared at Han Xiao in disbelief.

It was not until Han Xiao gave an affirmative answer that the three leaders and the officers were truly excited.

"How did you do it?!"

Marbruce hurriedly asked, and everyone looked at Han Xiao.

Seeing this, Han Xiao did not hide anything and briefly told them about Hayleen's assassination. He then emphasized that the Pivotal Snake had already unlocked its sensing ability, which made everyone excited.

Due to the existence of the Pivotal Snake, everyone had always been very confident in this war, but that was only with regards to their confidence in the long-term trend. They had originally thought that they would have to last for at least a few decades under the all-out invasion of the World Tree before the outcome could be decided, but they did not expect Black Star to solve the key problem at this stage.

This was equivalent to reducing the war losses for the galactic society for decades, allowing the officers to be freed in advance.

"Good job! This way, the initiative is in our hands!"

Marbruce clenched his fists and was overjoyed.

While he was overjoyed, he also felt a little ashamed. While they were still thinking about how to capture the traitor, Black Star had already found the key to ending the war and regained control. The two of them were on completely different levels.

Ever since the start of the war, Black Star had appeared almost every time, and now, he had given the three Universal Civilizations a chance to win. The three of them did not think it was an exaggeration to say that he was the one who led the war.

This time, Han Xiao waved his hand and said casually,

"There's no need to say anything else. The World Tree's weakness has been exposed, and it has completely fallen into a passive state. It's time for us to gather a large force to attack and completely end this enemy… The World Tree is at the end of its rope in this war!"

Upon hearing this, Simon immediately stood up with a sharp look in his eyes.

"Your Excellency Black Star is right. It's time for us to blow the horn of our counterattack!"

As soon as he said that, everyone stood up and looked at the three leaders with stern expressions.

"Please give the order!"

Seeing this, the expressions of Marbruce, Louis, and the Pope turned serious. They nodded heavily and declared solemnly,

"Good! From now on, we will make strategic adjustments. Our primary goal is no longer to defend our homeland, but to completely destroy the World Tree Civilization!"

"Understood!"

The officers responded in unison with stern expressions.

Han Xiao, who was watching from the side, smirked.

Although he and the three Universal Civilizations had the same goal of defeating the World Tree Civilization, their specific needs were different.

From the perspective of the three Universal Civilizations, the destruction of the World Tree was the most reassuring.

However, from Han Xiao's perspective… he could only say that their intentions of working together to defend against the enemies were sincere, and using each other was also sincere.

When the main conflict is resolved, the differences between me and the three Universal Civilizations will also surface. Even if these people thank me now, who knows what will happen after.

Han Xiao pondered, secretly calculating his odds.

...

As the World Tree retreated, the intense battle between the two sides stopped, causing the explored universe to suddenly become silent.

When the galactic residents were not mentally prepared, the flames of war suddenly extinguished, just like when the World Tree invaded.

The upper echelons of the three Universal Civilizations came to a consensus, and the changes in their strategy were quickly carried out. The Galactic Alliance Army no longer patrolled their territory but started to gather in the Central Galaxy.

Sensing the change in the situation, the countless galactic residents who were originally in a state of panic were stunned and confused, not knowing what to make of the situation.

There were many different opinions on the internet, and the Star Alliance Observer hiding in the desolate universe belt was confused by the withdrawal of the World Tree.

They did not know the secret of the Pivotal Snake and were still in the dark. They could only access the public information on the network, thus at this moment, they were completely confused.

"Strange, the World Tree should have been devouring the three Universal Civilizations. Why did it suddenly leave?"

In the secret base, many of the Star Alliance observers were confused.

They had leaked the information because they wanted to lead the World Tree to destroy the three Universal Civilizations. In the past half a year, the World Tree's actions had perfectly met their expectations, allowing them to watch from the side.

Originally, things were going according to their plan, and they were just enjoying the show when the World Tree suddenly slipped away. The Star Alliance observers were caught off guard.

"The World Tree definitely has its reasons for doing this. They might not be satisfied with small skirmishes and are gathering their troops, preparing to make a big fuss!"

The Observer captain analyzed for a while and concluded.

Hearing this, many members felt that it made sense, and the surprise in their hearts turned into anticipation.

At this moment, the Star Alliance's spies did not know that the World Tree Civilization, which they had placed high hopes on, was already in a dire situation.

Chapter 1435: Counterattack

The news of the turn of the battle quickly spread to the upper echelons of the Galactic Alliance Army. The allied civilizations that were originally troubled by the World Tree's invasion were pleasantly surprised. They worked together with the three Universal Civilizations to gather their forces, and the armies of the various Star Fields all flowed toward the Central Galaxy.

The fact that Han Xiao had matured the Pivotal Snake in advance was also made known to the various civilizations. Although Black Star had guided the war on more than one occasion, the impact it had on the upper echelons this time was still shocking. Everyone was originally prepared to fight hard for decades, but they suddenly realized that they did not need to suffer anymore and had the chance to achieve their task in one battle.

If the invasion of the World Tree was a disease, then Black Star had already developed a treatment to cure the illness before the health of the galactic society was greatly damaged, saving countless lives. With decades of wartime reduced, countless refugees and soldiers were saved.

Although it was a little corny, many upper echelons felt that using the word 'hero' to describe Black Star's contributions to this war was not a problem at all.

As an important part of the Galactic Alliance Army, the upper echelons of the Super Star Cluster Alliance also received this information, and they could not help but be stunned.

"I didn't expect the situation to change so quickly…"

In the conference room, the upper echelons of the Super Star Cluster gathered with complicated expressions.

More than half a year ago, Black Star had forced them to terminate the relocation plan. Although the Super Star Cluster Alliance had lowered their heads, they naturally had some grievances in their hearts. Due to the agreement between the two sides, they could only stay for the time being, but they still did not plan to give up on the relocation plan. They originally wanted to use two to three years to observe the situation, and once the situation turned bad, they could restart the relocation plan at any time.

However, they did not expect that in less than a year, the 'great situation' would be turned around by Han Xiao. The full invasion of the World Tree crumbled apart, causing the three Universal Civilizations to be free. This way, even if they wanted to migrate, they would lose the prerequisite. The current explored universe did not have a chaotic environment for them to carry out this plan. If they insisted, the three Universal Civilizations would have enough energy to deal with them.

"Sigh, we can't leave even if we want to. It's all because of Black Star. We didn't seize the opportunity." Someone was frustrated.

The Star Arc leader shook his head and said helplessly, "You're wrong. This is a blessing in disguise. If not for Black Star stopping us from carrying out this plan, we would have been in trouble."

Everyone thought about it and agreed.

No one had foreseen that in just half a year, the World Tree would be overwhelmed by Black Star. If they had really decided to migrate, they would have been screwed. This amount of time was not enough to complete the entire relocation plan, and they would not have been able to go far. At the same time, there would be no turning back for them, and they would be treated as traitors who leaked the information and become the target of public criticism. In that case, this was a blessing in disguise, and they had to thank Brother Black Star ‽

Upon realizing this, everyone shivered.

At this moment, the Star Arc Leader said, "I feel that Black Star has already anticipated this change. After all, he has always been in control of the Pivotal Snake, and the current situation is in his grasp. Back then, he came to us and insisted that we give up on migrating. Other than taking into consideration the overall situation, he might have given us a subtle reminder and used his method to help us avoid this trap."

Hearing this, the eyes of the Super Star Cluster upper echelons flickered.

The Star Arc Leader looked around, paused, and continued.

"Black Star did this not because he has any relationship with us, but because of the benefits. Just as he said, after the war ends, the conflict between the three Universal Civilizations and the Beyond Grade A Association still exists. He needs an ally with enough weight to help him expand further, so he helped us this time."

"…What a dangerous guy."

Many upper echelons of the Super Star Cluster shook their heads and sighed at Black Star's farsightedness.

While they were still focused on the war, Black Star had already begun to plan for the post-war situation. What this revealed was Black Star's firm confidence in this war. He believed more than anyone that the Galactic Society would be able to obtain the final victory… because the key to ending the war was in his hands.

On the other side, when the Galactic Alliance Army was gathering, the Beyond Grade A Association also heard about the change in the situation from Han Xiao and was shocked.

"Beautifully done, Black Star. You've captured the lifeblood of the World Tree!"

In the conference room on the main planet of the association, this piece of good news made many Beyond Grade As excited.

They had been rushing to reinforce everywhere for more than half a year, and they could only deal with the invaders passively. They had no room to fight back, and they were all holding their anger in.

Ever since the start of the war, only the World Tree had been able to invade, and now, they could finally counterattack. Most of the Beyond Grade As present were excited and eager to give it a try. They looked at Han Xiao with admiration and appreciation.

Han Xiao knocked on the table and said, "I have already provided the coordinates of the World Tree's main body to the three Universal Civilizations. They are currently gathering a large force and preparing to achieve their goal in one go. Everyone has to contribute."

"Don't worry, even if you don't say it, we will still give it our all. My cannon is already thirsty!"

Sun Hunter waved his hand, his tiny body exuding a grand aura.

Manison said calmly, "We can finally end this war once and for all. It's earlier than I expected."

The majority of the people were overjoyed. Although they had the Sanctum to back them up and were not afraid of casualties, it was better to deal with painful things quickly. No one wanted to die several times in the long-term war.

Han Xiao raised his hand and gestured for everyone to not be so excited. He slowly said, "In this war, our chances of winning are more than ninety percent. Defeating the World Tree Civilization is only one aspect. After the war, we have more things to deal with. To prevent the three Universal Civilizations from kicking us to the curb after we've outlived our usefulness, I need everyone's support."

Hearing this, everyone held back their excitement and waited.

"What do you plan to do?" Kasuyi asked for everyone.

"I plan to use the aftermath of the war to change the organizational nature of the association, turn it into a civilization regime, and form a true Third Force. With our reputation and strength in the war, the three Universal Civilizations will have no choice but to accept it. I am letting you guys know first. When the time comes, and I give the signal, everyone will fully support me," Han Xiao explained.

"Have we finally reached this step? Don't worry, we will definitely cooperate."

Everyone's spirits were lifted.

This was a crucial step in the transformation of the Beyond Grade A group. Everyone had expected this, and there were no objections.

At this moment, Manison suddenly said, "We have to be careful of a problem. The three Universal Civilizations might have other thoughts under the premise that victory is within their grasp, and they might be interested in the power of the World Tree… We can help the three Universal Civilizations defeat their enemies, but we can't let them control or subdue the World Tree and turn it into a weapon to deal with us. This definitely won't do!"

Hearing this, everyone nodded in agreement.

The World Tree had already proved how terrifying it was. Originally, the combination of the Beyond Grade A Association and the Super Star Cluster Alliance could rival the three Universal Civilizations. If the three Universal Civilizations controlled the World Tree, their strength would expand to a new level and threaten the survival of the Beyond Grade As once again. This was an outcome that no one wanted to see.

Han Xiao's eyes flickered, and he smiled. "So, when we fight, be careful and pay attention to the three Universal Civilizations. Don't let them obstruct me."

The three Universal Civilizations had designated a gathering area in the Central Galaxy. As the armies of the various Star Fields continuously arrived, the size of the fleet waiting there had reached an astronomical number.

The Federation of Light took out almost all the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Devices in their inventory and arranged them neatly.

Because the World Tree had retracted its troops to protect the mother tree, this battle could only be fought head-on. It was truly an all-out battle between both sides. The scale of the battle was the largest since the start of the war.

All the warriors on the ships had solemn expressions, and the atmosphere was filled with the air of a decisive battle.

On the players' forums, the related threads were already being flooded.

The players naturally would not miss such a huge scene. Everyone had gathered and accepted the same mission—to be the vanguard of the main army and find out the distribution of the World Tree Civilization's troops in the main body's dimension.

Regarding this, the players did not have any objections. In fact, they were even willing to do so. After all, no one was more suitable for this mission than them, and there was still room for them to perform on such a grand occasion.

However, most of the players were not mentally prepared for the sudden change in the war situation. They were all shocked.

"Isn't this version called War of All Territories? I thought the World Tree's attack would last longer."

"We might have made a mistake. Our invasion of the other side is the true meaning of the version name."

"Speaking of which, with such a large-scale war, I feel that our influence is very limited… Damn it, are we going to watch CG again ‽"

"I don't think so. I don't think this battle will end anytime soon. I'm afraid it will become a meat grinder battlefield. It will probably be very tragic."

"It's hard to say. It's not that the enemy isn't working hard, but our army has Black Star."

The players discussed endlessly on the forums. Although there were quite many complaints, they were still looking forward to the three Universal Civilizations' counterattack.

On the other hand, the strategic command center was busy deducing the tactical arrangements of this battle and various possible scenarios.

Simon, Teny, and the other high-ranked officers were having a heated discussion, and Han Xiao and the others listened from the side.

"Our first wave of Immortals will be the vanguard and bring back more data. Then, we will use the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Devices to bombard the enemy with firepower. With 200,000 Keys of Destruction in a batch, we will send out 20 batches first. Then, we will cycle it a few times and try to damage the enemy's strength."

"After this, we will send out the main fleet in batches. Due to the limitation of the transmission device's efficiency, we can only use the reinforced swarming tactic. It will take some time to ease the disadvantage of our troops, so this period will be the period with the highest casualties."

"The enemy will guard the World Tree's main body tightly. Our goal will be to break through the enemy's defense zone, open a path to the World Tree's main body, and destroy it. This requires the cooperation of high-level combatants."

At this point, all the senior officers turned to look at Han Xiao.

Han Xiao knew what they meant, and he slowly said, "When the time comes, I will act as the arrowhead and lead the Beyond Grade As forward. You guys will be responsible for providing fire support."

"At that time, all the direct Beyond Grade As will listen to your commands," Simon said with a solemn tone.

Beyond Grade As had strong individual combat strength and mobility, so they were the best choice to advance. According to the tactical deductions of the three Universal Civilizations, this battle would most likely be fought with high-level combatants. Thus, the importance of Black Star and the Beyond Grade As in this war was self-evident.

Han Xiao was already mentally prepared. What he wanted was the military strength of the three Universal Civilizations, which could help him reach the World Tree's main body. Only then would he be able to carry out his real plan.

Although the three Universal Civilizations did not intend to engage in a blitzkrieg, with the speed of the World Tree's troops production, there would be a large number of new troops every day. The three Universal Civilizations could not help but speed up their gathering.

A few days later, when the three Universal Civilizations saw that their forces were more or less gathered, they started the battle without hesitation.

In the vast universe, teams of fleets carrying the players drove into different Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Devices and disappeared.

At the same time, in the secondary dimension world, the World Tree main body's dimension.

The area of this space was far larger than an ordinary dimension. A towering tree stood in the middle, its leaves lush and verdant. There were dense cracks in space around it, and countless roots extended out from the tree—this giant tree was the World Tree's main body.

At this time, layers of protective shields covered the World Tree's main body, and the seemingly endless World Tree fleet had been waiting here for many days. They formed layers of tight defense and were installed with countless weapons.

Buzz—

All of a sudden, the sky in the distance flashed with light, and the scout team formed by the players descended, appearing in the vision of the World Tree fleet.

"It's here…"

On a branch at the top of the World Tree, the Ancestral Tree King opened his eyes and looked in the direction of the enemy.

Chapter 1436: Fight to Win or Die

The light of the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Devices faded, and the scenery outside the porthole of the players' battleships turned into an incomparably vast green world. The huge World Tree's main body stood in the distance, and the endless World Tree fleet surrounded it like a green sea of light.

The distribution of the World Tree troops appeared in their eyes. It seemed to cover every inch of space, and it was extremely packed. It was enough to trigger trypophobia in ordinary people and make one's scalp tingle.

Countless spaceships adjusted their cannons at the same time and aimed in the direction of the players, ready to fire at any moment and smash them into pieces.

It was as if they could smell the strong scent of death. However, the players were not afraid at all. Instead, their blood was boiling, and they were trembling with passion.

"Hahahaha—Little saplings, to think that you would also have this day!"

"Brothers, charge!"

"For the tribe!"

"The sacred forum is connected to us!"

"Watatata, die!"

The tens of millions of players shouted excitedly and dispersed!

Batch after batch of battleships split up without hesitation and charged in all directions.

"Fire!"

As the Ancestral Tree King gave the order, countless cannons were fired, forming a tsunami of light cannons without any gaps. When the wave swept past, a large number of players, including the shields and hulls of the ships, were instantly crushed into powder!

In just one exchange, the players' fleet suffered huge casualties!

However, a portion of the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Devices operated in different groups, forming a teleportation channel that could be activated at all times. New troops would be teleported out every moment, and the rest of the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Devices operated together. They were specifically responsible for large-scale deployment, and the combination of the two teleportation methods ensured that there would not be a vacuum at the frontline.

A large number of players died, and new players continued to enter the battlefield, bringing back detailed information about the main body's dimension of the World Tree… Because the communication was restricted, it was difficult for normal scouting troops to send messages to the headquarters, and the players who could revive were the most unrestricted intelligence agents.

The World Tree Army's firepower was endless, and the enemy ships exploded into fireworks. However, at this moment, the players suddenly stopped teleporting, and in their place were densely packed Keys of Destruction.

"Shield!"

The roars of the various commanders could be heard from the World Tree's mental network. The outermost layer of defense immediately activated its response measures. Space expanded, lengthening the distance and turning into a deep region to cushion the bombardment. It was the Lerbo Space Protection Belt.

The next moment, batch after batch of Keys of Destruction emitted a blinding light, as though hundreds of thousands of suns were rising. Violent energy poured out like a floodgate!

Boom!

The high-density energy explosion caused the space to distort, and the source of the explosion seemed to have become a singularity. The surrounding space collapsed, showing the folds of the vortex-like space.

Immediately after, a world-rending light burst forth and spread out rapidly. It only slowed down after entering the Lerbo Space Protection Belt, like a wave on a beach. Its momentum gradually slowed down, and finally, it touched the outer layer of the defense circle's anti-explosion shield. It exploded with powerful electric arcs, leaving large cracks on the shield.

The Keys of Destruction's cleansing was repeated many times, but most of its power was reduced by the space protection belt. The remaining power shattered layers of protective shields, causing considerable damage to the World Tree fleet in the outermost layer of defense. However, the maintenance fleet was constantly repairing the shields, causing the Keys of Destruction's bombardment to stop at the outer layer.

If it was an ordinary secondary dimension, it would have exploded from the inside under such an energy explosion. However, the toughness of the World Tree main body's dimension far exceeded common sense, and its spatial strength was stronger than even the main universe. Furthermore, it was reinforced by the World Tree fleet with a large number of spacetime stabilization devices, making it extremely sturdy.

The players explored the battlefield and used the Keys of Destruction multiple times to wipe out the World Tree battleships. The rear battleships kept moving forward to replace the World Tree battleships, maintaining the protective shield. One side was acting like a bomb, while the other side was defending.

After another batch of Keys of Destruction exploded, the official troops of the Galactic Alliance Army finally arrived in groups.

Due to the limitations in the teleportation, the mission of the vanguard troops was to withstand the attacks of the World Tree and buy time for the follow-up troops, allowing the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Devices to continuously send troops over. Only when there were enough troops present would the first phase of the mission be considered a success. Only then would they be able to enter the next phase of the large-scale head-on battle.

The Galactic Alliance Army at the scene immediately took action. The division of labor was clear—the construction team constructed a base, built magic gates that connected straight to the main universe to add new channels for deploying troops. The guards surrounded the area, preparing to defend against the attacks of the World Tree, while the harassment mission was temporarily handed over to the Spacetime Splicing Technology suicide squad.

The Lerbo Space Protection Belt extended the distance between the two parties, causing the Galactic Alliance Army to have to travel for a long time to reach the outermost defense circle of the World Tree.

On the other hand, if the World Tree wanted to attack the Galactic Alliance Army, it did not need to travel in the Lerbo Space Protection Belt and could teleport directly. This was because this was the main dimension of the World Tree, and it had the ability of the 'World Tree Express'. All the members of the World Tree had the ability to teleport quickly and could appear anywhere.

The World Tree Civilization had the home-ground advantage here.

The next moment, green lights flashed, and batches of World Tree fleet appeared, directly crossing the Lerbo Space Protection Belt.

Looking at the densely packed armies of the three Universal Civilizations outside the window, countless World Tree warriors revealed fearless expressions.

Although their thoughts were controlled by the World Tree, the members of the World Tree still had their own consciousness and treated the World Tree as a totem. Now, they only had one thought, and that was to repel the three Universal Civilizations at all costs.

"For the mother tree! Kill all the enemies!"

The World Tree soldiers let out a shrill battle cry and controlled the battleships to attack.

"Stop them!"

The officers of the Galactic Alliance Army also roared and gave orders.

One side carried the flames of revenge for their compatriots, while the other side carried the determination to fight to the death. The strong collective consciousness clashed and tangled into a Psychic Current that wreaked havoc throughout the entire battlefield. Countless people could vaguely see two huge beasts biting each other.

Immediately after, the two armies clashed. In an instant, it was as if the sky was collapsing!

As soon as they started fighting, the situation became one-sided. Due to the large difference in strength, the World Tree fleet quickly gained the upper hand and broke through the Galactic Alliance Army's formation on a large scale.

The vanguard of the Galactic Alliance Army struggled to hold on. The pressure did not only come from the large number of enemy troops stationed in the main dimension but also from the harassment of the World Tree itself.

Every time the Galactic Alliance Army's forces were teleported to the battlefield, space cracks would appear all around them, and dense tree roots of the World Tree would extend out and smash the starships.

In the main body dimension, the Mother Tree's consciousness could control the World Tree Roots to block the enemy. Its destructive power might not be strong, but it was definitely a powerful method to disrupt the battle.

The World Tree and the Universal Civilization Army's special technological troops did not rest either. They used genetic bombs, dimensional weapons, and viruses at times. All kinds of technologies were being used.

Batch after batch of fleets was sacrificed, and more troops were teleported over. The number of troops increased and decreased like roller coasters, but the overall trend was still on the rise. The speed of the battle casualties was not as fast as the speed of the reinforcements sent by the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Devices.

The two armies clashed with each other, and the battlefield was extremely chaotic. The number of casualties increased at a terrifying speed.

...

"Attack, attack! We can't let the enemy defile the mother tree!"

Frenzied fighting spirit spread through the mental network, infecting all the World Tree members.

However, no matter how agitated they were, they could not determine the direction of the battle.

The two sides had been fighting for a long time, and the Galactic Alliance Army had already passed the most dangerous early stage. At this time, the number of troops present had already reached a large scale, and they gradually broke free from the disadvantage and began to fight against the World Tree fleet.

In the chaotic battlefield, one of the World Tree's battleships nimbly shuttled between the curtains of bullets, dodging attacks from all angles. It continuously shot out beams of light energy bullets, shattering the enemy battleships like a whip.

The pilot clenched his teeth, his eyes bloodshot.

When he neared a Galactic Alliance Army combat squad, the firepower covered his ship. The pilot immediately activated teleportation, and the entire spaceship disappeared from the spot, dodging a round of firepower.

The next moment, his spaceship appeared in the middle of this squad. The pilot did not hesitate to remove the limiter on the reactor, turning the entire spaceship into a large bomb, wanting to self-destruct and eliminate this enemy team.

However, at this moment, an invisible force field suddenly pressed down, directly crushing his spaceship into dust, turning his roar into nothingness.

Hundreds of Beyond Grade As appeared in the growing army formation of the Galactic Alliance Army. Heavenly judgment descended, instantly destroying a large portion of the World Tree troops that were attacking.

A gigantic Mechanical Deity was also exposed in the vision of both parties. It was Han Xiao's Supreme Heavenly Venerate, and its Transcendent Grade energy fluctuations instantly attracted the attention of all the soldiers and officers on both sides.

The members of the World Tree were already traumatized by Han Xiao.

The soldiers of the Galactic Alliance Army were the exact opposite. They were overjoyed.

"Attention, the Beyond Grade A Association is on the move! We are officially launching a counterattack!"

The entrance of the high-level combatants was a signal. It meant that their strategy had entered the second stage; from defense to offense.

The Galactic Alliance Army had accumulated enough troops and no longer focused on defense. They finally launched a ferocious counterattack and advanced toward the World Tree's main body from all directions.

"The Lerbo Space Protection Belt will be able to stop them for a very long time. The enemy won't be able to break into our official defense circle in a short period of time. We can use the strategic depth to deal more damage to them…"

Seeing this, many World Tree members had the same thought, but the next moment, their expressions changed.

Han Xiao's Supreme Heavenly Venerate raised his arm and shook it in the direction of the World Tree fleet's defense circle. A strange spatial fluctuation was released, covering the Lerbo Space Protection Belt in an instant.

The next moment, the Lerbo Space Protection Belt quickly lost its effect, and the extended space shrank back to normal.

However, this was not the only change. Originally, even if the Lerbo Space Protection Belt lost its effectiveness, there was still some distance between the two armies. However, the sudden reversal shortened the distance. In the blink of an eye, the main force of the Galactic Alliance Army was right in front of the defense circle. There was no need to waste time on the road.

The Universal Treasure technologies provided by the Saint Tyracles Race, the 'Space Constants Modifier', had already been improved by Han Xiao. The moment it was used, it showed a brilliant effect, and the function of the Lerbo Spatial Protection Belt was directly neutralized.

The shortening of space was extremely helpful to the galactic alliance army. The World Tree Civilization's expression changed.

"Charge!"

After doing this, Han Xiao spun the Emperor Skysplitter Blade, and the gigantic Supreme Heavenly Venerate advanced forward, tearing apart the World Tree fleet's formation. Psionic waves shot out freely, paralyzing the enemy ships.

The Beyond Grade As followed closely behind with grim expressions. They seemed to have formed a sharp blade and stabbed into the World Tree's defense circle.

Everywhere they passed, the World Tree battleships exploded!

Such an arrogant advance was immediately met with the large-scale focus fire of the World Tree fleet, but the Galactic Alliance Army was providing cover.

Just as Han Xiao was about to penetrate the outermost layer of defense, another Transcendent Grade aura suddenly descended, sweeping across the entire battlefield like a hurricane.

The Ancestral Tree King had already sacrificed himself, burning the remaining stock of the Beyonder's Vestige and activating the descent of the Tree God.

If there was no Transcendent like Black Star among the enemies, the Ancestral Tree King would still have a chance. He could use the Information Form revival mechanism of the Tree God to let the World Tree look like they were defeated on the surface, but in reality, they could resurrect elsewhere and return to the dark to recuperate.

However, in the face of a Transcendent's Information Form Obliteration, this path was no longer possible. Furthermore, as long as the Pivotal Snake did not die, the World Tree would have nowhere to hide. The Ancestral Tree King had no way out.

At this moment, the Tree God, who was only driven by his instincts, led the remaining high-level combatants of the World Tree to face Han Xiao and the others head-on. All of them were filled with tragic battle intent.

"Even if I die, I won't let you pass!"

"Kill!"

They were enemies, there was no need for any unnecessary words.

Bang!

Without hesitation, Han Xiao charged into the Tree God's arms and stabbed his blade into the Tree God's chest.

Two enormous Transcendents tangled together and rolled in the battle formation, crushing the starships in the sky.

Chapter 1437: Liberation of the Crown

The Emperor Skysplitter Blade revolved in the hands of the Supreme Heavenly Venerate like a light wheel, shooting out countless blue high-density psionic energy blades, shattering all the starships and mechas in its path. It left a blank space in the dense defensive formation, akin to a searing streak of light that never dissipated.

Swoosh! Swoosh! Swoosh! The blades of light landed on the Tree God's body one after another. The roots of the tree were cleanly cut in half, but sprouts quickly grew from the broken parts, repairing and closing the wounds.

As the Mechanical Force surged, the mechanical army was like a black and gold thundercloud, colliding with the green energy tsunami created by the Tree God, causing explosions around the two giants.

Buzz—

The two of them released their domains at the same time. The grayish-blue Void Domain and the green Tree God Domain collided and pressed toward each other. They rubbed against each other like tofu, creating dazzling electric arcs.

During this process, Han Xiao and the Tree God's bodies expanded endlessly. They rolled and fought together, colliding more than a thousand times in an instant. The shockwave sent all the spaceships flying.

This was not the first time the two of them had fought. The Tree God was still in an irrational state, but Han Xiao could clearly feel that the power of the Tree God had increased a lot. It was not as easy to deal with as the last time, especially since the strength of the Tree God Domain had increased tremendously.

The closer he got to the main body of the mother tree, the stronger the power of the Tree God became. This was especially so when he was in the main body dimension of the World Tree. The ability of the Tree God was enhanced, and it also had the ability to teleport without any cooldowns. It was extremely agile, and the most disgusting thing was that its regeneration speed was also shocking. Even Han Xiao felt that it was troublesome.

Under the enhancement of various factors, the Tree God actually managed to restrain Han Xiao's advancement for a while, even forcing Han Xiao to retreat far away from the mother tree.

"Looks like it won't be that easy to deal with this fellow…"

Han Xiao had already expected this. He had suspected that the Tree God would be buffed in the main body dimension, so he was not surprised.

His advance was blocked, but he was in no hurry at all. He focused on fighting the Tree God, waiting for his various talents to take effect, which would continue to increase his combat strength.

The last time he extracted the ability of the Tree God, he had obtained some obscure information. He guessed that the enemy had to pay a huge price to summon the Tree God, and it was not a long-term method.

Therefore, Han Xiao was not in a hurry to achieve anything. In his eyes, as long as he dragged this out, the Tree God would eventually weaken.

If not for the fact that he had attacked the World Tree's old home, he reckoned that the Ancestral Tree King would not have been willing to stop him.

While the two Transcendent Grade Supers were fighting, the Beyond Grade As on both sides were also engaged in battles.

All the Beyond Grade A Mechanics temporarily put aside their pin the strategic command center Allersonal grudges, and the mechanical army formed a formation, pouring out fierce firepower. The Mages summoned their respective Mage Pagodas and connected to each other, building large-scale magic circuits. They were like mobile formations, continuously releasing all kinds of large-scale attacks.

Mechanical Deities wreaked havoc on the battlefield one after another. Manison's silver mechanical body waved its trident and swept across a large area. His Indestructible Mechanical Troops stood beside him in an awe-inspiring manner. Herberlon finally had the chance to take revenge, starting a massacre. He let out a soundless roar even as he tore apart the roots of the World Tree.

On the other side, EsGod and his dozens of doppelgangers were traversing the battlefield. Their various Esper Abilities toyed with many World Tree experts. Not far away, Evans activated his [Energy Control] Esper Ability with all his might, gathering all kinds of energy from the battlefield and smashing it toward the World Tree fleet.

Hila's expression was solemn as she controlled the red tide of death, raising waves one after another and swallowing the enemy ships. Aurora, on the other hand, had a solemn expression and was emitting vitality. She continuously treated her injured teammates and summoned a large number of spirits to enter the battlefield from time to time.

Kasuyi was burning with an unlimited amount of mana, and his psychic energy was surging nonstop, shattering the thoughts of countless World Tree Blessings. In another area, Feidin held the Soul Swapper in his hands and strolled around the battlefield. The surrounding battlefield became a forbidden zone for life, and all the souls of the enemies were crushed.

The Pugilists no longer fought alone. Instead, they formed a battle formation. Sierron, Mercer, Heber, Viru, Jotina, Kohler, and the others launched a collective Iron Head Charge, turning the defenses of the World Tree fleet upside down. Their fists punched continuously, their voices of 'OraOra!' echoing in the dimension.

Karlot was among them. He drove Silver Shadow and crashed into enemy ships one after another.

'Quantum Demon Spirit' Judith, 'Defender' Romo, 'Mechanical Queen' Mornisa, and the others set off wave after wave of data attacks in the Virtual Network. 'Army Flag' Enid activated his ability, enveloped all of his allies in a buff halo, and together with Aurora, they increased the overall strength of the Beyond Grade As.

As they had not hesitated to invade the galactic society some time ago, many of the high-level combatants of the World Tree Civilization had died, and they had yet to revive. They did not expect to be counterattacked by the three Universal Civilizations so quickly, and this weakness had become a huge pit, causing the current high-level combatants to be far inferior to the three Universal Civilizations.

Thus, not long after the battle had started, the Beyond Grade As of the three Universal Civilizations displayed their abilities and beat the World Tree experts until they bled.

One after another, the Holy Tree Emissaries and ancestral spirits stared with bloodshot eyes. They were filled with unwillingness as they died in battle.

The high-level combatants were the sharpest blades, and they charged the deepest. In other directions, the armies of the three Universal Civilizations were also attacking the World Tree's defense circle. The battlefronts were in a deadlock, shifting back and forth.

"The current situation is advantageous to us. The longer the battle lasts, the more troops we can send out, and the pressure on the World Tree will continue to increase. It's impossible for them to maintain the frontline!"

In the strategic command center, all the upper echelons gathered together and looked at the real-time battle situation on the virtual strategy sand table. The atmosphere was tense.

Simon placed his hands on the table and said with a deep voice, "I've roughly divided the defense circle of the World Tree into five layers. Our main force is fighting on the outermost layer, and the Beyond Grade As have broken into the second layer. Black Star was about to break into the third layer, but he was forced back to the second."

"The World Tree Civilization is also going all out. It seems like we won't be able to penetrate the enemy's defenses in the short term," an officer commented.

Simon nodded in agreement. His tone was solemn as he continued:

"If we exhaust the World Tree's forces at the outermost perimeter, the troops inside will come out to reinforce our defenses. Furthermore, because the World Tree fleet can teleport indefinitely in this space, we will not be able to break out of the encirclement in a normal sense. We will either have to face the enemy head-on or defeat the enemy's army… Therefore, before both sides' forces are exhausted to a certain extent, our main force will not be able to open the situation."

Everyone had a serious expression and understood what he meant.

This was a bloody battle, and the casualties would be astronomical.

"As the attacker, we have the upper hand in the short term, but in the longer term, our future in a protracted war is not good."

Simon paused.

"The speed of our reinforcements is far slower than the World Tree. The World Tree is sending out troops every second from the roots, allowing them to immediately return to the battlefield… Although we can use the tactic of adding weight to increase the pressure on the World Tree, if the stalemate continues for a long time, the situation will probably turn around when all our troops are deployed."

Everyone was shocked. This situation was not impossible. If the World Tree Civilization erupted with astonishing tenacity and withstood their continuous attacks, their attacks would decline at some point in time. No matter how many advantages they had accumulated before, they would be taken back.

This time, Simon changed the topic. Pointing at Black Star in the strategic sand table, he said with a deep voice, "We can't count on the victory of the main force for now. The ones that are most likely to break the stalemate are the Beyond Grade As. With Black Star leading the way, as long as they can get rid of the obstruction of the enemy's high-level combatants, they will be able to advance quickly. They are the breakthrough point of this battle, and they might be able to influence the outcome."

All the officers and the leaders of the three Universal Civilizations nodded.

Although it seemed like Black Star would not be able to get rid of the Tree God anytime soon, after experiencing so much, everyone had strong confidence in him and had high hopes.

Bang! Bang! Bang! Bang!

One black and one green Transcendent clashed countless times. As his various talents were activated, Han Xiao's attributes increased bit by bit. The more he fought, the stronger he became, and he gradually suppressed Tree God.

Because the Tree God had an extremely high absorption rate toward energy attacks, Han Xiao could only use physical attacks against him. The black torrent formed by mechanical particles transformed into all kinds of forms, leaving wounds on the Tree God's body.

Very soon, Han Xiao started to push forward again with unstoppable momentum. The Tree God hurriedly released a series of World Tree Roots to wrap around the Supreme Heavenly Venerate, trying to stall him. However, these roots were all easily torn apart by Han Xiao and crushed into dust.

"Without the incomplete state of rationality, it can only rely on its instincts to fight, and cannot release its full strength. It's a pity."

Han Xiao spun his blade and chopped off the head of the Tree God. Seeing the head of the Tree God regenerate rapidly, he shook his head.

However, right at this moment, the Tree God suddenly jolted, and the chaotic emotions of the beast subsided. For the first time, a clear mental thought came to him. It was the consciousness of the Ancestral Tree King.

"Black Star! Don't even think about getting past me!"

"Eh, you regained consciousness?"

Han Xiao raised his brows. He was curious about what method the Ancestral Tree King had used to regain his rationality and take over the control of the Tree God.

Just as the Ancestral Tree King took over the body of the Tree God, its fighting style immediately changed. The fighting style was no longer rough and a lot of details were added.

Although his strength did not increase, the actual combat strength that the Tree God displayed had increased significantly. It was like a completely different person.

At this moment, in the inner space of the Tree God, the illusory figure of the Ancestral Tree King was floating. His senses were connected to the Tree God's vision, and he looked at Han Xiao with a determined expression.

Until just now, the Ancestral Tree King was trapped in the consciousness of the Tree God and was in a state of chaos. However, the World Tree finally realized that it was facing a great calamity. The will of the Mother Tree descended, allowing the Ancestral Tree King to wake up alone. It also took back the crown positions of the Fortitude Tree King and the Subduing Tree King, handing them all to the Ancestral Tree King. Its meaning was very clear. It was to let the Ancestral Tree King fight alone.

This was something the World Tree had learned from the process of those previous tree kings who had attempted to break through to the Transcendent Grade. Burning the information state foundation of the Ancestral Tree King allowed him to enter a state similar to the advancement of the Transcendent Grade, but he was still controlled by the World Tree. This way, the consciousness of the Ancestral Tree King would be connected to the senses of the Tree God and could control the Tree God alone.

The price was to temporarily deprive the Ancestral Tree King of the chance to revive. If he could survive, he would be able to return to the mother tree's embrace after exiting the tree god state. However, if he died in this state, the Ancestral Tree King would then end up like those tree kings who failed to advance to the Transcendent Grade, unable to revive. This was the disadvantage.

However, this was the will of the Mother Tree, and the Ancestral Tree King had no right to choose.

Han Xiao said with a calm tone, "With your control, the Tree God is indeed much stronger, but if you think that this small change can stop me, you're overthinking it. Furthermore, how long can this state of yours last?"

"Do you think you've won?!"

The Ancestral Tree King's expression was stern. Without saying a word, he activated [Tree King Crown —Liberation].

In the void, the Subduing Tree King Crown that represented the Pugilist class shattered!

The experience and skills accumulated by every generation of the Martial Tree King were all integrated into the Tree God. At the same time, the origin power of the crown seemed to have become a catalyst, instantly increasing the combat power of the Tree God!

A seemingly endless amount of energy suddenly surged out from deep within his body and spread throughout his entire body in the blink of an eye.

"Ahhh—"

The intense pain invaded the mind of the Ancestral Tree King, causing him to let out a low growl. However, his mental strength did not weaken. Instead, it was stimulated and quickly strengthened.

The next moment, green muscles suddenly grew out of the Tree God's body. The originally dry tree body suddenly became burly and round.

This feeling was as though the original Tree God was just a skeleton. Only now did the flesh and blood appear on the skeleton.

The Tree God Domain that was originally at a disadvantage suddenly expanded, pushing Han Xiao's Void Domain away.

[Tree King Crown —Liberation] could strengthen the combat power of the Tree God, and the corresponding Tree King Crown had to be sacrificed. Losing the right to be the Tree King for a long period of time would require thousands of years to recover, and the price was huge!

However, to reduce the losses, the Ancestral Tree King sacrificed the title of the Pugilist without hesitation!

Ancestral Tree King's emotions were affected as if a pile of dry wood had been touched by a spark, and his battle intent soared.

"My strength is far from my limit! Black Star! Only when you die will we be at peace!"

Chapter 1438: Come on, Big Brother who plays with tree roots!

The Pugilist flames burned, and the Tree God's movements became even faster. His strength increased tremendously, and he suddenly grabbed the Emperor Skysplitter Blade coming at him. He stopped the momentum of the blade in midair.

At the same time, roots shot out from the surface of the Tree God's body. The ends of the roots curled up like a knot, forming thousands of fists that rained down on the body of the Supreme Heavenly Venerate.

Green fist shadows filled the sky, piercing through the combined shield of the mechanical army and bombarding the body of the Supreme Heavenly Venerate. Cracks appeared on the surface of its body.

Energy shot out from the back of the Supreme Heavenly Venerate one after another, forming a green shockwave that did not weaken in the slightest even after passing through it, destroying patches of battleships as collateral damage.

"His close combat ability has increased tremendously. This should be a sacrifice for the Tree King Crown, right?"

Han Xiao endured the impact and analyzed calmly.

He had seen the [Tree Crown—Liberation] skill when he was extracting the Tree God's ability. The Tree God did not use this skill the last time they fought. This time, he recognized it at a glance.

Seeing the actual effect, Han Xiao felt a sense of familiarity. He felt that this move was a bit like a Character Summon Card, used to obtain the Super system power stored in the different Tree King Crowns.

"The World Tree has a total of five… Oh, no, it's now four Tree King Crowns, which means that the Tree God can spawn at least four more times. Its strength will continue to stack, and its final battle strength will probably be very astonishing. Furthermore, this doesn't even take into consideration if the Tree God has other explosive abilities."

Han Xiao quickly calculated.

The moment the Tree God used his one-time explosive ability, the best way to counter it would be to avoid it, but the situation did not allow it. The Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device was one-way, and if he wanted to send a large group back, he would have to set up a new group of teleportation devices here. Now that the majority were already locked in battle with the World Tree, they naturally would not retreat halfway, or many warriors would have died for nothing.

Furthermore, Han Xiao also wanted to fight the Tree God head-on. After all, with his current strength, it was difficult to find an opponent. Now that he had finally met one, how could he not show the other party some love?

"Looks like I have to show you my true skills. Let me see how many tricks you have."

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

He had long known that the Tree God had an explosive ability, but the Ancestral Tree King thought that he did not know and wanted to give him an unexpected attack. However, he had long been prepared for it.

On the other side, the Ancestral Tree King held onto the Emperor Skysplitter Blade tightly, not allowing Han Xiao's weapon to escape his control. Endless energy flowed out from his body, and he was able to gain the upper hand against the Supreme Heavenly Venerate, pushing Han Xiao back.

Taking advantage of the fact that Han Xiao could not move, the Ancestral Tree King controlled a large number of roots and attacked the chest of the Supreme Heavenly Venerate.

The mechanical army also reacted and began to block the attacks of the Tree God. At the same time, the mechanical particles flowing around the body of the Supreme Heavenly Venerate also transformed into streams, intercepting the roots halfway.

Bang! Bang! Bang!

Looking from afar, countless blurry afterimages of light appeared around the two super gods and collided with each other. Metal and tree roots clashed at a high frequency, and continuous shockwaves exploded in midair.

"Your strength is already below mine!"

The Ancestral Tree King had a vicious expression on his face. He twisted the Emperor Skysplitter Blade as he channeled his energy into his arm. He was about to launch a follow-up attack.

However, at this moment, an irresistible force suddenly came from the blade and suppressed his strength!

Boom!

The next moment, the Emperor Skysplitter Blade, which was originally frozen in midair, suddenly broke through the Tree God's stance and slashed down. In an instant, it slashed across the Tree God's shoulder all the way to his waist, leaving a huge wound. The Tree God was almost cut into two.

"What?!"

The Ancestral Tree King was horrified. Instead of retreating, he rushed forward and hugged Han Xiao. He wanted to use the power of the crown to restrict Han Xiao's movement and stop his follow-up attack.

However, the result was far from what he had imagined. The Tree God was crushed under the body of the Supreme Heavenly Venerate and almost dismembered as though he was suffering from the capital punishment of 'Death by a Thousand Cuts'. The power brought by the sacrifice of the Pugilist Tree King Crown was still suppressed by Han Xiao!

The Ancestral Tree King was horrified. He had barely escaped by igniting the Pugilist flames, but the body of the Tree God was already in tatters. Countless pieces of its newly born flesh had been cut off, and it was currently in the process of recovery.

Han Xiao casually cut off the World Tree Root that he was following before looking at the Tree God with dissatisfaction.

"You're so arrogant at only this standard?"

"You…"

Feeling Han Xiao's energy level rising, the Ancestral Tree King's expression darkened.

He had thought that he would be able to gain the upper hand after liberating the Tree King Crown, but reality had given him a huge slap. He did not expect that he would still not be Han Xiao's match after using his burst ability, and the other party was also increasing their combat capability.

The Ancestral Tree King clenched his teeth before making a decision.

"Don't celebrate too early. I haven't reached my limit!"

The moment he said that the crown of the Secret Tree King shattered!

A new source of energy was released. It was like adding fuel to the core furnace of the Tree God. Its energy level broke through its limits once again!

Countless magical knowledge flowed into his brain. At the same time, many complicated magic circuits appeared on the surface of the Tree God's body, forming various enchantment runes.

In an instant, the power of the mages was also applied to the Tree God!

The Tree God Domain expanded once again, almost flattening the Void Domain!

"Ahhh—"

An even stronger burden descended, and the mental strength of the Ancestral Tree King soared. However, at the same time, it brought him even more intense pain. His soul wailed uncontrollably, and his emotions became even more intense.

He endured the pain, mobilized his new strength, and launched an even stronger attack at Han Xiao.

Boom!

The surging magic power formed a densely packed Forbidden Technique that almost drained all the free energy particles in the nearby battlefield. It turned into bright rainbow light and submerged Han Xiao's entire body. It was extremely deadly.

As the Tree God maintained the bombardment of magic, he charged into the light of the explosion and chased after the body of the Supreme Heavenly Venerate. The fists and roots that contained the shocking Pugilist flames landed on Han Xiao's body continuously, creating loud explosions!

The Ancestral Tree King stared with bloodshot eyes, tirelessly attacking again and again!

"Black Star! I will never let you destroy my civilization!"

The mental shockwave of the roar swept across the battlefield, instantly stirring the emotions of countless people!

However, right at this moment, an extremely dense aura of blood suddenly erupted in front of him.

Buzz!

Before the Ancestral Tree King could react, a cold light suddenly lit up. He felt a huge force coming from his chest. The Emperor Skysplitter Blade flew over and stabbed into his chest.

The next second, the Ancestral Tree King realized that his arm was firmly locked in place. Not only that, but all the roots that he was using to attack had also stopped moving.

The light of the magic explosion dissipated, revealing the appearance of the Supreme Celestial Venerable. Han Xiao's entire body was covered in blood energy, and he grabbed the arm of the Tree God. The mechanical particles formed countless tentacles that extended out from his back, accurately wrapping around the roots of every World Tree. They were joined in midair like bridges.

The power of the Supreme Heavenly Venerate increased rapidly, and it soon exceeded the second stage liberated Tree God, making it impossible for the Ancestral Tree King to escape.

"You…"

The Ancestral Tree King's eyes widened.

However, before he could do anything, Han Xiao suddenly smashed his head against him.

The next moment, the Supreme Heavenly Venerate grabbed the Tree God's arm and pressed him down. At the same time, he bent his knee and raised his leg, smashing the Tree God's head with a powerful knee strike, producing a green shockwave. Han Xiao extended his hand and stabbed into the hole on the Tree God's head, all the way to his chest. He grabbed a bunch of messy roots and pulled them out, tearing out a large number of broken roots.

If it had been a normal life form, its spine and organs would have been pulled out. Even the Tree God, who had a special body structure, would not have felt good.

At this time, Han Xiao pulled out the Emperor Skysplitter Blade from the Tree God's chest. He then used Virtual Creation to create countless huge cannons around the tree god.

Hong Long Long~

After a round of firing, countless physical bullets of planetary-sized mass blasted the Tree God into smithereens.

The terrifying kinetic energy pushed the Tree God and sent him flying, creating a blank space on the battlefield. Han Xiao followed closely behind and entered the middle of the third layer of defense.

Only then did the Ancestral Tree King manage to stop his uncontrolled retreat and teleport to avoid Han Xiao's pursuit. He jumped a distance away and quickly summoned more World Tree Roots to heal his injuries.

Seeing this, Han Xiao swung his blade and said casually,

"That's it? Anything else?"

In terms of the quantity and quality of the attribute enhancement abilities, there were very few people who could beat him. The Tree God had buffed itself twice in a row, and his combat strength had increased by quite a lot, but it was still insufficient in front of him.

Although he had just stepped into the Transcendent Grade not too long ago, as long as he activated all the bonuses, his combat strength would increase to an astonishing level. Han Xiao was not sure what level he would be at after he unleashed his full strength.

Hearing this, the Ancestral Tree King became even more agitated. Anger, shock, and unwillingness filled his mind.

Even after sacrificing two Tree King Crowns and paying such a huge price, his combat capability was still no match for Black Star?!

The Ancestral Tree King was already caught between a rock and a hard place. To him, a stalemate was meaningless. If he could not kill Black Star, Black Star would be able to make a comeback countless times. There was only one path left, and that was to kill Black Star at all costs.

Various thoughts flashed through his mind. The Ancestral Tree King looked at the main body of the mother tree with determination.

Seeing that the Ancestral Tree King did not reply, Han Xiao was about to continue attacking, but at this moment, the World Tree fleet charged toward him as though they were insane.

"Protect the mother tree!"

"Go, give the Tree God some time to breathe!"

"Fight for our homeland!"

Countless World Tree warriors rushed over to engage in a fierce battle.

Seeing this, Han Xiao casually attacked, only to see the new troops constantly approaching to replenish those wiped out. Many World Tree soldiers were willing to die, using their lives to form a line of defense to stop him from chasing after the Tree God, just to give the heavily damaged Tree God more time to recover.

However, in the face of the absolute difference in strength, the determination to face death was meaningless. No matter how many fleets there were, they would all be destroyed by the psionic waves.

Countless members of the World Tree Blessed Race swarmed over like moths to a flame, leaving behind a bunch of paralyzed battleship wreckages. There was only dead silence in the ship, as the crew had all died under the psionic waves.

Han Xiao was hardly obstructed at all. He stepped on the debris of the countless World Tree battleships and pointed at the heavily injured Tree God. The gigantic figure of the Supreme Heavenly Venerate gave off an aura of despair to his enemies.

Seeing this tragic scene, many players who were fighting were moved.

"They should be evenly matched, but why do I feel like it's an adult bullying a child…"

"Look at Black Star's style, I'm a little confused. Which one is the real villain boss?"

"Come on, big brother who plays with tree roots!"

Amidst the cheers of the players, Han Xiao slammed into the Tree God, who had yet to fully recover, and pushed him as he shot forward.

The Tree God seemed to have lost its ability to resist and could not stop Han Xiao at all. The two of them surrounded each other and broke through the third and fourth layers of defense. Not long after, they reached the fifth layer of defense. The World Tree's main body that supported this dimension was now right in front of them.

The eyes of the Galactic Alliance Army and the World Tree fleet all focused on Black Star. Seeing that Black Star was approaching the World Tree's main body, everyone's hearts were in their throats.

However, right at this moment, the Tree God's green domain suddenly expanded.

Buzz!

The green light exploded and enveloped the two of them. It then shrank into a light spot and disappeared.

The two of them were swallowed up and disappeared from the battlefield under the eyes of everyone.

This scene was out of the Galactic Alliance Army's expectations. Countless people's hearts suddenly constricted, and they did not know what had happened.

At the same time, in the Strategic Command of the Allied Army.

Simon rushed to the table, his eyes wide with shock.

"Where's Black Star? Where the f**k did the two of them go?!!"

Chapter 1439: Exhausted

This was a deep and vast space, like a real universe. The black velvet curtain was decorated with green stars, bright and dazzling.

Suddenly, a green light appeared out of nowhere, spinning and expanding, turning into a wormhole-like vortex and spitting out Han Xiao's figure.

Han Xiao quickly stabilized himself and looked around curiously.

"Where did you bring me?"

He glanced at the interface, and the combat information showed his current state. He had been 'swallowed' by the Tree God. This universe-like world was the inner space of the Tree God.

The next moment, Han Xiao immediately felt the repulsion of the entire world. Pressure came from all directions, suppressing his strength. The Void Domain was so compressed that it could only stick to the surface of the body, almost becoming a flat membrane.

At the same time, Han Xiao also discovered that an unknown corrosive force was continuously reducing his health. It was shown in his status bar as the 'World Tree's Digestive Function'.

"So, I've fallen into the stomach of the World Tree."

Han Xiao thought to himself.

Buzz!

Right at this moment, the green light in front of Han Xiao's eyes shrank and condensed into the body of the Tree God. Its injuries had already recovered, and it stood in the distance.

"Black Star, our battle is not over yet," the Ancestral Tree King said with a deep voice.

Han Xiao sized him up and said, "This is your inner space, right? How dare you suck me in? You're really not afraid of death."

Releasing the Inner Spatial Domain did not have any side effects, because it was just a projection of power, just like the descent of a secondary dimension. However, absorbing the enemy into the Inner Spatial Domain was the opposite. This was a dangerous action. If the Inner Spatial Domain was destroyed, the Transcendent would be heavily injured, which was equivalent to exposing their vital points to the enemy.

However, in the inner space, the enemy's strength would be greatly suppressed, and the user would receive a higher boost. Therefore, this was a double-edged sword.

No matter how tanky Han Xiao was, he was not willing to suck any enemy into his body. This would only increase the risk. In his eyes, the Ancestral Tree King was putting everything on the line without thinking.

"If you don't die, the mother tree will never have a day of peace. This will be where you die!"

The Ancestral Tree King's tone was fierce, and he attacked without hesitation.

Countless green lights shot out toward Han Xiao like meteors.

Seeing this, Han Xiao lifted the Emperor's Cape, and the thick psionic shield blocked the dense rain of light.

At the same time, he ordered his mechanical army to open fire, but they did not attack the Tree God. Instead, they exploded in all directions, triggering many energy bombs.

Under normal circumstances, attacking the inner space was akin to turning the world upside down in the other party's body. The damage would be reflected back to the Tree God.

However, the next moment, something that Han Xiao did not expect happened. The Tree God was not affected at all, and he even gave up all his defenses. His attacks were extremely fierce, as though he was not worried about his internal space being damaged at all.

Han Xiao was a little surprised. His Void Domain was suppressed, and the Tree God was like a fish in water in his internal space. His strength was decreasing, and he had no choice but to defend.

"Interesting. Your inner space won't be damaged?"

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and observed the flow of energy while resisting the attacks of the Ancestral Tree King.

Not long after, Han Xiao's eyes lit up, and he smiled.

"I see. I have roughly guessed it. Your inner space is connected to the World Tree and you transferred all the damage, right?"

"..."

The ancestral tree king's heart tightened, but he did not reply. His attacks became more intense.

The things that the World Tree devoured formed a 'Mother Tree World' within its body. It also had planets and lives, and most of them operated according to the state when they were swallowed. They would not increase or decrease naturally, and it was equivalent to a special 'gallery'. If the members of the World Tree were not willing to appear in the outside world, they would live in the Mother Tree World. The so-called transformation of the World Tree was like spitting something out from the body into the outside world.

The Tree God was closely connected to the World Tree's main body, so there was a connection between its internal space and the mother tree world. Strictly speaking, the internal space of the Tree God was a clone and interlayer of the mother tree world, and the Ancestral Tree King was able to split the damage suffered by the internal space into the mother tree world.

This way, the World Tree's main body would suffer some damage, and the Tree God would not be injured and could remain in peak condition… Under normal circumstances, the Ancestral Tree King would not let the World Tree's main body take this risk, but now, increasing the Tree God's combat strength was more important, so he could only make a temporary choice.

Therefore, in order to prevent the World Tree's main body from suffering any further damage, the Ancestral Tree King chose to end the battle as soon as possible and deal with Han Xiao before he caused even more damage to the internal space!

Seeing that Han Xiao had discovered his weakness so quickly, the Ancestral Tree King clenched his teeth.

"Even if I have to gamble our future, I have to kill you!"

As soon as he said that, the Fortitude Tree King's crown shattered!

The powerful Crown Origin Energy surged in, and the power of the Tree God soared once again!

Intensive mechanical armor rapidly spread across the surface of the Tree God's body. At the same time, mechanical soldiers shining with green light appeared around the Tree God. This scene was like a Legendary Mechanic activating [Virtual Creation].

However, the Ancestral Tree King did not stop. He endured the rising pain and directly took over the allocation of 'King's Legacy' from the Mother Tree Will.

Sacrificing the Tree King Crown was the way to strengthen the Tree God, but it was not the only way. Among the abilities that Han Xiao did not see, there were other ways to strengthen it, and investing more Beyonder's Vestige was another way.

If the Beyonder's Vestige was a 'firewood' that could ignite the power of the Tree God, then adding more 'firewood' would naturally make the flames burn even stronger.

After so many years, generations of tree kings had failed to break through to the Transcendent Grade, leaving behind some 'King's Legacy', which were considered strategic resources.

Initially, he only needed to use one portion to summon the Tree God each time, but the Ancestral Tree King could not be bothered anymore and burned half of the inventory!

Bang!

A violent energy tide spread out, and the power level of the Tree God increased steadily. Thick green waves gushed out as if they were going to fill the entire space.

"Holy, another SEED activation[1] ‽"

Han Xiao gritted his teeth.

This is too much. Are you a Saiyan… ahh, no, Saiyan Tree ‽

After sacrificing three Crowns and burning half of the Beyonder's Vestige stock, the Tree God's combat capability soared to a higher level, and his combat style changed as well. Other than using the strength of the World Tree, the various magic, martial arts, and mechanical systems formed an exquisite combination. One person was like a powerhouse of three different classes, very flashy but also very powerful.

For a time, the violent attacks penetrated the shield, leaving all kinds of wounds on the body of the Supreme Heavenly Venerate. One device after another was destroyed.

"I still can't underestimate this guy. With the World Tree Civilization's many years of foundation, there's a lot of room for his combat strength to fluctuate…"

Han Xiao felt immense pressure from the Ancestral Tree King's continuous attacks, and he was slightly shocked.

If he had not sealed the Heart Tree Crown, the complete Tree God might have been able to completely suppress him after receiving so many enhancements.

However, the current Tree God was in an incomplete state. Its foundation had been weakened, so the SEED activation effect was also reduced, and it could not reach its peak.

"What a pity. If this is your full strength, the one dying today won't be me."

Han Xiao's tone became serious.

Boom!

Without waiting for the Ancestral Tree King to react, the energy level of the Supreme Heavenly Venerate also increased tremendously. In the blink of an eye, he caught up to the level of the Tree God's combat strength after the SEED activation!

All kinds of strange abilities exploded one after another, stopping the attack of the Ancestral Tree King in an instant. Han Xiao immediately took back the initiative and counterattacked, instantly turning the situation around.

The Ancestral Tree King's eyes widened. "You…"

"Tsk, do you think that the SEED activation is your patent?"

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes. A steady stream of new energy entered his body, bringing with it an incomparable sense of power. He almost felt like he could shatter the universe.

The reason for this instant change was because he had used the Character Summon Cards in his inventory.

Ever since stepping into the peak Beyond Grade A realm, Han Xiao had not used his Character Summon Cards that much. Because there was no need for that, he had a lot of stock.

Before this expedition, he had specially used all his blank Character Summon Cards to replicate the abilities of different Beyond Grade As and obtained a large number of resources.

After finally accumulating a huge amount of wealth, Han Xiao now activated the Character Summon Cards one after another without any heartache. He used whatever he had. He only felt carefree and happy!

After such a long time of careful planning, he could finally be extravagant!

Compared to Saint Seiya's explosion of a little universe, I'm the expert!

Sensing that Black Star's strength had caught up once again, the Ancestral Tree King was furious.

Every time the gap between them opened up, he would eventually catch up. Black Star's unfathomable trump cards made the already unstable Ancestral Tree King go completely crazy!

"Black Star!"

Bang!

The last Tree King Crown exploded; the Ancestral Tree King decisively sacrificed his own crown!

He threw all his worries to the back of his mind and poured all the remaining Beyonder's Vestige into the Tree God's body.

He was going to push the power of the Tree God up regardless of the cost!

His strength increased at an astonishing speed, but at the same time, faint green cracks spread on the surface of the Tree God's body. The huge burden was already at the limits of the Tree God.

The Tree God had its limits, like a container. When the accumulated power exceeded its maximum capacity, it would burst from the inside.

Perhaps in its perfect state, the capacity of the Tree God would be able to withstand its current power, but the incomplete Tree God was like a container that was one size smaller. It could not endure such a burden, and its injuries began to accumulate rapidly.

However, the Ancestral Tree King ignored the overload and charged toward Han Xiao with an unstoppable force.

At this moment, he only had one thought, and that was to kill Black Star!

"Come!"

Han Xiao was full of fighting spirit.

Bang! Bang! Bang!

The two of them were overflowing with terrifying power, only attacking but not defending. They bombarded each other countless times, and the energy clashed, forming an extremely high density explosive area. In this place, time and space twisted, almost condensing into singularities.

The two of them abandoned all distracting thoughts, having only their opponents in their eyes. They fought tirelessly, and the battlefield spread across this universe.

Space trembled and shattered. The starlight dimmed and died!

It was unknown how long the battle lasted, but it felt like an eternity. Only then did the battle come to an end.

Only by burning the Beyonder's Vestige could the existence of the Tree God be maintained. The Tree God had finally run out of energy, and the power obtained from the SEED activation quickly weakened. The Tree God's body was already filled with cracks from the overload, like a piece of porcelain pieced together after being shattered.

Crack!

The Tree God's chest suddenly split open, triggering a chain reaction. With its chest as the center, its entire body 'collapsed', turning into fragments of light that filled the sky.

This scene represented the death of the Tree God.

The Tree God also had life. Once it was killed, the fused Tree Kings would also be heavily damaged, and the Tree God's Descent would enter a cooldown… In addition, because the four Tree King Crowns had been sacrificed, the World Tree could not summon the Tree God anymore.

In the sky full of light fragments, the Ancestral Tree King's body floated. It was as if he had overdrawn all his lifespan, becoming old and wrinkled.

As the Tree God dissipated, the Ancestral Tree King also slowly turned into dust. His life was like a candle in the wind.

"I lost… I'm sorry Mother Tree, I failed you… I was so close, I can't accept it…"

Ancestral Tree King's consciousness gradually dissipated as he muttered to himself.

Han Xiao still did not relax. He received the Ancestral Tree King's intermittent brainwaves, clicked his tongue, and said mercilessly,

"What do you mean by almost? From the start to the end, you had no chance at all."

The Ancestral Tree King turned around and glared at Han Xiao.

"…I did not protect my civilization, but one day, you will also taste my despair! I curse you…"

"Don't look so bitter. When you destroyed other civilizations, you should have been prepared to be destroyed as well."

Han Xiao did not want to waste any more time talking to him. He stretched out his hand and grabbed the Ancestral Tree King.

Pu!

The Ancestral Tree King was crushed and turned into dust. His consciousness completely fell into darkness.

Han Xiao was not interested in waiting for him to die. He was not a villain who did not know how to deal the finishing blow.

Due to the manipulation of the World Tree, the Ancestral Tree King had already lost the ability to revive. If he died in this state, he would truly die and disappear.

"Finally got him. Damn, he almost squeezed me dry."

Only at this moment did Han Xiao finally relax.

Although he had won this battle, Han Xiao was also exhausted. In the final stage, it was as though the Tree God had activated the Ultra Instinct Technique. It was so powerful that it almost shattered his Supreme Heavenly Venerate several times.

Strictly speaking, the one who killed the Tree God was not Han Xiao but the Ancestral Tree King himself. The damage caused by the overload and the burning of the Beyonder's Vestige was the main reason the Tree God was so exhausted.

If the Tree God was in the perfect state where all five crowns were gathered, Han Xiao felt that he would not be a match for it.

Unfortunately, there were no ifs in this world.

Crack!

The moment the Tree God died completely, the space inside began to collapse rapidly, splitting open like a broken mirror. Dazzling light flowed through every crack, leading to the outside world.

Han Xiao calmed himself down and retrieved the heavily damaged mechanical army back into the Godly Stronghold. He then drove the Supreme Heavenly Venerate into one of the cracks and disappeared in the light.

[1] Gundam reference Back

Chapter 1440: Missing the Opportunity, Going All Out

In the main dimension of the World Tree, the war had reached its climax.

Black Star and the Tree God had disappeared together for a very long time. Due to the sudden change, the galactic allied forces did not know what was going on. Countless officers and soldiers could only endure their unease and fear and continue to fight.

Due to the lack of a sharp blade like Black Star, the advancement of the army was also slowed down considerably.

At this moment, the interstellar fleet had just arrived at the second layer of defense, and the World Tree Blessing Race did not care about the cost and reinforced the defense line. The battlefield was like a millstone, crushing the battleships and soldiers into powder. There were countless casualties, and it was a huge blow to both sides.

Without Black Star's support, the advancement of the Beyond Grade As was also blocked. However, the quality and scale of their combat strength still exceeded the current high-level combatants of the World Tree. After the protracted battles, the Beyond Grade As of the galactic society had already annihilated most of the high-level combatants on the World Tree's side.

However, because the Beyond Grade As did not have the strength to ignore the large-scale galactic battlefield like Black Star, they could not enter even after killing many of the World Tree's experts. On the contrary, due to the intense firepower of the World Tree's Blessed Race, they did not dare to advance too far and be used as targets. They could only retreat to the vicinity of the main force to cooperate. Although there was not much danger with Aurora's help, the Beyond Grade As were temporarily unable to turn the situation around. After all, the World Tree had too many troops.

"I wonder where Black Star is. Can you contact him?"

Kasuyi placed his hand on his forehead and asked in the Beyond Grade A combat channel while controlling his psychic energy to shatter the enemies one by one.

"I can't contact him. It's most likely that the Tree God used some trump card to prevent Black Star from continuing his advance and brought him to some alternate dimension. I guess they can only come out after a victor is decided."

Hila casually replied. She manipulated the cold current of death and swept it across the fleet. Red ice crystals grew out of the battleships and broke through the hulls.

"Black Star won't lose, right?" Oulou asked hesitantly.

"There's nothing to be afraid of. Whether Black Star wins or not, he can come and go as he wishes." Hila was not worried about Han Xiao's safety at all.

"It's hard to say. The World Tree Civilization has developed to this point and is unfathomable. No one knows what other trump cards they have. Maybe Black Star will fall for it too…"

Although Hila, Aurora, and the others were not worried, many Beyond Grade As were.

It was not that they did not believe in Black Star's strength, but no one could say for sure what would happen in a war of this scale. As the saying goes, 'concern leads to confusion'. Black Star had the responsibility of leading the association, and he was the ruler of the Sanctum Revival. It was difficult for a portion of the Beyond Grade As not to feel nervous, especially when they knew nothing about Black Star's current situation.

At the same time, in the strategic command center, Wuornos' remote projection was also present, watching the battle.

Most of the Beyond Grade As in the galactic society were involved in this war, but Wuornos was not one of them.

When the church came to find him, he still refused to participate in this battle. The reason was the same as before—he needed to maintain a perfect state at all times and did not want to waste his energy in other areas, lest he missed the opportunity to step into the Transcendent Grade.

Because there was a true Transcendent like Black Star participating in the battle, the Arcane Church did not force Wuornos to take action. However, Wuornos did not reject the request to watch the battle.

On the side, the officers and staff officers discussed nonstop for the sake of the battle. Wuornos did not interrupt from the start to the end. He stood alone and watched the battlefield silently.

He did not have much interest in the battle and only requested to watch because he wanted to see a battle between Transcendent Grade Supers. He planned to use this to inspire himself, but this idea fell through.

"Black Star and the Tree God should be fighting in the alternate dimension, but I can't see them…"

Wuornos sighed.

He had only seen a small portion of the battle between the two of them on the main battlefield, and neither of them had used any of their trump cards. He could not help but feel that it was a pity that he could not see the rest of the battle. He only felt that he had yet to satisfy his curiosity, and his heart was itching.

If he could watch the entire battle between the two Transcendent Grades, his chances of entering the realm would be higher…

Just as he was secretly feeling regretful, a strange feeling suddenly surfaced in his heart. It was an indescribable feeling as if he had lost something.

"Strange…"

This feeling came and went very quickly. Wuornos pressed on his chest, somewhat confused.

Before he could think about it, the officer beside him suddenly exclaimed.

Wuornos turned around and saw Black Star, who had disappeared for a long time, appearing on the battlefield once again. This immediately caused a change in the situation.

The fifth layer of the World Tree's defense circle was right where the two of them had disappeared. A smattering of green light suddenly burst out, and a huge figure flew out. It was Han Xiao's Supreme Heavenly Venerate.

"Black Star is back!"

The Galactic Alliance Army was overjoyed. They opened their eyes wide and waited for the Tree God to appear.

However, the next moment, the green light exploded and turned into light fragments. The Tree God did not come out. It was as if he had really disappeared.

"Where's the Tree God? Where did he go?"

Many of them were excited, beginning to come out with conjectures.

Before they could ask, Han Xiao connected to the combat channel again and confirmed their guess.

"I've already gotten rid of the Tree God. He won't stop us anymore. Continue attacking!"

Han Xiao exhaled.

Seeing that the battlefield was still in a stalemate, he was relieved. He was afraid that if he was held back by the Tree God for too long, something might happen on the battlefield.

He did not waste any time. He continued to rush toward the World Tree's main body without hesitation. He bore the brunt of the enemy's attacks and entered the defense circle alone.

Seeing that Han Xiao did not mention anything about the battle, although they were curious, they did not ask too much. To them, knowing the outcome was enough.

"Follow Black Star!"

"Victory belongs to us!"

The Galactic Alliance Army was motivated. Their uneasiness was gone, and they followed closely behind, launching even more ferocious attacks.

Han Xiao had thought that after the Tree God died in battle, the morale of the World Tree Family would be low and they would be defeated. However, to his surprise, the result was the opposite.

Not only did the World Tree team not retreat, but their counterattack was even more intense. They abandoned all their worries and fought with their backs to the wall.

The casualties were extremely tragic, but the World Tree Blessed Race did not retreat even in the face of death. The fleets on the periphery abandoned their formation lines one after another and teleported to the fifth layer of defense. They charged toward Han Xiao like moths to a flame, using their lives to build a barrier to slow him down at all costs.

In fact, all the members of the World Tree saw the entire process of the Tree God resisting Black Star through the mental network.

Every time the Tree God exploded with power, everyone knew what price the Ancestral Tree King had paid. Seeing the Tree King, who usually only dwelled in the King City risking his life at all costs, countless members of the World Tree felt the same and encouraged him anxiously, hoping that the Tree God would defeat Black Star with his burst of strength.

However, the high hopes that they had all turned into disbelief. Seeing that the Ancestral Tree King had paid such a huge price only to be completely killed by Han Xiao, a huge sense of tragedy crashed into the hearts of all the World Tree members, leaving only despair.

All the members of the World Tree understood that there was no one who could stop Black Star. However, this triggered their final determination.

As the saying went, a cornered soldier will find all means to win. The morale of the World Tree Blessed Race did not decline but instead increased exponentially. No one gave up, and everyone was willing to die together with the enemy.

If they could not rely on the Tree God, they could only rely on themselves!

All the fear and confusion disappeared, leaving only the determination to die. This was the final counterattack of a civilization at its end!

Hong Long Long~

The densely packed battleships blocked the path ahead. Han Xiao attacked time and time again. The flashes of his blades and artillery could shatter a large number of battleships with every attack. However, there were people filling up the gaps, and it was difficult to clear a path.

Continuous high-density explosions surrounded him, and Han Xiao felt as though he was stuck in a swamp. The concentrated attacks coming from the front even exceeded the pressure that the Tree God gave him.

"What a stubborn civilization…"

Han Xiao was also slightly moved. Although they were opponents, he had to admit that the tenacity displayed by the World Tree Civilization exceeded his previous judgment.

In his previous life, even the galactic society that was united against the outside world was weaker than the World Tree fleet. In the final battle, the World Tree fleet did not show such determination either.

"Although the World Tree is a deformed civilization, in terms of unity and cohesion, they probably won't find any similar opponent in the entire universe…"

Han Xiao shook his head.

He appreciated the World Tree's desperate struggle, but unfortunately, without the Tree God, the World Tree could no longer stop him. All of this was futile.

Han Xiao turned around and looked at the large group of Beyond Grade As behind him.

This hint made all the Beyond Grade As understand. They spread out and formed a loose formation in front of the various armies.

If one did not look closely, they would not be able to notice that the formation was like a net, trapping the fleet at the front.

The victory was already decided. The problem now was to pick peaches… no, to prevent others from picking peaches.

Seeing this, Han Xiao turned around and activated a Character Summon Card.

"Golden Ring" Oulou Character Summon Card—[Golden Treasure Ship—Collision]!

Dense streams of light suddenly appeared on the body of the Supreme Heavenly Venerate. He adjusted his direction before suddenly taking a step forward and charging toward the World Tree's main body!

The World Tree fleet in front of them could not withstand it at all. Their shields shattered one after another, and debris flew everywhere!

The Supreme Heavenly Venerate was like a gigantic golden meteor that pierced through the final defensive perimeter and crashed heavily into the World Tree.

Bang!

Countless roots seemed to have been struck by lightning. With a sudden roll, the entire space of the dimension started to tremble!

"Let me see what exactly you are made of!"

Han Xiao hooked his finger and inserted it into the tree.

At this moment, the World Tree's main body, which seemed to have been waiting for death, finally revealed its secret card!

Buzz!

In an instant, the consciousness of all the World Tree members turned into a terrifying mental impact that had never been seen before. It rushed toward Han Xiao's brain through the energy link channel.

The impact was so strong that even if all the Beyond Grade As in the galactic society joined forces to resist it, their minds would be shattered in a single breath!

The main body of the World Tree was not completely powerless. When both parties built a physical or energy connection, she would be able to launch a psychic attack on the target. This was because only by invading the world tree with energy could they form a soul connection with her and take the initiative to turn her into a controlled Universal Treasure. This was her trump card to protect herself from being enslaved by others!

However, at this moment, Han Xiao unveiled another Character Summon Card without hesitation.

"Underworld" Onicelu Character Summon Card—[Thousand Soul Stream]!

Immunity to all mental attacks!

In his mind, the destructive Psychic Current bombarded Han Xiao's spiritual body, but it was like a breeze, not causing any damage. Instead, it turned into pure energy and was absorbed by Han Xiao.

"I've been waiting for this… Come and meet your natural enemy!"

Han Xiao's eyes lit up. The next moment, a translucent snake shot out from between his brows, and its body expanded at an unbelievable speed.

The Pivotal Snake had already turned into a Virtual Life Form, and its size in the physical world could be shrunk at will. In the blink of an eye, it became the size of the World Tree. It coiled around the World Tree's body, opened its mouth, and bit down without hesitation.

With this bite, the Pivotal Snake and the World Tree's main body finally established a bridge of information, and countless information streams were exchanged rapidly.

Buzz—

The entire World Tree trembled violently, as though a person was struggling in pain, causing the space to shake violently!

In order to subdue the World Tree, Han Xiao had naturally come prepared. Building a soul connection was only one of the reasons. The biggest problem was actually to destroy the resistance of the World Tree, and his trump card was the Pivotal Snake.

After the Pivot turned into a Virtual Life Form, it automatically awakened a new ability, which was why it was the World Tree's natural enemy. The World Tree's independent consciousness was its food!

Only then did Han Xiao understand the significance of the Pivotal Snake. It could turn the World Tree from a special life form into an unconscious Universal Treasure!

It was because of this trump card that Han Xiao finally made up his mind to carry out the plan to subdue the World Tree. He would not do anything that he was not confident of!

Chapter 1441: Uneven Distribution of the Spoils

Crack!

The gigantic Pivotal Snake coiled around the World Tree and bit it.

Although it was only an illusory Virtual Life Form and could not harm physical objects, the Pivotal Snake's method of harming the World Tree was an Information Form channel that only targeted the Mother Tree's will.

The World Tree's main body struggled frantically, trying to break free from the Pivotal Snake. However, the waving roots could not touch the Pivotal Snake's virtual body at all.

Although the World Tree was strong, the reason why the Pivotal Snake was its natural enemy was because of its unresolvable restraint. The will of the Mother Tree did not have the time to care about Han Xiao, and the mental shock was immediately silenced. It was held up by the Pivotal Snake and struggled non-stop, like a young girl anxiously grabbing her clothes and not letting anyone strip her naked.

An endless stream of machinery poured out from the Godly Stronghold and fused into the Supreme Heavenly Venerate, causing Han Xiao's body to expand rapidly. His arms could gradually wrap around the trunk as though he was going to uproot the World Tree.

While the mother tree's will was in chaos, Han Xiao did not hesitate to use his energy to infiltrate the World Tree's body and attempt to form a Soul Connection, dyeing the other party with his own color and turning it into his own shape.

To the members of the World Tree Family, this feeling was akin to having their faith insulted. Countless people charged toward Han Xiao with bloodshot eyes, and batches of them were destroyed midway.

Because of Han Xiao's actions, the World Tree fleet was inevitably thrown into chaos. The galactic alliance army naturally would not let go of such a good opportunity. The fleet quickly penetrated the defensive perimeter and reached the fourth layer very quickly, suffering an even more intense counterattack.

The troops at the front were not far from Han Xiao, and they all provided firepower support to help him intercept the World Tree's troops. Energy beams shot everywhere, detonating a series of battleships on the battlefield.

On the other side, seeing that Black Star had successfully arrived beside the World Tree's main body, the commanders in the strategic command center were excited.

"Good! Black Star has already stepped on the World Tree Civilization's weakness!"

"We'll have to rely on him to destroy the World Tree's main body. We have to protect him and let him focus on dealing with the World Tree."

"Even at a conservative estimate, our chances of winning are more than 95%!"

"The World Tree has no chance of turning the tables!"

The officers were excited.

The goal of the three Universal Civilizations in starting this battle was to eliminate the enemy in one fell swoop, hoping to finish everything. Thus, they had gathered most of the forces of the explored universe. Although it could not be said that it was to the extent of win or die trying, if they lost this war, the three Universal Civilizations would also suffer heavy losses, and the gains would not make up for the losses. Therefore, before going out to war, many officers had made a military pledge that they would only win and not lose.

However, the officers did not want to lie to themselves. Their confidence came from Black Star and the Pivotal Snake. If they did not have such a trump card, they would not have dared to say they would definitely win.

Seeing that Black Star had killed the Tree God, broken through the encirclement, and was uprooting the mother tree, almost single-handedly pushing the battle forward, everyone heaved a sigh of relief. They felt that they trusted the right person… As expected, this war was still being carried by Black Star.

However, the leaders of the three Universal Civilizations were not happy at all. Instead, their expressions were solemn, as though they had some concerns.

The Pope hesitated for a moment before speaking.

"Why do I feel like Black Star isn't destroying the main body of the World Tree?"

Hearing this, the officers were stunned. They suppressed the joy in their hearts and carefully observed Han Xiao's actions toward the World Tree. The more they looked, the stranger they felt.

"That does seem to be the case… He is not continuing to attack, more like he is subduing the World Tree's main body… Is he trying to control the World Tree ‽"

Everyone was shocked and understood that the situation had become complicated.

The officers turned around, and as expected, the expressions of the three leaders became extremely ugly.

"What a great Black Star! I knew he had other plans. Isn't he afraid of dying from overeating ‽"

Louis was furious.

"Our worries were right. He used us to defeat the World Tree's troops and create an opportunity for him to subdue the World Tree's main body. We can't let him achieve his goal!"

The Pope was furious.

The World Tree was too powerful. No matter where it landed, it was a threat to the three Universal Civilizations. The three Universal Civilizations only wanted to destroy it, and they did not even dare to take the risk of capturing it.

Black Star was already an existence beyond the norm, and the three Universal Civilizations could no longer control him. If Black Star was to obtain the World Tree, he would be a threat to them. It would be equivalent to him obtaining a Universal Civilization, and he would be able to rival the entire explored universe. In fact, he might even surpass them to a certain extent. It would be enough to shake the foundation of their rule!

Although the internal conflicts were temporarily suppressed by the invasion of the enemy, the three Universal Civilizations did not forget the fear of losing control over the individual strengths. They still had conflicts with Black Star that were difficult to reconcile. Once the war ended, these problems would surface again, so the three of them would not watch the Beyond Grade As control the World Tree.

Furthermore, the war had been going on for more than ten years, and the three Universal Civilizations were the main victims. They had wasted so much time in the war and lost countless resources. Now that they were finally going to reap the fruits of their labor, they naturally did not want to let Han Xiao steal their fruits.

We were the ones who mobilized the army to resist the World Tree, and we suffered the most losses. However, we created an opportunity for the other in the end. Who can tolerate this!

Even if Black Star's contribution was high, they could not allow him!

In the eyes of the three of them, Black Star was showing his true intentions.

Fighting against the enemy together was just an excuse on the surface. Black Star's real goal was to use the galactic society's troops to obtain the World Tree for himself!

The three of them actually had some guesses about Han Xiao's selfishness, but it was useless. The war still depended on Black Star, and it was almost certain that they would reach this stage.

"We can't let Black Star succeed."

"Then what should we do? Are we going to fire at Black Star?"

"Are you crazy? We haven't even won yet, and you still dare to have internal strife in front of such a powerful enemy? What are you thinking ‽"

The officers were agitated and started arguing.

Simon made a prompt decision and shouted, "Inform the direct troops of the three Universal Civilizations to stop providing cover fire to Black Star and attack the World Tree's main body. We must blow it up before Black Star succeeds!"

They had to stop Han Xiao, but they could not turn against him. Thus, they could only change their tactics temporarily and race Black Star for time to destroy the target.

However, everyone knew that the World Tree fleet would definitely protect the mother tree and stop their firepower. Furthermore, it was impossible for Black Star to not be prepared, so he had definitely taken some measures to stop them.

"It all depends on human effort…"

This thought flashed through the minds of many of the officers. Their faces were stiff, and their attitudes were not optimistic.

The order was quickly passed down. The direct troops of the three Universal Civilizations did not think too much about it and immediately fired at the World Tree itself. However, most of the attacks were stopped by the World Tree fleet halfway.

Just as the three Universal Civilizations' fleets did this, the Black Star Army and all the other Beyond Grade A organizations also reacted. They immediately started to slack off and moved around to block the attacks of the three Universal Civilizations.

The members of the Beyond Grade A Association also started to move. Some of them deliberately guided the World Tree fleet to attack the direct troops of the three Universal Civilizations through various positions, while others activated their AOE fighting style that did not differentiate between friend and foe. They attacked the enemy and the three Universal Civilizations together, indirectly disrupting the three Universal Civilizations' formation.

Because many of their 'allies' were causing trouble, the coordination of the Galactic Alliance Army was disrupted. Their attacks suddenly slowed down, and their advancement became stagnant. They were dragged into the chaotic battle by the berserk World Tree fleet and could not withdraw for a while.

"Damn it!"

The Pope was furious. He wanted to punch the table, but the remote projection could not touch the real thing. His fist passed through the table.

"I told you Black Star was prepared."

Marbruce also had an unfriendly expression.

Both parties were aware of their respective goals and were obstructing each other, but on the surface, they still had to pretend to fight together as if all their actions were focused on attacking the World Tree. This situation could be said to be hiding different purposes behind the semblance of the accord.

The three leaders did not want to go against the others and affect the war, but they felt that they had no choice.

Due to the conflict between the two sides, the galactic alliance army had split into three parties. One was the three Universal Civilizations' direct troops that wanted to destroy World Tree's main body, and the other was the Beyond Grade A forces who provided cover for Black Star and obstructed the three Universal Civilizations.

The final party was the remaining allied forces who were fighting seriously and were shocked by the 'chaos' on the two sides. They did not know what was going on. Why did the other two suddenly drag each other down?

The galactic alliance army was in chaos, but the conflict between the three Universal Civilizations and the Beyond Grade A organizations did not affect Han Xiao's process of subduing the World Tree.

Han Xiao's energy continued to seep into the depths of the World Tree's main body. The will of the Mother Tree had already been completely destroyed by the Pivotal Snake, and there was no way to stop his assault.

Amidst the spiritual entanglement, illusions flashed past Han Xiao's eyes, and he saw the history of the World Tree's growth.

When it was weak, it was worshiped by certain races and was offered all kinds of sacrifices. The will of the Mother Tree slowly took shape during this process, providing convenience to the races under them while guiding them to expand outward.

After completing the accumulation, the World Tree then embarked on the bloody path of rising up, becoming a Universal Predator. One race after another became vassals, and civilizations became food. Gradually, it started to grow, and its abilities became richer and richer.

Countless memories appeared before Han Xiao's eyes. In a daze, he seemed to see a small tree sprout growing rapidly, eventually covering the sun and standing on top of the starry sky. Countless wormholes appeared between the tree branches, each leading to a different world. Endless cosmic radiation storms swept past, but it was like a breeze, only able to make the lush leaves sway slightly. Trillions of Blessed Race and Believers were spread out on the roots, worshipping sincerely. This scene gave off a majestic and mysterious feeling.

Buzz!

Suddenly, Han Xiao's eyes cleared, and he stepped out of the illusion. A new existence had appeared in his senses. It was the World Tree that had successfully formed the Soul Connection.

At this moment, the will of the mother tree finally reached its limit, and it was completely devoured by the Pivotal Snake.

The next moment, the World Tree's main body stopped struggling and lost any ability to move independently, turning into a dead object.

Han Xiao's body trembled, and a stream of information flowed into his mind. It contained the various abilities of the World Tree, as well as the control rights.

Although the authority of the Tree Kings was high, they were still the subordinates of the World Tree, while Han Xiao's authority was above the Mother Tree and was not under any restrictions.

The surging new energy flowed into Han Xiao's body through the soul connection, providing him with a new enhancement, pushing his energy level up.

Hiss…

Han Xiao could not help but take a deep breath. His entire body was filled with energy.

Just as he was about to take back the Pivotal Snake, he realized that the Pivotal Snake did not stop. Instead, it dived into the World Tree and merged into it.

Han Xiao looked at the interface and saw a new suffix in the name of the World Tree.

[World Tree (Complete Form)]!

"Hmm? Could it be that the Pivotal Snake was not only a natural enemy, but it could also fuse with the World Tree and complete it?"

Han Xiao was shocked.

This ability did not appear on the attribute panel of the Pivotal Snake. He had only seen it now.

Just as the Pivotal Snake fused into the World Tree, Han Xiao noticed a change. He had just formed a Soul Connection with the World Tree, and it was only the shallowest layer. It was still very weak, but at this moment, the Soul Connection was suddenly strengthened, and it became many times stronger.

If his previous invasion progress on the World Tree was 10%, it was now more than 80%!

"Could it be that the Pivotal Snake can help the controller better control the World Tree?"

Han Xiao's heart skipped a beat.

Suppressing the surprise in his heart, Han Xiao felt the power of the World Tree. He could not be more satisfied. The World Tree's independent will had been cleared, and it had become a tool without any thoughts. It was completely controlled by him and could be used at ease.

Due to the devouring and conversion characteristics, the World Tree could be regarded as a growth type of Universal Treasure. However, he did not need to start from zero because the World Tree had already matured. Controlling it was equivalent to gaining the loyalty of the entire World Tree Civilization!

The power of this thing was countless times more terrifying than the inheritance of the Underworld that Hila and Aurora had!

"Cannot blame the three Universal Civilizations for wanting to destroy my goal…"

Han Xiao turned to look at the battlefield. His eyes flashed, and he suddenly activated the authority of the World Tree to recall all the World Tree fleets.

The World Tree fleet, which had been fighting back fearlessly a second ago, suddenly stopped fighting. Without saying a word, they turned around and flew into the roots, turning back into their information form and entering the mother tree world.

For a moment, the battlefield was much emptier, and only the galactic alliance army was left.

Originally, the members of the World Tree were all filled with the desire to fight to the death. However, the moment the will of the mother tree disappeared and Han Xiao replaced the control, everyone's hostility disappeared. Just as they were feeling lost, a new mission arrived. They would not disobey the orders of the World Tree and immediately ceased fire and retreated.

"No matter how tragic the counterattack was, they were just a bunch of puppets. With the owner changed, they have to listen obediently…"

Seeing this, Han Xiao sighed.

However, sympathy was sympathy, and he would not foolishly let the World Tree Civilization go free. This was the World Tree's own foundation.

Seeing that the enemies had left, the galactic alliance army was stunned. They then looked at Han Xiao beside the tree and were overjoyed.

"We won ‽"

"We're still alive!"

"Hahahaha—I knew I could trust Black Star!"

Countless soldiers were overjoyed, and the atmosphere of excitement and surprise quickly spread throughout the entire army. Every combat channel was filled with wild cheers, and even many players who had yet to spend all their revivals were affected and cheered along.

However, when most of the fleets stopped firing, the direct troops of the three Universal Civilizations still did not stop firing at the World Tree itself.

Without the obstruction of the World Tree fleet, the direct troops of the three Universal Civilizations had a clear way. This scene immediately caused the cheers to stop, attracting the shocked gazes of countless comrades.

"Oh? You still haven't given up. Do you want to pretend you know nothing and try to destroy the World Tree one last time while I haven't notified you?"

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes. He knew what the three Universal Civilizations were thinking.

He suddenly waved his hand, and a thick psionic barrier surrounded the World Tree to block the attacks of the fleet.

At the same time, Han Xiao shouted in the channel.

"You can stop the fire. I've controlled the World Tree."

After waiting for a few seconds, the Pope's solemn voice suddenly sounded in the channel.

"Since that's the case, let's destroy it. It's still a threat to the world!"

"There's no need. I've already subdued the World Tree."

"It's not enough! Only by destroying it will we be able to completely eliminate the hidden threat! Even if it's you, we won't be at ease!"

"Do you want to cast us aside so soon?" Han Xiao said with a smile that was not a smile.

"You're mistaken. We're only doing this to maintain the peace of the galaxy. No one in the galactic society wants to face such a disaster again!" the Pope said with a deep voice.

Han Xiao shook his head. "Stop it. Don't make the situation too ugly. We just won. Do you want the other allies to see our internal strife?"

Before the Pope could reply, Marbruce interrupted.

"Black Star, this is the only thing we can't compromise on! You're the one who should stop. You've already made enough contributions, don't be stubborn! Let go, you're still the Universe's Hero of the Final War!"

"Looks like you won't regret it until things are too late…"

Han Xiao shook his head.

As soon as he finished speaking, the expressions of the three leaders and the officers turned grave.

They knew that Black Star would not give up so easily, and they were already prepared for a conflict to break out. However, their goal was only to get rid of the World Tree's main body. Although they were suspected of burning the bridge after crossing it, their goal to get rid of the hidden threat could be accepted by others. In their opinion, if Black Star went on a killing spree against them, it would definitely incur the wrath of the masses. The reputation that he had accumulated during the war would immediately collapse, and the allies of the other civilizations present would also stand on their side to resist Black Star together.

Thus, despite being nervous, the three of them were not afraid of Black Star fighting back. In fact, they were even looking forward to this development.

However, the next moment, the three of them widened their eyes.

Han Xiao did not make a move. Instead, he raised his hand and patted the World Tree. The huge World Tree shrank rapidly and turned into a green stream of light that flew into Han Xiao's palm, disappearing in front of everyone.

"This…"

Marbruce and the other two were stunned.

The battle with the World Tree fleet previously had given them the impression that the mother tree could not move, so they felt that they had the upper hand. Thus, the three of them would rather take the risk of angering Black Star and gather their forces to destroy the World Tree.

However, the three of them did not expect Black Star to be able to store the World Tree and do something that the World Tree Blessed Race could not. They could not react in time. What was there to destroy now?

In fact, Han Xiao could not do this in the beginning. It was all due to the Pivotal Snake strengthening his Soul Connection exponentially, crossing many stages. This allowed him to unlock more functions, including putting the World Tree into the Transcendent's inner space.

Strictly speaking, the inner space was also a type of secondary dimension. It could also allow the World Tree to take root in it. This way, the inner space would receive a huge enhancement and become extremely tough. Furthermore, there was no need to care about the weakness of the enemy targeting the World Tree's main body. It was equivalent to carrying the mother tree with him. It was very convenient.

Han Xiao had originally planned to use other methods to force the three Universal Civilizations to stop, but the direct conflict was unavoidable, and it would damage his reputation more or less. However, with this new ability, he changed his plan at the last minute and made the three Universal Civilizations lose their target. This would save him a lot of effort.

Just as the three leaders were at a loss, Han Xiao's remote projection appeared in the strategic command center.

"What do the three of you say now?"

The faces of Marbruce and the other two flickered. They did not respond.

Only when the World Tree's main body was exposed in front of the army would they have a chance. There was no chance now. As for letting Black Star take the initiative to hand it over… the three of them knew it. No matter how arrogant they were, they did not think that they had that much face.

"Black Star, you've succeeded. You must be very happy now…"

Marbruce had a complicated expression on his face. His tone was bitter, and there was a hint of unwillingness and mockery.

"Yes, I am indeed very happy. The war has finally ended, and everyone is cheering. Are you not happy about this?" Han Xiao raised his brows.

The three of them had solemn expressions.

It would be weird if we were happy. Who knows if we have just left the tiger's den but entered the wolf's den again…

Seeing this, Han Xiao smiled and did not continue teasing them.

Since he had already taken advantage of them, there was no need for him to pretend to be innocent. There would be plenty of time for him to settle scores in the future. He did not plan to argue with the three of them about what had happened just now. This was not the right time.

This time, Han Xiao changed the topic and said, "Alright, let's not talk anymore. Let's get down to business. I have a plan, and I hope you guys can cooperate."

"…What plan?"

The three of them were surprised.

We just won, what is Black Star planning?

"Don't leak the news of us defeating the World Tree Civilization. This Galactic Alliance Army's composition is complicated. It's best to control them for the time being."

"Er… what are you planning?" Marbruce was confused.

Han Xiao smiled and said,

"Haven't you guys been trying to find out who leaked the information? I said it was a third party, but you guys just don't believe me. I just happened to obtain the Information Form Warning Network technology from the World Tree. I don't have to explain the effects. You guys have already experienced it. This way, you might be able to find traces of a third party. What do you guys think?"

The eyes of the trio lit up.

Chapter 1442: Further Scheme. The Things Are Still There, but Men Are No More the Same Ones.

This proposal was very constructive, and the three leaders immediately took it seriously. After pondering for a while, they quickly came to a conclusion with Han Xiao and told the strategic command center to call back the three Universal Civilizations' direct troops.

Their goal was to destroy the World Tree, not to fall out with Black Star. Although they were not willing to let Han Xiao subdue the World Tree, there was nothing they could do.

Marbruce and the others could only suppress the fear in their hearts and wait for a targeted plan to be discussed in the future. In any case, there was nothing they could do now. They could not really start the second round of the war with Black Star… Who wins and who loses was secondary. There was a third party who might still be eyeing them from the dark.

Even if they were going to fall out with each other, they should at least wait until they had a direct descendant of the Transcendent Grade. Wuornos was their greatest hope, and he might advance one day.

The direct troops of the three Universal Civilizations stopped firing and silently withdrew from the encirclement. The tension on the battlefield quickly dissipated.

The brief confrontation between Han Xiao and the three Universal Civilizations had stunned the soldiers of the Galactic Alliance Army. They realized that the conflict between the two sides had reemerged, and they were extremely nervous. They were afraid that an internal conflict would break out as soon as they won.

Seeing that both sides had stopped fighting, countless people heaved a sigh of relief. They only felt that their emotions were in turmoil, and their entire bodies felt a little weak. No matter what kind of conflict there was, the three Universal Civilizations were the main force in resisting the World Tree, and Black Star was the hero who changed the battle. They were all heroes in the war. They had just joined forces to defeat the foreign enemy, and now they were turning against each other in front of everyone. It was hard to accept. No one wished for their joy to turn into sorrow.

However, the World Tree was not destroyed but subdued by Black Star. This reality made many people feel strange.

Although Black Star had contributed too much to the war, this last wave made them feel like Black Star was using them to achieve his goal… Of course, there might be a reason for Black Star's actions, but the impression he gave everyone was still rather complicated.

However, they did not think too much about it and quickly threw this thought into the back of their minds.

The conflict between Black Star and the three Universal Civilizations was a conflict between the big shots, and it was not their place to worry. At this moment, these front-line combatants only wanted to enjoy the joy of victory and the joy of surviving the calamity.

"We won!"

"Long Live the Dynasty!"

For a moment, the cheers of countless soldiers echoed in the combat channels.

The officers did not stop them and allowed their soldiers to vent their emotions. In reality, they were also excited and could not help but celebrate with their subordinates.

On the other side, Han Xiao deactivated the Supreme Heavenly Venerate and retracted his troops. He passed through the direct troops of the three Universal Civilizations that had given up on stopping him and returned to the army formation of the Beyond Grade A organizations. Many Beyond Grade As immediately surrounded him.

"That was close. I thought the three Universal Civilizations were going to act arbitrarily and start a civil war."

Sun Hunter wiped his non-existent cold sweat.

Kasuyi casually analyzed, "That won't happen. They still have a very good understanding of the situation. We're clearly on Black Star's side, and Black Star has the World Tree Civilization's troops. The three Universal Civilizations won't dare act recklessly. They know what the outcome will be, and they won't seek their own death."

"Speaking of which, Your Excellency Black Star took too big of a risk this time. We didn't know about your plans before this…"

Some of them mumbled softly, and many of the association members looked at Han Xiao with strange looks. These people did not know about this beforehand.

Because there were spies from the Super Star Cluster in the association, Han Xiao did not want to leak the news in advance. Therefore, he only told Kasuyi and his confidants about his plan to subdue the World Tree, and he told the entire association to prevent the three Universal Civilizations from trying to get the World Tree.

Therefore, not long ago, a portion of the association members was still in the dark. Even if they had doubts, they did not confirm it. They could only follow the original plan and work together with their teammates to create obstacles for the direct troops of the three Universal Civilizations, giving Han Xiao time and creating opportunities.

To be honest, if Han Xiao had stated his goal of subduing the World Tree from the start, many Beyond Grade As would not have been willing to help him. They would have been like the three Universal Civilizations, more inclined to completely destroy the World Tree. After all, the World Tree was quite similar to the Underworld, but its power was much higher. It could control an individual's thoughts. Even if Black Star was 'one of them' for the time being, who knew what the future would be like?

If one day, Black Star's ambition reached its peak and he wished to use the World Tree to devour everyone, what would they do? They did not think this was improbable, killing intent would rise when one held a sharp knife. Black Star had no such thoughts in the past because he did not have the World Tree. Many Beyond Grade As had to consider their own safety and were secretly afraid.

Seeing the complicated expressions of many Beyond Grade As, Han Xiao did not mind. He smiled and said,

"Everyone, there's no need to worry. I subdued the World Tree because of other considerations. One of my intentions is to make use of the World Tree's power to make the three Universal Civilizations hesitate and consolidate the safety of our Beyond Grade A Association after the war. This way, we can completely make the three Universal Civilizations give up on suppressing us. Only then can we put down all our worries."

Manison nodded slowly and agreed.

"This is similar to my original plan. However, we were not strong enough back then, and it was not the right time. My idea was too far ahead. Now that our forces are expanding rapidly through the war, the time is ripe. The strategic significance of the World Tree is actually the same as the Virtual Mutiny Virus, but it is more suitable as a strategic deterrence weapon so that the three Universal Civilizations will no longer dare to attack us."

Manison then gave Han Xiao an appreciative look, as though saying 'we are indeed the same type of people.'

He was also afraid of Han Xiao's threat after obtaining the World Tree, but if he was in that position, Manison would have made the same choice. The situation now was similar to when he snatched the 'Virtual Mutiny Virus'. However, he had failed, and Black Star had succeeded.

Upon hearing this, some of the association members could not say anything no matter how unhappy they were. It was mainly because what was done was done. There was no point in objecting.

Seeing this, Aurora changed the topic and said with a smile, "We won this war. Everyone, be happy."

Hearing this, everyone relaxed and smiled… No matter what, now was the time to enjoy the victory, they still had to give face to the healer.

"We've finally dealt with this powerful enemy. We can take a break now."

"Heh, I've been exhausted all these years. Don't wake me up until I've slept for a month."

"After enduring the tough times, a beautiful tomorrow is waiting for us."

The Beyond Grade As were relieved of their burdens and chatted with each other.

At this moment, someone thought of something.

"By the way, Black Star, when do you plan to revive the recently killed Beyond Grade As?"

In the past year of the war, a few more Beyond Grade As had died in battle. Han Xiao had yet to revive them, and their names were still on the Soul Comfort Monument.

"After some time, I still have some things to do, so I can't leave for the time being, especially when it comes to the establishment of a civilization… The timing, location, and people are all in our hands. I've convinced the three Universal Civilizations to temporarily track down a third party. Taking advantage of this buffer time, we'll let our people complete the final preparations for the transformation of the association. When the time comes, everything will be in place."

Han Xiao replied casually.

He took out the technology of the Information Form Warning Network and convinced the three Universal Civilizations to search for a third party. On one hand, he did not want the enemy to continue hiding and benefit from it. On the other hand, he also temporarily shifted the focus of the three Universal Civilizations and bought time for the final stage of preparations for the transformation of the association into a Civilization.

The two plans were carried out side by side, killing two birds with one stone. This way, he would be busy, and he had to hurry up. For the time being, he did not have the time to study how to complete the Virtual Creation.

However, when talking about the Sanctum Revival, Han Xiao thought about the problem of the Iteration.

He had once planned to reveal the information about the Sanctum to the three Universal Civilizations when the time was right, and they would work together to figure out how to survive the Iteration. In the past, the time was not ripe, but now that the World Tree was in his hands, he truly had the foundation to work together as an equal. This plan could also be officially put on the agenda.

If he remembered correctly, there should still be a related mission in his interface.

Because of the World Tree's alchemy-like material transformation ability, he did not have to bother collecting the materials for the Sanctum Key in the future and could create a new key at any time. To him, most of the Sanctums were a backyard that he could enter as he wished, so he was not afraid of the three Universal Civilizations studying the Sanctum together. The other party did not have such a unique condition.

"This is really the case of overwhelming advantage…"

Han Xiao was secretly overjoyed.

With the World Tree Mechanism working together with the Sanctum, the benefits were unimaginable.

He inwardly decided that once the situation stabilized after the war, he would show his cards to the three Universal Civilizations and pull them to study the Sanctum together.

Rather than letting these people spend their energy on how to deal with them, it would be better to let them figure out how to deal with the problem of Iteration, lest they waste resources for internal conflicts.

'My actions will definitely move the Galaxy…'

Han Xiao shook his head.

For the sake of the peace of the universe, I am really giving it my all. It's not right for me not to receive a few tons of medals.

This time, Ames came over with a strange expression. "You've made a huge profit this time. The entire galactic society suffered heavy losses in the war, and trillions died in the war. In the end, you became the biggest beneficiary. What do you think?"

"What? Are you trying to wake up my sense of shame? You've found the wrong person." Han Xiao shrugged and said calmly, "I ended the war early and saved countless lives. The dead are gone, and the living are still alive. What do I think? I have a clear conscience."

Ames spread out her hands. "Alright, there's nothing wrong with thinking this way. After this war, you will be extremely respected, so you won't be as busy as before, right? How about it, make some time to accompany me?"

Han Xiao was tempted.

But at this time, Jotina suddenly appeared and interrupted.

"Lord Dragon Emperor, the Army Commander doesn't have that much free time. Don't keep pestering him. It will only make him troubled."

Hearing this, Ames raised her brows and looked over. Jotina did not back down and glared back. Their gazes met in midair, and the air was filled with the smell of gunpowder.

Han Xiao felt a wave of killing intent, and his mouth could not help but twitch. He quickly flew to the side, not wanting to be involved in the battle between the two women.

The two of them glared at each other. One side was calm and dignified, while the other side was aggressive. There was a clear provocation in their eyes, and neither side backed down. No one cared about Han Xiao running away.

"Sigh, it's all my fault for being too outstanding…"

Han Xiao sighed helplessly.

He flew to the side alone and thought for a while before taking out the Heart Tree King's Spacetime Amber.

After obtaining the World Tree, Han Xiao had completely understood the mechanisms of the Tree King and the Tree God. He realized that the Ancestral Tree King had left him a mess.

The Beyonder's Vestiges were completely burned, the Crowns were completely destroyed, and their military strength was greatly depleted. The high-level combatants were almost completely wiped out, and the World Tree Civilization had suffered great losses. It would take many years for them to recover.

However, Han Xiao did not mind. After all, if he had not beaten the enemy into such a miserable state, he would not have had the chance to subdue the World Tree.

However, Han Xiao originally had an idea. If the timing and price were suitable, it was not impossible to sell Wuornos a Beyonder's Vestige in the future.

Now, he had no way to give it to Wuornos even if he wanted to. Wuornos had once again missed the opportunity to advance to the Transcendent Grade. Han Xiao could only say that it was destiny…

"Right now, the only undamaged Tree King Crown is on the Heart Tree King. This guy has become my only heir…"

Han Xiao shook his head and laughed.

Although the members of the World Tree were brainwashed and loyal, they were not puppets without self-awareness. They had independent thoughts and had their own lives. His entry into the World Tree Civilization did not affect these things. In a way that was easy to understand, his control of the World Tree was equivalent to using his own will to replace the will of the mother tree. To the World Tree Civilization, the two had similar meanings.

Therefore, Han Xiao also needed to find someone to manage the World Tree Civilization. Due to the 'waste' of the Ancestral Tree King, for a very long time, the World Tree would only have one Tree King qualification. The Heart Tree King was the best choice.

With this in mind, Han Xiao did not hesitate and unsealed the Amber.

Pop!

The Heart Tree King broke free from the seal and retreated without another word. His body glowed, and he was about to self-destruct.

After being trapped in the Spacetime Amber for so many years, the Heart Tree King had always regretted not being decisive enough. He had told himself countless times that as long as there was a chance to unseal it, he would immediately free himself.

However, just as he was about to self-destruct, the mental network of the World Tree connected to him again. The message that came made the Heart Tree King suddenly stop moving, and his expression became extremely shocked.

"The World Tree Civilization… lost ‽"

He quickly received the information in his mental network and finally understood how the war had progressed while he had been sealed for all these years.

"The Ancestral Tree King, the Secret Tree King, the Fortitude Tree King, and the Subduing Tree King… They all died, along with the Tree King Crowns. I became the Tree King that survived in the end…"

Just like that, the World Tree Army, which was at its peak, was wiped out. His familiar comrades were all wiped out, and even the entire civilization belonged to someone else. They had a new master… After more than ten years, everything had changed.

For a moment, the Heart Tree King was stunned on the spot. His heart was filled with complicated emotions.

Han Xiao did not interfere with the Heart Tree King's acceptance of reality.

"I'm sure you already understand why I let you out. I need you to help me manage the World Tree Civilization. It might not be a bad thing for you. As long as you do a good job, you will be the only Tree King for a long period of time. I will not interfere too much with your management. You will only be below me and above all others."

The Heart Tree King looked at Han Xiao with a complicated expression.

He did not expect that the moment he woke up, the culprit who had sealed him back then would become his boss. Due to the mind control of the World Tree, the Heart Tree King could not show any hostility toward Han Xiao.

"…I understand. As you wish."

The Heart Tree King sighed and lowered his head to agree. He had no right to refuse.

Han Xiao nodded and clapped his hands. The Heart Tree King turned into a green stream of light and entered his body, returning to the mother tree world.

After doing this, Han Xiao looked back at the excited crowd and smiled. He did not participate but changed into King and disappeared.

Chapter 1443: New Situation and Relief

While the Galactic Alliance Army was celebrating, the upper echelons of the Super Star Cluster Alliance were discussing the short confrontation between Han Xiao and the three Universal Civilizations, which gave them some excitement.

"External pressure was the adhesive for internal cracks. Now that the adhesive is gone, the rift between Black Star and the three Universal Civilizations will only grow larger. The conflict will happen sooner or later. However, unlike back then, the Beyond Grade A organizations are now like the sun in the sky, and they have also obtained the inheritance of the World Tree. The three Universal Civilizations can no longer restrain them."

The leader of the Star Arc knocked on the table.

The upper echelons of the Super Star Cluster felt the same. They were gloating yet at the same time a little worried.

"The galactic society might have won the war, but all the real benefits fell into Black Star's hands. Although the war has ended, it is only the beginning of the reshuffling of the galactic structure. The new structure will be formed in the chaos. A character like Black Star will not miss this opportunity. He has the reputation of a war hero, and the three Universal Civilizations cannot stop him at all… This will be the trend!"

"Now that Black Star has the World Tree, his organization will rapidly expand. He doesn't even need to form an alliance with us, and he can fight on par with the three Universal Civilizations. Will he still value our agreement?"

"It should still be the case. The World Tree has suffered a huge loss, and Black Star might not be willing to turn hostile in the short term. It's definitely better to pull in external help than to do it alone. Furthermore, from his past actions, Black Star actually does not have the ambition to steal the ruling rights, nor does he have the intention to unite the entire Galaxy under him… Of course, the hearts of people are hard to predict, and this judgment might not be correct. It can only be used as a reference. On the other hand, the three Universal Civilizations have also suffered a huge loss, and they don't want to fall out with Black Star."

"Sigh, I feel a little pessimistic. If there are no new external conflicts, Black Star and the three Universal Civilizations might have a battle in the future. From the perspective of the entire galactic society, we defeated the World Tree and obtained the spoils of war. This is our strongest period in history, but internal conflicts cannot be resolved. Are we going to die by our own strength?"

"Don't talk nonsense. The three Universal Civilizations aren't really headstrong. As long as Black Star doesn't have the intention to rule alone, the three Universal Civilizations will still give up their opposition under the threat of absolute strategic deterrence and accept Black Star as a member of the ruling circle. Having two supreme factions might be the new normal in the future."

They carefully analyzed the possibilities of the future.

The leader of the Star Arc listened for a while and said, "Under such circumstances, we should find a new way to deal with ourselves. The original agreement was for us to work together with Black Star to fight against the three Universal Civilizations, but things are different now. The three Universal Civilizations need to rope us in to fight Black Star. It's not suitable for us to side with Black Star."

"You mean to cooperate with the three Universal Civilizations?"

"Of course not. What I mean is that we have to work together with both sides. The three Universal Civilizations will fight Black Star, and we will be a huge bargaining chip. The three Universal Civilizations won't treat us the way they did in the past, so the suppression will naturally be nullified. The tables have turned, and they will lower their heads and beg us to work together. This time, we can really use the proper way to obtain a chance to develop freely. Maybe the three Universal Civilizations still wish for us to become stronger… However, we have to make the situation into a new balance, so we can't easily side with either. Only competition can bring benefits. Monopolizing or dictatorship is not possible."

"Hmm, that's true. Not to mention the three Universal Civilizations, Black Star is also a dangerous individual who represents individualism. If he ascends, he will definitely give the Supers more privileges, which will allow him to lead the galactic society. He might not even be as good as the three Universal Civilizations. Furthermore, he has the World Tree, so he's also a time bomb."

Suddenly, someone sighed and muttered,

"Black Star, oh Black Star… such a person is really too difficult to deal with. He's always seeking greater benefits and never relaxes. He's really someone who does big things. If the person leading the Beyond Grade As was not the way he is, the three Universal Civilizations might have suppressed them long ago. How could they have developed to this stage?"

Hearing this, everyone sighed.

The image that Black Star had left for them was strong and ruthless, able to seize every opportunity to expand. Even if they did not consider his individual strength, they were still afraid of such a person. They could trust each other when they were teammates, but turning back into competitors was torture.

...

The news of the Galactic Alliance Army defeating the World Tree Civilization was temporarily locked down by the three Universal Civilizations and Han Xiao. They controlled the quantum network base station to filter out any information that might leak.

Since they were worried that it would be difficult to control the troops once they were disbanded, the victorious Galactic Alliance Army temporarily stayed in the secondary dimension to recuperate. Regarding this order, the various troops were still rather cooperative, but they could not stay on standby all the time. Thus, the plan to find the third party infiltrator required to be performed as quickly as possible.

The players were not restricted at all. The 'Galactic Alliance Army ending the war and Black Star subduing the World Tree' incident had already been recorded in Galaxy Chronicles and was extremely popular.

Han Xiao's heroic act of uprooting the World Tree spread across all the forums. Although many players could not help but complain that they had watched another round of CG, they were still very happy to be able to participate in such a large event.

However, the players were only active on the forums, and the news that was occasionally spread through the communicator had been intercepted. Therefore, the galactic society was completely unaware of the Galactic Alliance Army's victory.

The situation that countless galactic residents were aware of was the moment when the World Tree evacuated the invaders. They were still uncertain about this, and there were many different opinions online.

As for the Star Alliance spies who could only gather intelligence from the public network, they naturally did not know about the World Tree Civilization's defeat. They were still patiently waiting for the World Tree Civilization's 'big move', completely unaware of the impending disaster.

...

In the Central Galaxy, somewhere in the desolate universe belt, the secret base of the Star Alliance lurkers.

"I wonder what the World Tree is planning. It's been a long time since there's been any movement."

"I see that the Galactic Alliance Army is gathering in the Central Galaxy. The World Tree Civilization is probably going to attack the Central Galaxy."

"By the way, we are also in the Central Galaxy. Will we be affected? Should we evacuate?"

Inside the base, a group of observers gathered together and whispered.

The Observer Captain was a little hesitant and said, "The probability of the desolate universe belt being targeted by the World Tree is very low. No one has visited this place for many years, so it should be safe… However, the World Tree might also send people to infiltrate and build some strongholds. That way, we will also have the risk of being discovered by others…"

"If we act rashly, we might get exposed. Other places might be more dangerous. Let's stay," one of the team members suggested.

"…Alright then. If our base is really discovered, we'll start the self-destruct sequence and sacrifice ourselves."

The Observer Captain's tone became solemn.

These observers who had infiltrated the territories of the three Universal Civilizations were all carefully selected death warriors. In order to prevent any information leak about the Star Alliance if they got captured, they had long been prepared to commit suicide. The self-destruct device they buried was enough to blow up the entire planet and erase all traces.

"You guys continue to pay attention to the news. I'll go sort out the intelligence for this week and send it to my hometown in a few days."

The Observer Captain stood up and was about to leave the room.

Ding!

However, all of a sudden, everyone's movements froze, as if time had stopped.

A certain area in the room rippled, and Han Xiao walked out.

"Hehe, it's the Lorese. It's exactly the same as the visions given in the Explorer. Looks like I found the right one."

Han Xiao looked at the Observer Captain, and his eyes sparkled.

In order to prevent any accidents from happening, after he returned to the main universe, he directly consumed the materials and used the Virtual World to create a temporary Information Form Warning Network. He quickly completed the installation and set the parameters before activating it.

If he had not used that, he would still have been left in the dark. Once he used it, he received a shock. The information state alert network gave him a lot of abnormal signals. He had the impression that the entire explored universe was like a sieve being spied on by countless enemies, and he was shocked. After some adjustments, he finally understood that this technology was used in a normal civilization, and it was very easy to churn out false reports. Since the World Tree Civilization existed as a single entity, there was no such problem. This was the difference in technology.

The World Tree Special Express was a perfect match for this Information Form Warning Network. Although the three Universal Civilizations did not have such mobility, the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device could be used as a replacement, so Han Xiao did not waste too much time traveling.

After some selection and adjustments, he removed most of the false reports and confirmed some real external signals, most of which were from secondary dimension life forms.

Han Xiao visited a few signal areas and only now arrived at the base of the Star Alliance's infiltrators. He immediately confirmed that this was the real mastermind. The process was much smoother than he had expected. He had controlled the entire base and all the enemies before he even appeared.

"Let me see your background."

Han Xiao's eyes lit up, and the shadow of the World Tree appeared behind him.

As the World Tree merged into the space, it was stained with Han Xiao's energy, and the entire tree turned into a bright blue electric arc. A few translucent roots shot out like electric whips and penetrated everyone's chests.

The next moment, the figures of these observers turned illusory at a speed visible to the naked eye, and waves of energy entered Han Xiao's body through the roots.

With the World Tree in his hands, Han Xiao had no intention of interrogating these people. As long as he could turn these spies into members of the World Tree, he would be able to obtain all the intelligence from their memories and turn them into 'guides', imitating the methods of the World Tree.

Not long after, these Star Alliance observers fused into the roots. Han Xiao snapped his fingers, and a few roots arched their bodies like snakes. With a puff, they spewed out a large number of lightning sparks, reforming their bodies.

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and received the memories of these people. There was a lot of information about the Star Alliance inside.

"So that's what happened. The Star Alliance has been hiding for many years… Hmm, this civilization doesn't seem to be that strong."

Han Xiao pondered.

The third party had already been found, but they still had to discuss with the three Universal Civilizations how to deal with it. They had to see if they could destroy the Star Alliance or merge them into the explored universe. After all, although the Star Alliance was not strong, they had reached the standard of a Universal Civilization. The three Universal Civilizations had already suffered heavy losses, and they still had to consider the cost of starting another war.

The three Universal Civilizations had been the targets of the invasion before, but now that they had the chance, they definitely did not mind changing their roles seamlessly and turning into the invaders. After all, the Star Alliance was the one who had plotted against them, so they could not be considered innocent. The damage caused by the World Tree's full invasion could naturally be blamed on the Star Alliance.

Han Xiao withdrew his thoughts and sized up a Planetary Alliance spy.

"Continue hiding and maintain contact with the Star Alliance. Don't do anything without my orders."

"Understood. We will do our best to help you steal the intelligence of the Star Alliance!"

Many of the lurkers turned into fanatics.

"…Sigh, with the World Tree mechanism, who would believe that the user is not a villain?"

Seeing how passionate these former Star Alliance loyalists were about dealing with the Star Alliance, Han Xiao felt strange. He shook his head and disappeared.

...

Not long after, in the joint office of the three Universal Civilizations, Han Xiao brought the news of the third party being captured.

"You're right. There really is a third party interfering, and they've been hiding for so long. If not for the Information Form Warning Network, we wouldn't have found them…"

As Marbruce and the other two looked at the information that Han Xiao had brought, their expressions kept changing. Sometimes, they were angry, and sometimes, they were glad.

With the evidence before them, they basically believed that the mole was not from the Super Star Cluster or any other ally.

After browsing through the information of the Star Alliance, the three of them discussed for a while and came to a consensus.

"The Star Alliance is very far away from us, but once we obtain the spatial coordinates, we can use the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device to send our troops over, just like how the World Tree Civilization was dealing with us. Therefore, we have the initiative… We are inclined to destroy the Star Alliance and take it as our vassal. However, we should hold back for now. We have just experienced war, and we still need some time to recuperate."

Han Xiao raised his brows. "How long are you planning to rest?"

Louis pondered and said, "It depends on the situation… However, time is on our side. Although the news of defeating the World Tree Civilization can't be sealed forever, you have already controlled the spies of the Star Alliance. You can make use of them to send fake intelligence and fabricate the battle situation, making the Star Alliance think that we are still fighting the World Tree Civilization."

"The prerequisite is that the Star Alliance does not have any other methods to monitor the galactic society…" Han Xiao paused for a moment and spread out his hands." However, with the Information Form Warning Network, this possibility can be eliminated. "

"In any case, try not to alert the enemy," Marbruce said with a deep voice.

Han Xiao nodded and suddenly commented.

"The association and I will not accompany you in the battle of invading the Star Alliance. You can deal with them yourselves. I'm only responsible for these spies."

The eyes of the three of them flashed, but they did not say anything immediately. They quickly analyzed the situation in their minds and felt that there were pros and cons.

In this World Tree War, the three Universal Civilizations did not gain anything in the first place. The World Tree Civilization had been taken away by Black Star, and they did not even have the slightest bit of technology or resources. If they could swallow the Star Alliance, they would be able to reap some benefits.

Since Black Star was not participating in the battle, he would not share the spoils of war. Han Xiao had the World Tree, and he was the best at snatching resources. The three of them had to be wary of him.

Without the help of the Beyond Grade A Association, the war would be a little more troublesome. However, the three Universal Civilizations were not to be trifled with. They could not defeat the World Tree, but the same could not be said for the Star Alliance.

However, the three of them were worried that Black Star or the Super Star Cluster would try to assassinate them while they were at war with the Star Alliance. It was very risky… Who knew if Black Star had such plans?

For a moment, the three of them were caught in a dilemma and did not know if this was a trap.

Han Xiao glanced at them and guessed their thoughts. He pursed his lips.

He had only helped the three Universal Civilizations because he had been thinking about the calamities in his previous life and wanted to resist the World Tree.

Do you still expect me to help the three Universal Civilizations expand their territory?

It's already good enough that I didn't replace you. Be content, little brother!

Now that the threat was finally resolved, the galactic society could enjoy many years of peace. Han Xiao was satisfied.

Ever since his arrival, the World Tree had been the sword of Damocles in Han Xiao's eyes. It was the biggest psychological shadow and the source of his anxiety. For a very long time, he could only keep this secret alone and work hard to get rid of it. He did not dare relax, and the pressure was difficult to speak of to others.

After persevering for more than a hundred years, he had finally removed the threat of the galactic society. He no longer had to worry about the safety of his friends. He was relieved and wanted to retire and truly relax for some time.

Chapter 1444: Abyss of Misery

The three Universal Civilizations were finally relieved after the Star Alliance's infiltrators were captured. They quickly returned to the fleet and no longer blocked the news.

Very soon, the explosive news of the Galactic Alliance Army destroying the World Tree Civilization spread throughout the entire galactic society in the shortest time possible. Countless galactic residents on the refugee planets were shocked.

Not long ago, we were still in a passive state, enduring the full invasion of the enemy. Our future was filled with pessimism, and we were in a constant state of panic. However, before we were even mentally prepared, the tables turned in the blink of an eye. Suddenly, they told us that the war had ended, and everyone was safe… Brother, we just woke up, we haven't even brushed our teeth!

The galactic residents were stunned.

However, as the official media of the three Universal Civilizations revealed the entire process of the war and confirmed that this was not a rumor, the entire galactic society finally recovered from the shock and only felt endless joy.

Under the shadow of the World Tree Civilization, the entire galactic society had been forced to change its way of operation, disrupting everyone's lives. Countless people turned from free and casual galactic residents into refugees avoiding the flames of war. The wartime policies had tightened the resource supply and livelihood rights of the people, and the difference was huge. This change had lasted for almost twenty years.

From the perspective of a civilization or a high-level Super, twenty years was just a short time. It was just a small wave in the river of time, but to ordinary galactic residents, this was almost a generation.

Any change in the era would be amplified on the individual. In the past, the three Universal Civilizations and the World Tree Civilization were in a stalemate, and no one could see the bright future of the war. Countless galactic residents pessimistically thought that this kind of life would continue forever, and tomorrow would not be any better. At least two or three more generations would have to suffer in the flames of war.

However, at this moment, the light of dawn tore through the dense fog and shone into everyone's lives.

This beam of light came from the countless soldiers who had sacrificed themselves at the frontline, from Black Star, who had single-handedly turned the situation around.

On the 17th of April, year 799 of the Galaxy Calendar, different races on countless planets were cheering in different languages.

Countless galactic residents called this day the 'turning point of time', representing the end of the war and the destruction of the World Tree.

As the victors, the three Universal Civilizations received the praise of the entire galactic society. In the promotion, the three Universal Civilizations did not cover up Black Star's achievements:

Before the war broke out, he had been maintaining internal checks and balances to reduce internal conflicts. In the early stages of the war, he had led a group of Beyond Grade As to defend against the foreign enemies without any hesitation, and he had also personally taken the risk to gather crucial intelligence about the World Tree. During the preparation stage, he had been training the seeds of potential and nurtured a new batch of Beyond Grade As. One man stood alone in the shallow layer dimension, preventing the World Tree Civilization from advancing and forcing them to give up the battlefront that was the most dangerous to the three Universal Civilizations. He had found the World Tree's main body first, forcing the World Tree to give up the invasion, and single-handedly lifted the curtains of the final battle, turning the long-term war into the final battle…

With so many achievements, Black Star's glory in the war could not be concealed at all. His presence was extremely strong, and countless galactic residents recounted Black Star's contributions in detail. The reverence that gushed out from their hearts was like a warm current that warmed the hearts, and it was like an uncontrollable soul trembling, penetrating every bone and nerve.

Although this was a little unfair to the normal soldiers who had sacrificed themselves at the frontline, after seeing Black Star's deeds from start to finish, many galactic residents felt that the pace of the entire war was controlled by Black Star. He adjusted the general direction of the war, and the Galactic Alliance Army was more like a 'tool' that only carried out his will.

Because of the huge contributions, Black Star became the recognized 'Chief War Hero' of the galactic society. His reputation skyrocketed, exceeding all the previous records. He was truly like the sun in the sky, gaining the respect of the entire galactic society and receiving fanatical support.

As for the Beyond Grade As, they also received a large amount of reputation and received countless praises. This was especially so for the 'sacrificed victims' on the Soul Comfort Monument, who received more respect and became more popular.

Before the World Tree War broke out, Beyond Grade As were regarded as the privileged class of the galactic society, and they had been hated by many galactic residents. However, these Beyond Grade As fought a bloody battle and protected their safety, and the galactic residents were sincerely grateful.

Due to the wartime policies, most of the population of the various Star Fields had been concentrated on different planets. Now that the flames of war had been extinguished, the three Universal Civilizations had also begun to relocate batches of refugees, slowly leaving the wartime state and returning to normal society.

...

Central Galaxy, Planet Aquamarine.

In the huge open-air landing field, teams of spaceships with the Black Star Army insignia were parked neatly. The doors of the spaceships opened, and the people of Planet Aquamarine lined up in a long line. Following the orders of the army members, they stepped onto the starships that were returning home one after another.

The constant fear and anxiety made everyone look haggard and tired, but it could not hide the smiles and relaxation on their faces. They were full of hope for a beautiful tomorrow.

In the office of the government building, the white-haired and wrinkly Bennett stood in front of the floor-to-ceiling window. He looked down at the dense crowd in the square and saw the tired and excited expressions of the Planet Aquamarine citizens.

"Only time can heal the wounds of war…"

As he spoke, Bennett turned around and looked at the statue of Black Star, which was the city's landmark, with a gratified look in his eyes.

"Black Star… you really did it. I knew I could always trust you."

Bennett smiled as though he was relieved of a burden.

He was already indifferent to many things, but he was still proud of having an old friend like Black Star.

At the same time, in the Floating Dragon Island above this planet.

A spaceship slowly entered the dock, and the hatch slowly opened.

Harrison walked out of the spaceship and stepped onto the platform. His eyes immediately locked onto Jenny, who was waiting for him.

As their gazes met, everything around them seemed to turn into nothingness. They only had each other in their eyes, as if a lifetime had passed since they met.

Harrison strode forward and kissed Jenny's shiny forehead before pulling her into his arms.

Jenny only struggled for a moment before hugging Harrison's back and whispering, "You still know to come back?"

"…Sorry, I had a reason to leave. I…"

"Alright, I'm not blaming you." Jenny interrupted him and said, "I'm just thanking Black Star. If he had not found the World Tree's main body and completed what you wanted to do, you would never have returned."

"Indeed." Harrison released Jenny and scratched his head in embarrassment.

Jenny glared at him and said, "Speaking of which, you've also reached the top in a single step. Now that you've got me, you're in-laws with Black Star. Although I don't get along with Black Star, I can't deny that he's already standing at the top of the universe. With him as your backer, you can do whatever you want in the future."

"This…" Harrison was a little embarrassed.

Jenny snorted, lowered her head, and touched her lower abdomen. Then, she raised her fist and pretended to be fierce. "You have to treat me better in the future, okay? Otherwise, my sister and my brother-in-law will find you and beat you up. See if you can take it!"

Harrison shuddered.

Although he was not dating Jenny because of her identity, he could not help but break out in cold sweat at the thought of the two Gods in Jenny's family.

Harrison felt that the more he talked about this, the more dangerous it became. He quickly changed the topic, coughed, and asked, "Erm, I'll be staying on Floating Dragon Island from now on."

However, Jenny rejected it and shook her head. "There's no need to stay on Floating Dragon Island. I plan to resign from the Chief Supervisor position of the Floating Dragon."

Harrison was shocked. "What's the matter?"

"I've worked overtime for so many years, and I'm already tired. Ames won't manage it, and I was worried before. Now that she's together with Black Star, she doesn't need my help anymore."

Jenny's tone was complicated. She was still dissatisfied with Han Xiao, who snatched her sister away, but it was not her turn to object.

As she spoke, Jenny paused for a moment, looked directly at Harrison, and said in a soft and shy tone,

"Plus, I know that you like to explore. I hope that you and I will be happy together. I can't stop you from pursuing your hobbies just because we're together. So… can you take me out to explore in the future?"

Harrison was stunned. Then, he was overjoyed.

"You're so good to me…"

He looked at Jenny's face, and his heart palpitated. He could not help but slowly move closer to her. Jenny's face turned red, and she slowly closed her eyes.

Just as the two of them were about to touch each other, a deliberate cough sounded beside them.

"Ahem!"

Like a sudden clap of thunder, the ambiguous atmosphere was instantly broken. The two of them snapped out of it as if they had just woken up from a dream.

Both their faces turned red, and they quickly looked in the direction of the sound. Aesop had appeared beside them at some point in time, and his eyes were on them.

"When did you arrive? You're already so old, don't you know not to disturb others!" Jenny was furious and embarrassed, so she fired first.

Aesop could not be bothered with her. He walked over to Harrison, sized him up, and smiled. He patted Harrison's shoulder with great force, feeling extremely gratified.

"Good lad, you're much more reliable than that bastard Black Star."

Harrison, however, knew Aesop. He smiled bitterly and said, "Don't make fun of me. How can I be compared to Lord Black Star?"

"Heh, why can't you compete? At least in terms of reproduction, you've already beaten him by one step. If he had half your skills, I would have gotten a grandson a long time ago. Black Star is clearly a greenhorn himself, but he still acts like he's very strong. I wanted to impart him some experience out of kindness, but he actually shunned me." Aesop was furious when he said this.

Harrison did not know what to say, so he said helplessly, "Stop fooling around. Black Star is someone who does big things. Why would he waste his energy on such a small matter…"

"Hmm? Small matter?" Jenny's ears twitched, and she caught the keyword.

"Oh no, that's not what I meant. I…"

Before Harrison could finish, Aesop grabbed his neck and pulled him down.

"I think you're much more pleasing to the eye than Black Star. Let's go, I'll teach you a few moves. I guarantee that you'll be able to subdue Jenny…"

"Get out of here. Don't disgust me." Jenny gave Aesop a kick and dragged Harrison away.

...

In the unexplored universe, Star Alliance capital.

In the office, the leader of the Lore Civilization and the other leaders of the Star Alliance gathered together. A virtual screen was suspended in front of each of them, showing the same information.

"The Observer team has sent this period's battle report. Have you all read it?"

The leader of the Star Alliance looked at everyone and asked.

Savignes nodded and said with a smile, "I finished reading it right away. It seems like the three Universal Civilizations won't be able to hold on under our influence."

Hearing this, many people smiled.

The leader of the Star Alliance smiled and lowered his head to read the information.

"The World Tree Army attacked the Central Galaxy and focused on destroying the refugee planets, causing all the refugees on the 1,783 planets to be sacrificed. The civilian casualties are estimated to be between 15 trillion and 25 trillion…"

"The Federation of Light's mother planet was attacked by a large force of the World Tree, and the defense forces managed to repel the invaders. However, the mother planet was severely damaged. Although the upper echelons were unharmed, many of the middle-ranked officials and important people died."

"The Galactic Alliance Army and the World Tree invaders fought a battle at Silver Arm but were ambushed. Eight Beyond Grade As died on the spot."

"Due to the disadvantage of the battle and the suspicion of being spies, the Super Star Cluster Alliance carried out the evacuation plan and did not want to participate in the battle. The three Universal Civilizations strongly opposed it, causing internal unrest in the Galactic Alliance Army. It seems like they have broken up…"

Although he had already read it once, after listening to the leader of the Star Alliance read it, he could not help but smile with joy, his heart filled with the joy of revenge.

Finally, the leader of the Star Alliance read through the 'intense battle' that Han Xiao had made up. He paused for a moment and said with a relaxed tone,

"It can be seen that the battle between the three Universal Civilizations and the World Tree Civilization is extremely tragic. Furthermore, the Super Star Cluster Alliance was plotted against by us and was mistaken as a traitor who leaked the information. With both internal and external threats, the three Universal Civilizations will definitely lose if this continues!"

As soon as he said that, many of the people present smiled gloatingly.

Some of the Star Alliance members who did not support the plan were silent.

After reading this report, everyone came to a conclusion—the three Universal Civilizations were definitely living in the depths of hell and were heading to their end!

This was a sure win!

Chapter 1445: Establishment of the Supers Holy Land

Somewhere in the explored universe, the Avengers' fleet was slowly moving.

Inside the cabin, Pangon and the others were watching the news of the three Universal Civilizations' victory on the virtual screen.

Looking at the countless galactic races in the image, the Beyond Grade As present had complicated expressions.

"Humph, the three Universal Civilizations became the winners, and the galactic society escaped the calamity. Pangon, are you satisfied now?"

A Beyond Grade A stood with his arms crossed, his tone dissatisfied.

Pangon was expressionless. "There's nothing to be happy about."

"Is that so? But why do I feel like you don't mean what you say? Don't forget what our goal is! To be honest, if you have given up on revenge, you'd better disband early," another person said coldly.

This group of people had been planning to take revenge on the three Universal Civilizations, and the galactic society was celebrating their victory. Of course, they could not be happy. They only felt frustrated.

Facing Pangon, who did not have a firm stand, everyone naturally did not have a good expression.

Pangon remained unmoved and said calmly, "If you have the time to talk nonsense, you might as well think about our next move."

"You still have the face to say that? This war was clearly a very good opportunity for revenge. If not for you not allowing us to cause trouble, we would have long…"

"We were beaten to death by Black Star long ago." Pangon cut him off and slowly said, "Judging from the current situation, the conclusion is that even if we had caused trouble, we wouldn't have been able to change the outcome of the three Universal Civilizations' victory. This is because the key factor that determined the war wouldn't have been affected by us at all… Therefore, if we had taken advantage of the war, the outcome now would have been our annihilation. You all should be glad that I saved our lives."

Hearing this, everyone was frustrated. Every time they talked about this topic, Pangon would use similar reasons to convince them, and it was not easy to refute.

Right at this moment, Pangon suddenly changed the topic and said, "Don't you guys think that this new internal conflict is the best environment for us to develop? The reason why I didn't agree to create trouble in the war is because of this. If the three Universal Civilizations lose, we won't have to do anything. But since they won, they will form a new balance with the Beyond Grade A Association and the Super Star Cluster Alliance, and we will have more room to maneuver…

That's why I've always emphasized that we have to have the foresight to foresee the changes in the future. We can't just look for a chance."

Pangon spoke calmly.

Everyone had strange expressions.

This sentence sounded right, but coming from a Pugilist, it felt weird…

After taking one last look at the galactic refugees on the news, Pangon turned around and left the room.

When he turned around, the corners of his mouth curled up slightly but then disappeared. He said calmly,

"Stop looking. Let's go. Their joy has nothing to do with us."

...

The migration of refugees from the various Star Fields was going on like wildfire, but one day, explosive news once again caused a huge shock in the galactic society.

On this day, the Beyond Grade A Association officially announced the establishment of a civilization regime called the 'Supers Holy Land'. The civil nature association was promoted to be the Civilization's Elders Association. All the Beyond Grade As in the association were members of the Elders Association, and some of them with Black Star as the leader were the main decision-makers.

The nature of the civilization was the nation of immigrants that was common in the galactic society. It expressed that it would publicly accept all Supers with good credibility as citizens of the Supers Holy Land, regardless of race. Its slogan was 'Building a Resplendent Nation Exclusively for Supers'.

The Beyond Grade As were the leaders of the Supers, and like the wind vane, it was enough to guide a portion of the Supers to join the alliance. Furthermore, Black Star, the only Transcendent, had even more appeal to the Supers.

Of course, there were more substantial benefits. As long as one became a citizen of the Supers Holy Land, they could obtain the Super knowledge of the various classes through official channels and apply for customized training programs to help raise their level. In addition, official citizens could also choose to enjoy the protection of the Underworld. If they were unlucky and died or died of old age, they could choose to continue living as Hero Spirits. If they advanced to Beyond Grade A, they could directly enter the Elders Association and enjoy the Sanctum Revival for free.

Other than that, there were also various detailed rules and regulations, as well as terms of civil rights. They were jointly created by the professionals of the various Beyond Grade A organizations, and they referenced the systems of many galactic civilizations and made adaptive changes.

The location of the Supers Holy Land was in the Flickering World, occupying almost half of the territory. There were also some Star Clusters that had yet to be explored, located at the outermost edge of the explored universe. However, this was not the only territory. The desolate universe belt outside the Flickering World border was also included in the Supers Holy Land's territory.

The World Tree's 'regurgitation 'mechanism had to be mentioned here. It could transform countless planets, and the barren area could also be transformed into a prosperous Star Field. Therefore, the Supers Holy Land could be said to have obtained a territory that could continuously expand outward and was not restricted.

The first batch of citizens was from the various Beyond Grade A races or civilizations under their jurisdiction. They were currently migrating over, and the members of the various Beyond Grade A organizations were the first to enjoy the benefits. As long as they were willing, they could obtain the identity of a Supers Holy Land citizen. If they were not willing, they would not be forced. These people built the framework of the Supers Holy Land.

This was clearly taking advantage of the entire universe, and any civilization would face the risk of losing their Supers. However, the three Universal Civilizations did not stand out to oppose it. Instead, they sent a congratulatory message, congratulating the establishment of the Supers Holy Land in the name of the Galaxy Central Civilization Court and accepting the Supers Holy Land as a new member of the Civilization Council.

Both sides had reached an agreement a long time ago—the Beyond Grade A Association would obtain the status of civilization after the war. The three Universal Civilizations had already contacted Han Xiao during this period of time, and even if they were unwilling, they had no choice but to fulfill the agreement.

Among them, half of the Flickering World and many Beyond Grade A races had successfully migrated, which was all the benefits that Han Xiao had obtained. The three Universal Civilizations had many concerns, but they still agreed.

...

Before the joy of winning the war faded, the galactic residents had a new topic. The birth of the Supers Holy Land attracted the heated discussion of the entire galactic society.

Although many galactic residents had guessed that the Beyond Grade A Association would make a big move after the battle, due to the lack of information, they had not expected the Beyond Grade A Association to make a move so quickly.

Not only the ordinary people, but the entire Super class was shocked!

The attraction of the Supers Holy Land to the Super classes far exceeded that of any civilization. Just the benefits of the Underworld and the Sanctum Revival alone were enough to move countless people. In addition, there was also free public knowledge and free training.

After enjoying the taste of superpowers, it was basically impossible for them to be satisfied with the current situation. Most Supers had the ambition to improve their own level. The treatment of the Supers Holy Land was enviable, and they did not have obligations like when joining a Beyond Grade A organization.

Although the Supers had special privileges in the galactic society, they also had all kinds of concerns. Under the tacit understanding of the advanced civilizations, many low and middle-grade Supers had to sell their lives for all kinds of resources and knowledge. This was one of the ways for the advanced civilizations to maintain the balance so that the Supers would not become unstable factors of Galactic Society.

Now that the Supers Holy Land had shouted the slogan of 'building the holy land of Supers', it caused a huge commotion. The Supers no longer hesitated and immediately joined the alliance.

Before the World Tree War, they might have been afraid of the authority of the three Universal Civilizations, afraid that they would no longer be able to live in the galactic society. Just like how the three Universal Civilizations had suppressed the Beyond Grade A Association back then, many people did not dare join the Beyond Grade A organizations. Now that the political position of the Beyond Grade A Supers Holy Land had been recognized, Black Star was no longer the ordinary Beyond Grade A Super.

Everyone could see that the Supers Holy Land and the three Universal Civilizations had reached the same level, and it was impossible for the same thing to happen again. Therefore, many Supers no longer had any concerns. Even if the galactic society banned them, they could just live in the Supers Holy Land in the future, what was there to be afraid of!

...

At the border of the Flickering World.

Han Xiao was floating in the desolate universe belt, and the power of the World Tree was flickering with electric arcs all over his body. Facing the dark space, he waved his hands rhythmically, as if he was playing a symphony.

Under his command, roots tore through space and slowly took root. At the same time, the ends of the roots seemed to spout bubbles as they scattered the transformed planets in the galaxy to expand the territory of the Supers Holy Land.

Behind him, a group of Beyond Grade As were watching the scene of changing stars with shock.

No matter how many times they watched this scene, they were still shocked and awed.

After a while, Han Xiao finally finished modifying this area. He retrieved the power of the World Tree, turned around, and flew in front of everyone.

"Maintain this large territory for now. It should be enough."

"As long as you're happy…"

Everyone had mixed feelings and did not know what to say.

Han Xiao turned to look at Aurora and asked, "What does the galactic society think of the Supers Holy Land?"

"About one hundred and twenty billion Supers have applied to become a Supers Holy Land citizen, and this number is still rising rapidly," Aurora said.

"It's a little small, but it's just the beginning. Many people are still hesitating. When we completely stabilize, the population will skyrocket."

Han Xiao nodded casually.

During this period of time, he had been going everywhere, meeting with the leaders of the various organizations, reaching a consensus, and finally establishing the Supers Holy Land.

Establishing a civilization was very cumbersome, and all kinds of structures needed to be perfected. However, Han Xiao only needed to control the general direction and simple diplomacy. The details were filled in by the professional subordinates of the various Beyond Grade A organizations.

Because of the general trend, even the three Universal Civilizations did not make things difficult for him anymore. The creation of the Supers Holy Land was even smoother than Han Xiao had expected.

From now on, the Beyond Grade As were officially united, and they would be able to move around in the universe under the banner of the Supers Holy Land. The structure of the galactic society had truly become three-way. Han Xiao had fulfilled his promise to the Beyond Grade A Association.

Many Beyond Grade As became the upper echelons of the Elders Association in the Supers Holy Land. Among them, Aurora was promoted to be Han Xiao's assistant and replaced Kasuyi's position. This personnel change received everyone's approval. In the entire Beyond Grade A group, only Aurora could convince the masses.

This was also Kasuyi's intention. He had originally planned to explore the unknown universe after the battle, and Han Xiao had also changed his position according to his request.

Because Oathkeeper was traveling with Kasuyi, the Holy Accord was also empty, so Han Xiao made Beiger the acting leader of the Holy Accord and took over the job from Oathkeeper.

Beiger, on the other hand, did not mind being a mascot-like acting leader. However, Han Xiao did not really care about the Holy Accord anymore.

Now that he had obtained the World Tree that could convert resources, he no longer needed the Holy Accord organization to help him collect the Sanctum Keys. His main goal was to fulfill his previous promise and leave a place for the Beyond Grade As who wanted to retire.

Han Xiao turned around and looked at Psyker who was hiding in the crowd.

"The one with seven eyes. Haven't you always wanted to relocate your race? Move your Star Pupil Civilization to the Supers Holy Land. No one will suppress you here."

"Really? I don't believe it."

Psyker had strong doubts.

Even today, his Black Star PTSD had yet to be cured, and he felt that Han Xiao was up to no good.

Han Xiao rolled his eyes and ignored him.

At this moment, Hilbert walked out of the crowd with a group of revivors and said with a smile,

"Black Star, I wonder if the Supers Holy Land-realm welcomes our joining?"

Hilbert had always had the thought of leaving the three Universal Civilizations to join the Beyond Grade A Association. Now that the war was over and the Beyond Grade A Civilization was established, he had finally made up his mind. He brought along some of the direct descent Revivors who also felt that they did not owe the three Universal Civilizations anything; their motive was naturally the unlimited Sanctum Revival guarantee.

Seeing this, Han Xiao smiled.

"The three Universal Civilizations are even more furious now. If you make such a choice, it might invalidate the 'retirement benefits' that you gave up your lives for. Are you sure you want to do that?"

"It doesn't matter. We've all died for the three Universal Civilizations. We don't owe them anything anymore. It's time to live for ourselves." Hilbert smiled.

"In that case, the Supers Holy Land welcomes all of you."

Han Xiao nodded.

According to this trend, the future Supers Holy Land might really be able to get all the individual strengths in the universe.

At that time, the Supers Holy Land would become the sanctuary that all the Super classes yearned for. Almost all the civilian Supers who had awakened naturally would gather there, and the other civilizations would only have the Supers that were cultivated by the direct descendants. From another perspective, this would also increase the security of the galactic society, helping the various civilizations to consolidate their rule, and creating a more stable environment for the galactic residents.

Sigh, as expected, I still have peace in my heart. The three Universal Civilizations don't understand me.

Han Xiao shook his head and sighed.

Chapter 1446: Handing Over Positions and Farming Authority

There were only a few direct descent Revivors who chose to join the Supers Holy Land, and most of them chose to stay in the three Universal Civilizations. Even so, the difference between the high-level combatants on both sides was still quite large.

However, Han Xiao was no longer afraid of openly poaching from the three Universal Civilizations. Ever since he subdued the World Tree to end the war, many problems that he had been facing had been solved. For example, the three Universal Civilizations had never given in to the Ultimate Knowledge Transmission right.

"The three Universal Civilizations knew that they would not be able to stop the Supers Holy Land from becoming a sanctuary of individual strength, so they compromised with me in the end…"

Han Xiao's eyes swept past everyone and suddenly locked onto Karlot, Evans, and the other new Beyond Grade As.

Karlot and Evans' potential did not need to be strengthened, and their futures were naturally limitless. However, because the World Tree War broke out many years earlier than in his previous life, they did not have enough time to grow. Even with his nurturing, it was not easy to make up for the lost time, and they were far from reaching the theoretical peak of their ability.

Therefore, in this war, the two of them did not perform too well, but it was undeniable that they would still be extremely valuable in the future.

In Han Xiao's opinion, since the Beyond Grade As had shouted the slogan of 'Holy Land of the Supers', they had to have new injections of Supers, and they could not let the production of Supers stop. Although the current peak Beyond Grade As had a long lifespan and were distinguished, it would not do if there were no new generations of experts. They had to let the galactic society see the 'individual strength nurturing ability' of the Supers Holy Land that exceeded any organization.

Although there might not be any chance for Han Xiao to make a move in the future, he still needed a new generation to hold the fort for the Supers Holy Land. Han Xiao had already treated Karlot and Evans as his right-hand men and the future pillars of the Supers Holy Land.

The construction of the territory was completed. Secret Master and the other Mages summoned the transportation door and sent everyone back to the main planet of the Supers Holy Land.

The main planet of the Supers Holy Land was called 'Planet of the Deities'. It was located at the back of the Flickering World and had statues of all the Beyond Grade As of the Civilization's Elders Association. Black Star's statue was the most eye-catching and was the landmark of the entire planet.

Countless spaceships gathered on this planet from all directions, leaving behind streams of light like a bright galaxy. These were the various Supers who had chosen to join the Supers Holy Land and came to pay their respects to the statues of the various Beyond Grade As.

This area was originally a defensive area built by the Galactic Alliance Army, but after the war, all the troops stationed here left, and this area had a new owner.

Every Beyond Grade A had their own residence here. After returning, they left to do their own things. Now was the time to migrate their forces to the Supers Holy Land, and most Beyond Grade As were very busy.

Han Xiao returned to his office. Aurora, Hila, Feidin, and the others from the Black Star Army followed him for a small meeting.

"The framework of the Supers Holy Land has already been built. All that's left is to fill it up. There are some personnel changes that I need to explain to everyone."

As he spoke, Han Xiao looked at everyone, his gaze landing on Nero.

"As the highest leader of the Supers Holy Land, it's not suitable for me to continue leading the Black Star Army. Nero, I'll leave the army to you for the time being."

Hearing this, everyone turned to look at Nero with different expressions.

"Ah, this isn't appropriate. I'm not mentally prepared." Nero was shocked, stammering, "You, you built this organization from scratch, and now you're handing it over to me. I'm afraid I can't bear such a responsibility…"

Han Xiao raised his brows and scolded, "What are you thinking? I only want you to be the acting Army Commander. I will be the Army Commander in name only and will not interfere with the daily affairs of the army, but you still have to report to me."

Now that he had become the Supreme Leader of the Supers Holy Land, he needed to avoid the outside world. If he continued to lead the Black Star Army, it would be easy for others to have ideas, and it would also increase the army's ego. Although Han Xiao was not afraid, he would avoid it if he could. It just so happened that he also wanted to relieve some of his burdens and make himself more relaxed.

After all, with his Transcendent Grade and the power of the World Tree, he no longer needed external organizations to support his position.

"Then I'm relieved." Nero heaved a sigh of relief.

He could not be blamed for being cowardly. There were too many Beyond Grade As in the army. Although he was Black Star's godson, he still could not hold on.

Furthermore, the name 'Black Star Army' was already renowned throughout the universe. Nero was afraid that he would ruin its reputation if he stood too high. However, it would be much easier if he only worked.

Han Xiao turned to look at Aurora and said, "The same goes for you. Now that you're the second-in-command of the Supers Holy Land, you don't have to continue being the Deputy Army Commander of the Black Star Army. You can hand over your position later."

Aurora was unwilling. "What happened to the promise of staying in the army as long as I'm willing to stay?"

Han Xiao shook his head and laughed. "Your identity is no longer suitable. You don't have to carry everything on your shoulders. Even if you're not in the army, our relationship won't change. As the saying goes, a person will always strive for greater things. The Black Star Army was just a phase of your life. It's already over."

"Humph, big liar."

Aurora turned her head to the side.

Helpless, Han Xiao turned to look at Hila and asked, "What about you? Have you thought about what I told you? Do you want to take on the position of the Supers Holy Land's Esper Department's Chief?"

"Sure."

Hila nodded.

"Alright, then hand over your positions in the army with Aurora."

Han Xiao nodded as he spoke out.

The Supers Holy Land was divided into five important departments, led by the corresponding Beyond Grade As.

Hila's performance in this war was clear to all. Coupled with the characteristics of the Underworld, no one had any objections to her taking over the Esper Department.

Originally, Han Xiao wanted Manison to be in charge of the Mechanic Department, but since Manison had rejected him, he had no choice but to give up and let Kant manage the Mechanic Department. The Mage Department was managed by Milizaus, and the assistant was Secret Master. The head of the Pugilist Department was Sierron, and Han Xiao planned to replace him with Karlot in the future. The best candidate for the Psychic Department was Kasuyi, but he was traveling far away, so he replaced him with a peak Beyond Grade A Psychic who had been following the association for a long time, with Feidin as the assistant.

After a series of changes, the high positions of the Supers Holy Land were given to the various contributors.

Many of them were 'former members of the Black Star Army'. Han Xiao told them to hand over their positions in the army and did not force them to be tied up with the army.

Although these people did not mind following him, he still had to give them face. As upper echelons of the Supers Holy Land, it would not be good to keep the title of Deputy Army Commanders. It would also make it seem like the Black Star Army controlled the decision-making power of the civilization. Although he had the qualifications to be a dictator, he did not need to show it.

On the surface, a batch of Beyond Grade As leaving would make it seem like the upper echelons of the Black Star Army had lost their strength, but in reality, it was not much different to Han Xiao. In the past, he had wanted to gather a large number of experts to strengthen the Black Star Army, but now he had to do a reduction. His position had changed greatly, and just because these Beyond Grade As were not in the army did not mean that they would not listen to him.

This time, Hila crossed her arms and said straightforwardly, "You have to teach me how to enter the Transcendent Grade."

"I can't teach you now. Wait till you reach the bottleneck."

Han Xiao waved his hands.

He arranged many army Beyond Grade As' positions. After dealing with the last person, he thought for a while and looked at Aurora.

"Right, let Sorokin out. I have something to talk to him about."

Aurora curled her lips, but still did as she was told. Balls of gentle golden energy condensed into a physical body, gradually turning into Sorokin.

Sorokin opened his eyes and looked around before looking at Han Xiao. "Hmm? Isn't the war over? Why did you call me out?"

Han Xiao rubbed his knuckles and said, "I have a good deal for you. As long as you're willing to agree to a few rules and not cause trouble or mess around, I will allow you out of the Underworld and to keep moving outside."

Hearing this, Sorokin was suspicious.

"Since when do you treat me so well? Tell me, what do you want me to do?"

"The Beyond Grade A Association has established a civilization called the Supers Holy Land. I'll tell you the details later. I hope you can be an upper echelon in terms of economy or business and display your strengths. How about it? Are you interested?"

"There's such a good thing." Sorokin's eyes lit up.

"Just tell me if you're willing."

Han Xiao said casually.

Of course, there was no shortage of professionals in the Supers Holy Land, but Sorokin was the one who knew how to make money the best among the Beyond Grade As. Han Xiao felt that throwing him in the Underworld would be a waste of his talent, so he might as well get Sorokin out and make use of him.

Anyway, with his current position, he was no longer afraid of Sorokin stirring up any trouble.

"No problem, you don't have to worry. With me around, I will definitely make this Supers Holy Land's economy flourish, become stronger, and create glory!" Sorokin immediately agreed.

Since he had nothing to do in the Underworld, he naturally would not reject such a rare opportunity to 'relax'.

As for the enmity between him and Black Star, Sorokin had already accepted his fate over the years. He was a smart person and would not take it to heart.

Han Xiao nodded with satisfaction. Just as he was about to say something, his communicator suddenly rang.

Beep beep beep…

He took a look. It was a call from the Dynasty Ruler, Marbruce.

Han Xiao waved his hand and signaled for everyone to leave. After everyone left, he picked up the call.

"What have you called for?"

"Black Star, we plan to hold a grand ceremony on January 1 of the 800th year of the Galaxy Calendar to celebrate this victory, to commemorate the lives sacrificed in the war, and to honor the heroes. Your Supers Holy Land should participate as well, especially you. The entire Galactic Society sees you as a hero, so don't be absent."

"I'll be there."

Han Xiao nodded in agreement.

This war was indeed worthy for the three Universal Civilizations to hold a grand ceremony, and the date they chose was also very meaningful. The first day of the New Era… It was probably not for the convenience of the students to memorize that they chose this date.

After chatting casually for a while, Han Xiao told them about the choice of Hilbert and the others. However, Marbruce's reaction was very calm, as though he had expected it. It was a pity that Han Xiao did not see how furious he was.

After hanging up, Han Xiao calculated the date.

"There's still half a year left before the ceremony. This period of time is enough for the Supers Holy Land to gain a firm foothold. After the ceremony, I'll have a lot of free time. I'll then enter the Sanctum and revive those unlucky people who died in battle… I'll also find out all the information on the message board."

Because the World Tree had solved the problem of the Sanctum Key, Han Xiao naturally thought of a plan, which was to use it to enter and exit the Sanctum and unlock all the information on the message board.

In theory, this was completely possible.

However, this would require a lot of time, so Han Xiao decided to wait for the situation to stabilize before implementing it.

"Speaking of which, I wonder what the players have been doing recently…"

Han Xiao opened the interface and looked at the players' forums. Most of the topics discussed in the posts were related to the victory of the war and the Supers Holy Land.

Now that the war had ended, the players had nothing to do. Although Han Xiao had put up the Dungeon Crystals of the 'World Tree War' series, most of them still had nothing to do. They had just experienced the end of a main storyline mission, so many of them could not be bothered to do side missions for the time being.

In addition, the fifth Pro League was already in the preparation stage, attracting the attention of the players. Therefore, Han Xiao did not have to worry about the players having nothing better to do.

"The universe is peaceful and society is stable. Everything is improving… Tsk tsk, I haven't had such an easy time in a long time."

Han Xiao heaved a sigh of relief and felt a sense of satisfaction.

...

On the other side of the Planet of the Deities Manison's mansion.

Manison casually played with the pile of cards and looked at Kasuyi who was deep in thought. "You've already decided to travel far and found a new life goal. I haven't congratulated you yet."

"After living for so long, I have to find something to do. There are no secrets in the explored universe to me. Finding the unknown is more fun." Kasuyi casually threw out a card and smiled. "Speaking of which, I didn't expect you to reject Black Star's invitation and give up this position."

"Aren't you the same?" Manison did not comment.

"I don't want to work because I have to travel far away, but why don't you want this authority if you are staying here? This isn't like you." Kasuyi raised his brows.

"I have other plans." Manison glanced at the cards, took out a card, and pretended to play it. However, after thinking for a while, he stuffed this card back in and changed to another card. He did not stop talking and said, "I plan to study in seclusion for decades. I don't want to be distracted elsewhere… Furthermore, with Black Star around, I will never be able to surpass him in the eyes of Mechanics."

"Indeed." Kasuyi sighed. "Being in the same era as him is the misfortune of all Mechanics."

Manison looked up at him and knocked on the table. "You're not a Mechanic, why are you so emotional?"

"To be honest, if I were you, I would have directly taken Black Star as my teacher. Learning is not embarrassing." Kasuyi shrugged.

"You talk too much. Hurry up and play."

Manison snorted.

Although his relationship with Han Xiao had improved quite a bit, and he was willing to listen to the other party's orders to a certain extent, asking him to lower his head again? Impossible!

...

Supers Holy Land established a new structure after the war. After preliminary observation, a large number of Supers from different civilizations entered the territory of the Supers Holy Land from various Star Fields. After approval, they received official citizenship.

The work efficiency of a Beyond Grade A organization was known to be very high. As the various projects were quickly completed, the Supers Holy Land that had only been established for a few months started operating efficiently. On the other hand, the entire galactic society was still in a daze and needed a lot of time to adapt to the new situation.

The Super Star Cluster Alliance also made use of the birth of the Supers Holy Land to get rid of the suppression they had always been in and finally enjoyed the treatment of normal advanced civilization, obtaining a certain degree of freedom to develop.

After the war, the situation gradually stabilized. The entire galactic society was trying to adapt to the changes after the war, and in the blink of an eye, it reached the end of year 799 of the Galaxy Calendar. The three Universal Civilizations held a celebration ceremony as scheduled.

Chapter 1447: Support and Entry

Year 800 of the Galaxy Calendar, 1st January.

Central Galaxy, New Era Planet.

A few months ago, in order to hold this celebration, the three Universal Civilizations started manually modifying this planet, turning the desolate and dying planet into a celebration planet. They named it 'New Era Planet' to commemorate their hundred years of experience, especially the victory of the World Tree War.

Looking down from space, there was a huge building that looked like a tower on the New Era planet. At the top was an open-air square platform. This was the venue of the celebration, and there were rows of floating seats around it.

Countless spaceships were hovering in the air, covering the sky. Countless galactic media outlets had arrived to broadcast the scene.

This time, it was also a full broadcast of the various Star Fields. However, the number of viewers could not create a new record. Because of the war, many people had lost their lives. However, the viewership ratings had reached a new high, and almost every family stayed in front of the television to watch the broadcast.

Anti-gravity hovering cars rose from the ground and flew to the venue. The invited guests took their seats one after another. The representatives of the various civilizations, the military, the Beyond Grade As, and so on were all important people in the galactic society. As the guests entered and waited for the ceremony to start, the venue quickly became lively.

The Beyond Grade As beside him chatted casually, but Han Xiao did not participate in the conversation. He took out his communicator and looked at it. The galactic media had already started broadcasting, and the cameras swept across the venue. It seemed like they knew what the audience wanted to see, and they would pull it to his face from time to time, capturing every masculine detail.

"Tsk, always taking pictures of me. Am I that pleasing to the eye?"

Han Xiao smacked his lips without any shame.

Kasuyi, who was sitting at the side, nudged his waist with his elbow and chuckled. "It's a pity that you haven't revived those Beyond Grade As who died in battle. They're going to miss this celebration."

"I did it on purpose. In a while, when we pay our respects to the dead, if we see those victims alive, it would spoil the atmosphere."

Han Xiao paused for a moment, and with a strange expression, he added,

"Besides, you don't want to see Dillon speak on such an occasion, right?"

"…That's true." Kasuyi shivered.

Han Xiao shook his head and stopped talking.

In the past half a year, his Supers Holy Land had stabilized, and he had a rare holiday. His mental state was pretty good, and he was enjoying himself.

Although the ceremony this time was just a formality for Han Xiao, it was quite meaningful for the galactic society. They wanted to comfort the wounds left by the galactic residents in the war so that they would have the courage to look forward to the future. After all, a normal person's life required a sense of ceremony.

Not long after, the leaders of the three Universal Civilizations personally arrived. The venue gradually quietened down, and the audience watching the broadcast held their breath.

Under the watchful eyes of the crowd, Marbruce slowly walked up to the podium. His expression was solemn as he scanned the audience.

"The universe is vast and boundless. Countless unknown civilizations are like stars in the sky, bringing life to this world that should have been dead. We are also one of them, living in a corner of the universe, constantly reproducing… In the past hundred years, we have experienced many hardships, internal conflicts, technological disasters, and foreign enemies…"

Marbruce explained everything in detail, including the Crimson Tide, the Flickering World, the Intelligent Plague, the World Tree War, and so on.

The past hundred years could be said to have been like a storm, and Black Star is a character that could not be avoided talking about. He had an extremely strong presence on the galactic stage as he was part of most galactic events. The past hundred years were like the history of Black Star's rise.

Many players who were watching the broadcast listened with great interest. When they thought of Bun-Hit-Dog's 'Black Star Army' series, they could not help but feel honored. It was as if they were there on scene the whole time.

No matter how great Black Star's achievements were, the image of Black Phantom still lingered in the minds of many of the hardcore players. With their support and witness, he grew up step by step like a child.

"…We've survived through all the tough times in the past. Today, we've finally entered a peaceful New Era. This can't do without the contributions and sacrifices of the pioneers. They used their lives to exchange for a stable new life for us…"

Marbruce's expression was solemn. He took out a speech and slowly read it.

"The 31st Galactic Alliance Army Fleet No. 31, the original 'Iron Flag' fleet of the Crimson Dynasty, blocked the World Tree Civilization. A total of 8.8 million people were wiped out."

"Galactic Alliance Army Fleet No. 477, former Federation of Light 'Glimmer' fleet, met the World Tree Vanguard troops at the Flickering World's defense frontline. They had 11.2 million people, and only 403 are left."

"Galactic Alliance Army…"

Marbruce's tone was solemn as he read the shocking death statistics.

As the numbers of the sacrificed troops appeared one after another, everyone present and the galactic residents in front of the screen became solemn.

Many people only knew that there were many casualties in this war, but they did not know the details. Only now did they get a clear idea.

Everyone mourned for a few minutes before Marbruce continued to speak. The atmosphere was solemn as he conferred the honors to the victims who died in battle. After all the sacrifices were conferred, it was time to reward the surviving war heroes. Only then did the atmosphere become more relaxed and lively.

One by one, the war contributors took to the stage, and the leaders of the three Universal Civilizations consecutively awarded honors. Most of them were military officers, and all the Beyond Grade As had a share. The previous Revivors who had transferred to the Supers Holy Land also received different Medals of Honor. Even the Super Star Cluster Alliance, which normally could only be bystanders, also received different medals.

The three Universal Civilizations had expressed their sincerity. They did not talk about factions today, only about merits.

Lagi actually wanted to express himself freely, but when he felt Han Xiao's gaze on him from where the latter sat, he obediently followed the speech prepared for him.

This segment lasted for a long time, and it was finally Han Xiao's turn.

Marbruce coughed and said brightly,

"In the World Tree War, Black Star made too many contributions and provided us with a large amount of intelligence. In the end, he turned the tables and gave us the opportunity to end the war in advance. His contributions are irreplaceable. All the members of the Galaxy Civilization General Council unanimously decided to award Black Star the Galaxy Medal!"

Pa pa pa!

Everyone applauded loudly. Black Star's reputation in the Lawful Faction was already off the charts, and almost everyone was sincerely congratulating him.

When dealing with the Intelligent Plague, Black Star had already received a Galaxy Medal, and now he had received a second Galaxy Medal. The Galaxy Medal was the highest honor in the galactic society, and it would not be given a second time. However, Black Star was the only person who had received it twice, and he had already created history.

However, they were not surprised at all. Black Star deserved this honor. Other than the Galaxy Medal, there was no other award that could match his contribution.

Amidst the applause, Han Xiao stood up calmly and walked onto the stage.

"Thank you for your contribution to the galactic society," Marbruce said sincerely.

On the other hand, Louis and the Pope patted Han Xiao's arms to show their closeness.

Han Xiao would not refuse to give them face in such a situation. He nodded and received the Galaxy Medal from the three Universal Civilizations' leaders.

According to the usual practice, the person who was awarded the award had to give a speech. Han Xiao had prepared a speech long ago, and it was all just for show.

He walked to the podium and was about to speak when he suddenly paused.

Countless lights flashed in front of his eyes, and countless galactic residents were looking at him from behind the screen. The guests around him quietened down and stretched their necks. The faces of the different races were filled with the same anticipation and hope. They held their breaths and waited for him to give a long speech.

Seeing this, Han Xiao was a little dazed. He looked down at the medal on his chest and subconsciously rubbed it.

He hesitated for a few seconds and gave up on the long speech. He shook his head and said in a solemn voice.

"…I hope that there will be no more wars in this universe. I hope for universal peace."

The venue hesitated for a moment, waiting for Han Xiao to continue. However, Han Xiao nodded at the crowd after he finished speaking. Seeing this, the people present all applauded.

The process was carried out step by step. After Marbruce's impassioned speech about 'looking to the future', the ceremony finally ended smoothly.

The entire galactic society was jubilant. It was as if their souls had been baptized, and they were filled with new motivation for the future.

A few days later, in the conference room of the three Universal Civilizations.

"The Star Alliance is still the same as before. According to the spies that were instigated by Black Star, the upper echelons of the Star Alliance believe in their intelligence and are very excited."

"However, we still have to be careful in case the Star Alliance sends out new spies. If that happens, we'll be exposed."

"That's right. Black Star has already informed us. He said that he will disappear for a period of time to revive a batch of Beyond Grade As in the Sanctum. We have to be careful during this period. Don't let the Star Alliance see through our trick."

The three of them discussed softly.

Black Star would not be able to helm the Supers Holy Land for the time being if he went to the Sanctum, but the three of them did not have any other thoughts about him. They were only worried that the Star Alliance would see through their plan if Black Star was not around.

"After more than half a year of recuperation, the army has recovered a little, but the loss of Supers is quite severe. There's no way to compete with the Supers Holy Land. Sigh…"

"However, Black Star said a few days ago that he was willing to develop the Sanctum with us in the future. I wonder if he's lying."

The three of them were confused.

Now that Black Star had the upper hand and his position was stable, there was no need for him to share the information about the Sanctum with them. They did not know what Black Star was planning.

"I don't think so," Marbruce said hesitantly. "The Sanctum Revival is an important trump card of Black Star's, so how can he share it with us? If he really did that, he definitely has a bigger plan."

Louis shook his head. "Let's not talk about him for now. It's more important to deal with the Star Alliance. Although they have fallen into our trap, we can't hide it forever. The more time passes, the more suspicious they will be. When do you think it's better to take action?"

The Pope pondered for a moment before saying, "The galactic society can't take another round of war. If we act rashly, the praise we have now might turn into criticism… I think we should at least wait for the galactic society to stabilize for three to five years before we act. Anyway, time is on our side, so there's no need to rush. Let's wait until we recover."

The three of them discussed plans on when to start a new war.

Half a month later, somewhere in the Supers Holy Land.

Han Xiao floated in the universe without anyone around him.

He had already spoken to the three Universal Civilizations and the Supers Holy Land. He would enter the Sanctum today and begin his plan to increase his authority.

In the inner space, the World Tree moved slightly, materializing a Sanctum Key and quickly burning it.

The next moment, a ray of light shot out from his palm and turned into the light door of the Sanctum in the universe before him.

"I hope this plan works…"

Han Xiao calmed himself down and flew in. His body was gradually engulfed by the light.

Chapter 1448: New Secret and Different Paths

It was the familiar tunnel of light again, and the familiar blur…

After some time, Han Xiao regained clarity.

Han Xiao's vision suddenly became clear. Looking around, he could still see the familiar scene of the First Sanctum. The white world was endless, and countless light spheres floated in it, these were the Information Form collective body that recorded information of Iterations.

"It's still blurry, but it's a little lighter than before…"

Han Xiao was no stranger to this feeling. After all, he had been here many times and was already a frequent visitor.

He looked down at the back of his hand. The Sanctum mark was shining brightly, one level higher than last time.

"Let's revive those unlucky fools first."

Han Xiao did not waste any time. He skillfully sacrificed the mediums of the Beyond Grade As that died and activated the Sanctum Revival function.

Very soon, rays of light appeared out of nowhere and gathered from all directions, forming a Sanctum revival mark that floated in front of Han Xiao.

Han Xiao pointed with his finger, and the Sanctum revival mark seemed to turn into liquid. It flowed along with his finger and stopped on the back of his hand, turning into a complicated tattoo.

He extended his consciousness into it and checked on the reviving targets. He confirmed that all the people on the Soul Comfort Monument were inside.

After doing this, Han Xiao let out a sigh of relief. He calmed himself down, brought out the Sanctum's message board, and looked at it.

His authority in the First Sanctum had increased once again, and more content appeared on the message board compared to the last time. Han Xiao compared it according to his memory and saw the records of Celestial Star Alliance in the fifth last paragraph. Only then did he focus and look at the last paragraphs carefully.

The last four paragraphs were the ones with the most empty content. He had read them twice in the past, but he had only obtained two pieces of valuable information. One was the 'Information Form Stripping Plan' mentioned in the fourth last paragraph, and the other was the last paragraph which indicated the continuation of the previous Iteration's plan. It mentioned some 'unknown device' and 'control terminal'.

This time, Han Xiao realized that some of the content in the last four messages had been filled up. There were some messages that he was concerned about in the second last and last paragraph.

[… ███ transformation plan failed, but the principle has been proved to be feasible. The reason for the failure is that there is no crucial true-state medium to establish connection with ███ , ███ needs to be improved next time. The Information Form Materialization device has been manufactured and loaded into the template, which may cause information alienation in the process of ███ and present in the following █████ in the form of 'distorted' unknown…] — was the message in the second last paragraph.

[…The existing true-state mediums are not enough to complete the ███ transformation plan of the previous iteration. We need deeper ███ connection to build a stable ███ bridge… We decided to add a control terminal in the Information Form Materialization device to reduce the processing cost of the Information Form Materialization device…] — was the message in the last paragraph.

"Hmm, this…"

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

The second last message was from the 'previous Iteration' written in the last message. Looking at the content, the latter had inherited the former's plan.

The 'unknown device' and 'control terminal' mentioned in the last paragraph had also been unlocked. They were the 'Information Form Materialization device' created by the Iteration who left the second last message.

In addition, these two pieces of information threw out a new concept, 'True State'. Han Xiao was secretly surprised. With his current level, there were very few things that he did not understand at the technological level. It was actually his first time seeing this term.

Han Xiao tried to use the term 'index function' with the Sanctum authority, but the Sanctum mark did not respond. Generally speaking, the index function could only be activated by a precise search of a single Iteration or the civilization's name.

"Looks like I have to continue to farm for more authority and unlock the civilization names of the last four messages."

Han Xiao nodded to himself. The name of the civilization mentioned in the last four messages was still empty, and he did not have the authority to check it.

After memorizing this information, Han Xiao closed the message board and began to search for technological information in the First Sanctum.

Although he had yet to finish researching his gathered resources and was not lacking in technology, he was already here…

After his clearance to the Sanctum increased, the upper limit of his memory capacity also increased. After quite some time, Han Xiao finally filled up the capacity and returned with a full load. He did not stay any longer and opened the Sanctum channel to leave.

After passing through the tunnel of light again, Han Xiao's body suddenly felt lighter, and he had already returned to the main universe. The Sanctum's light gate behind him disappeared.

Han Xiao opened his communicator. Only thirty days had passed.

"The flow of time is getting closer. The next time will probably only take twenty days." Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

The message board of the Sanctum seemed to be universal, and it was the same no matter which Sanctum it was. Therefore, he only needed to focus his firepower on gaining authority in one Sanctum. If he increased authority in all the Sanctums together, it would take many years.

Han Xiao thought about it, changed into King, and teleported to the main planet of the Supers Holy Land. He flew to the huge square where all the Beyond Grade A statues were placed.

At this time, the square was bustling with activity, and there was an endless stream of people. They were all Supers from all over the world. Upon seeing Han Xiao arrive, they were stunned for a moment before being pleasantly surprised.

"Look, it's Black Star!"

"It's the real deal!"

"I'm your admirer. Can you give me an autograph…"

The pedestrians were excited, and they swarmed over like crazy fans.

Among the Supers, Black Star was almost everyone's idol. At least eight out of ten Supers were his worshippers, no different from a great personage.

Han Xiao smiled at them and waved his hand. A gentle breeze blew, and an invisible force field spread out, covering an area like a transparent barrier, blocking all the pedestrians.

The pedestrians who were further away also heard the commotion and came over. There was a sea of people outside the barrier, and very soon, they formed layers after layers. They looked at Han Xiao curiously and guessed the reason for his appearance.

Han Xiao did not explain anything and activated the Sanctum revival mark. Rays of light surged and condensed into balls of light, gradually turning into the bodies of the Beyond Grade As that had died.

The reason why he displayed it in front of the public was to let the public see the actual scene of the Sanctum Revival and increase the attractiveness of the Supers Holy Land. This was a plan that he had come up with during the meeting a few months ago. In the future, the Sanctum Revival would be carried out publicly.

Before farming the Sanctum authority, Han Xiao planned to revive these unlucky fools first. On one hand, he wanted them to return as soon as possible, fulfilling his promise.

On the other hand, he wanted the three Universal Civilizations and the other organizations to see that his time in the Sanctum was shortened, telling them that he could return at any time. Although those annoying people might not have other intentions, Han Xiao felt that it was best to avoid this possibility, lest these advanced civilizations felt that he had disappeared for too long and wanted to cause trouble again.

Very soon, the light in the square solidified, and under everyone's gaze, this batch of dead Beyond Grade As revived with confusion on their faces.

"Haha, I'm alive again. Praise Black Star!"

"Where is this? Why haven't I seen it before?"

"What era is it now? Has the World Tree War ended?"

The group of revivors looked around curiously before their eyes landed on Han Xiao.

"Alright, the war is over. We won. Ask Aurora and others about the details."

Han Xiao waved his hands casually. This was not the first time these people had revived. The advantage was that he did not have to explain the situation from the start.

He turned to look at Dylan and said, "I've fulfilled my promise and allowed you to regain your freedom. You'd better keep a low profile in the future. Otherwise, if others want to kill you again, I won't stop them."

Dylan's face twitched.

Restoring his freedom should have been a happy thing, but Dylan felt a little weak.

When he was the Hero Spirit of the Underworld, he did not have to worry about anything, so he was even more unrestrained in his words. He let himself loose and scolded whoever he wanted, and he offended many people.

Other people could not be bothered to argue with a 'dead person' like him, but now that he was alive, if they came to settle the score, he would suffer heavy losses…

For some reason, Dillon felt a little reluctant to part with the feeling of being an Underworld Spirit…

Han Xiao did not say much to the others. He turned around, teleported, and disappeared. Without the force field barrier, countless pedestrians swarmed over. These revivors did not understand the situation and almost drowned in the sea of people. They quickly rose into the sky and left.

Halfway through the flight, Aurora, who had already noticed the commotion, arrived with a group of Beyond Grade As on the main planet to welcome the revivors.

"Congratulations on reviving. Come with us to understand the situation," Aurora said.

Ever since she was elected as the second-in-command of the Supers Holy Land, she had been maintaining a big sister attitude, as if this would give her some 'prestige' bonuses. However, in the eyes of the Beyond Grade As who had the first impression of her, she was still cute and adorable. Even if Aurora deliberately put on an elegant and dignified appearance, it did not have any deterrence at all.

The revivors nodded and followed Aurora toward the core building of the Supers Holy Land.

Just as Dylan was about to follow, he suddenly felt a hot and vigorous bloody intent coming from the side. Two thick, firm, and flexible muscles clamped his arm like a huge mouth. At the same time, his shoulder was grabbed by someone, and waves of enormous strength were transmitted, grabbing him tightly and not letting him move.

Dylan turned around and saw Sierron appearing beside him. Sierron put his arm around his shoulders and leaned over with a wicked smile on his face.

"Yo, you're finally alive. Come over here. We have a bunch of guys who want to have a good chat with you."

Dylan turned around stiffly, only to see a group of Beyond Grade As staring at him with a teasing look in their eyes.

Gulp…

Dylan swallowed a mouthful of saliva, and cold sweat appeared on his back.

As the saying went, it was easy to go from frugal to extravagant, but it was difficult to go from extravagant to frugal. At this moment, Dylan realized that being a Hero Spirit was indeed more 'comfortable'…

...

Han Xiao only appeared for a short period of time. After completing the Sanctum Revival, he immediately opened the Sanctum again and started the process of farming his authority.

Currently, the matters of the Supers Holy Land were all being managed by Aurora and the Elders Association. The external environment was very stable, so his disappearance did not have much of an impact.

As the days passed, it was finally time for Kasuyi to set off. Most of the Beyond Grade As respected this comrade of theirs and they all came to see him off on the day he left.

After the battle with the World Tree, most of them had become comrades and their relationship was much better than before. As for Kasuyi, who was kind to others, he was quite popular.

At the dock of the Supers Holy Land, a long-distance spaceship with the highest technologies was docked. The hatch opened. Kasuyi and Oathkeeper had already packed their things. They stood in front of the gangway and said their goodbyes.

"The unexplored universe is filled with unknown dangers. The two of you must be careful," Aurora said on behalf of everyone.

Kasuyi smiled and said, "It's alright, we have Black Star to back us up anyway… Haha, it's just a joke. With our abilities, we won't fall into danger so easily."

"If you guys go, you probably won't come back for a long time. There will be no news of you. Sigh… I won't be able to find you to play cards anymore." Kant was a little sad.

"It's fine. Our Supers Holy Land may not have much of anything else, but we do have many card players." Kasuyi shook his head and smiled.

At this moment, Manison walked forward and patted Kasuyi's shoulder. He did not say much and simply said, "Goodbye, old friend. Have a good journey."

"Thanks. I also wish you success in your seclusion." Kasuyi stopped smiling and nodded.

Not counting Black Star, his relationship with Manison was actually the best among everyone. The two of them had known each other for hundreds of years, and they were old acquaintances.

Most of the people who saw off Kasuyi were Beyond Grade As of the current era. On the other side, Oathkeeper was surrounded by the first batch of revived Primordial Ones of the Holy Accord.

"Back then, we made the Holy Accord together, and our comrades died one after another. You are the only one who has lasted till now. None of us expected you to really complete this work."

"It's been hard on you all these years. If not for you, we would still be sleeping."

"Although you did not reveal yourself in our active era, we now know that you might be the best among us."

Many Primordial Ones sighed.

Oathkeeper was expressionless. He waved his hand and said, "Let's not talk about the past. I'm just fulfilling the promise I made back then. There's nothing worthy of praise… Unfortunately, although we've really achieved our wish and successfully revived in the future, the era no longer belongs to us."

Beiger sighed and said with a reluctant tone, "Sigh, no matter what, we are still grateful for your actions. When you miss us, take a look at the Primordial Ones card set that we gave you. This is the first-generation discontinued card set that we 'kindly' requested from the Wayne Card distribution group headquarters…"

"I will keep it well." Oathkeeper was speechless, but his usually serious face still revealed a smile that was hard to notice.

After bidding farewell for a while, Kasuyi and Oathkeeper looked at each other.

"Let's go."

The two of them nodded at everyone before boarding the spaceship.

Buzz—

Everyone watched as the spaceship slowly began to move. It glided along the orbit and took off into space. With a sudden acceleration, it disappeared into the depths of space, leaving only a trail of flames behind.

Manison retracted his gaze and left without saying goodbye.

He decided to enter a long period of seclusion from today onwards. He would isolate himself from the rest of the world and focus on his research.

Compared to taking shortcuts, he preferred to rely on his own intelligence, and this had never changed.

...

At the same time, in the Temple of Ten Thousand Gods.

A fleet was already ready.

"Your Excellency Wuornos, have you decided? Are you really going to the unexplored universe?"

The priests surrounded him with complicated expressions.

"I've already discovered that the key to the path ahead is hidden in the depths of space."

Wuornos looked at the galaxy with deep eyes.

Just a few months ago, he finally dug out his hidden perception and sensed the location of the Beyonder's Vestige in the galaxy. Like the bright Venus, it guided him from afar.

In the end, he decided to follow his intuition and leave the explored universe, heading to the unknown area to search for the opportunity to enter the Transcendent Grade.

"In that case, we will respect your choice… The Pope told us to specially send a message. He said that he hopes when you return, you can become the first direct descendant to become a Transcendent."

"Tell him that he will get what he wants."

Wuornos replied calmly and walked into the spaceship.

The next moment, the Arcane Church fleet slowly set off, heading toward the unknown.

...

Chapter 1449: We Are People Who Have Experienced Tumultuous Times

Supers Holy Land, in a certain lifeless sector.

A ball of colorful energy floated in space, its shape changing unpredictably, like a cloud being kneaded by an invisible force. All kinds of high-energy particles flowed through it, like electrical signals being released during neuron activity. The entire energy ball was like a small nebula-shaped energy field brain.

Evans floated in the middle with a serious expression, carefully controlling all kinds of energy to perfect this nebula brain.

However, all of a sudden, the energy nebula started to expand uncontrollably, and the neural bridge that was built from all kinds of energy collapsed.

Just as the energy nebula was about to explode, Evans' Esper Ability Domain opened up. The violent energy suddenly stabilized and quickly shrank, turning into a dazzling light sphere the size of a human head before being absorbed into Evans' body.

"Sigh, I failed again…"

Evans sighed in helplessness.

Ever since he witnessed the battle between Transcendent Grade Supers, he had always felt that his strength was insufficient. He had been driven ever since to pursue that unbelievable power.

Originally, after the war ended, everyone had started to take a break, but Evans was one of the few people who did not relax and had been busy developing his Esper Abilities.

On one hand, his motivation was his own pursuit, and on the other hand, Evans still remembered Black Star's high hopes for him. He was not willing to waste his hard-earned potential and wanted to reach Black Star's level.

On the other hand, EsGod was very glad about this. He thought that Evans was keeping his promise to help him beat Black Star up and always taught him things to guide Evans in his cultivation.

"I hope to increase my strength as soon as possible. His Excellency Black Star told me that he hopes I will be the main pillar of the Supers Holy Land in the future. I cannot disappoint him…"

Evans clenched his fists and encouraged himself.

Just as he was about to give it another try, he suddenly sensed something and looked in a direction.

The stream of light approached, and a spaceship arrived in hyperdrive, hovering not far away. A burly figure flew out. It was Karlot.

"Eh, so it's you. I was wondering why there was another high-energy reaction zone in our territory."

Karlot was surprised to see Evans and took the initiative to talk to him.

"Er, hello." Evans hesitated for a moment before nodding.

Although the two of them were both members of the Black Star Army, they did not interact much with each other. They only knew each other's basic situation and could only be considered as colleagues.

"What are you doing here?" Evans was curious.

"I was looking for an extreme environment to temper my body. The spaceship sensed a high-energy reaction, so I came over. So, you were training. No wonder."

"Oh, I see…"

The two of them were not familiar with each other, so they bit the bullet and chatted for a while. When they realized that there was nothing to talk about, they gradually fell silent.

However, neither of them left. The atmosphere slowly became strange.

When the two of them were in seclusion, they had always thought that they were the only seeded players who had received special treatment from Black Star. However, after leaving the mountain, they were surprised to find out that they were not the only ones.

Such a relationship made the two of them have strange thoughts about each other. On one hand, they were curious about the other party's background, and on the other hand, they were curious about what Black Star saw in the other party…

This mentality was akin to two top students in a class receiving special treatment from their teacher, and they subconsciously felt competitive…

After a long time, Karlot coughed and broke the silence.

"How about… we spar?"

"…Sounds good."

Evans and Karlot's eyes met in midair, and sparks seemed to fly.

...

Black Star Army headquarters, Fleet Commander's Office.

Herlous sat on the sofa with his legs crossed. He looked at the Sunilian in front of him and pushed the wine glass on the table.

"Drink some?"

"No need, Your Excellency Herlous."

Herlous did not mind. He sized up the Sunilian and nodded.

"You must be the Sunil leader of this generation. Not bad, not bad. The previous leader mentioned you to me before. He said you're very smart and capable."

"You flatter me." The leader nodded.

The Sunilians were Herlous' race. Ever since the rise of the Black Star Army, Herlous, as the earliest elder, had a lot of authority, and he provided many resources to the race.

Therefore, every generation of Sunil leaders would come to visit him. This generation was no different.

"Since you've become the leader, do your best."

Herlous encouraged and looked at the young Sunilians behind him. He raised his brows.

"These are…"

"Your Excellency Herlous, these are a few young men with potential among my immediate family. They wish to enter the Black Star Army to train. Please take care of them," the Sunil leader said respectfully.

Herlous sized up the few of them, and the youths immediately stuck out their chests and raised their heads nervously.

Seeing this, Herlous shook his head and said, "The army has changed its leader, and Nero is now in charge. However, the standards are still as strict as ever. I can make them official members, but whether they can climb up will depend on their own abilities."

"Thank you, Your Excellency." The Sunil leader bowed.

Herlous waved his hand, indicating that there was no need for formalities. After a pause, he suddenly changed the topic.

"From now on, leaders of your generation should stop visiting me. You should be more independent. You should leave me out from now."

The Sunil leader's body trembled slightly, and his expression was complicated. However, he did not say anything, lowered his head, and left with his men.

After the group left, another person walked in. It was Sylvia. She had been eavesdropping outside for quite some time.

"Not bad. You've finally decided not to use your position for personal gain," Sylvia teased.

"Nonsense. I've always been thinking about the army." Herlous rolled his eyes.

"I was just joking. However, I'm very curious. Why aren't you helping the race anymore?" Sylvia blinked.

"They can't always rely on me, or else they will become dependent sooner or later. After close to a hundred years, the habits that have been cultivated from generation to generation have already started to show signs of this. I can't just ignore it." Herlous shook his head and said with a deep voice, "Furthermore… Black Star was able to tolerate me in the past, but now that the authority has changed hands, I have to be sensible in the future."

Sylvia curled her lips and did not speak. She stood in front of the window with her hands behind her back and looked at the bright galaxy outside. Suddenly, she sighed and muttered,

"In the blink of an eye, it's been a hundred years…"

Herlous also turned to look out the window and sighed. "That's right, it's been a hundred years… We actually followed Black Star to this point. Sometimes, it feels like a dream. If Black Star had not invited me back then, I might have spent the rest of my life in my own little pub."

"If I hadn't met him…" Sylvia's tone paused, and she shook her head. "Maybe I would have died in some corner of the universe long ago. The life we have now is not something we can hope for…"

The two of them looked out of the window quietly and did not speak anymore. They quietly savored their memories.

...

In this peaceful era, time passed even more silently. In the blink of an eye, another few months passed.

On this day, in the conference room of the three Universal Civilizations.

"Recently, the direct Beyond Grade As have been restless. The expansion of the Beyond Grade As is too shocking."

"Thankfully, Clotti, Oulou, and the others have stabilized the situation. Otherwise, the direct line of descent might have turned to the Supers Holy Land."

The leaders of the three Universal Civilizations sighed.

The Supers Holy Land had broken the old structure. As the original beneficiaries of Supers, they naturally could not feel comfortable, but they could only silently endure the waves of impact.

"Speaking of which, Black Star did not appear during this period of time. Hasn't he already completed the Sanctum Revival? What has he been busy with recently?" The Pope was curious.

"Who knows? Anyway, I can't get any information." Marbruce was helpless.

"It's not a good idea for him to disappear for so long. If the Star Alliance sends in a new infiltrator, and Black Star happens to not be around, we might get exposed."

"Speaking of which, if Black Star is willing to help, as long as he controls the leader of the Star Alliance, we will be able to win easily. It's a pity that he doesn't want to help."

"Heh, with Black Star's personality, there's no such thing as an absolute deal. I think the price is not enough. As long as some conditions are made, he should still agree."

"That makes sense, but he has a huge appetite now. We have to think of a way to convince him…"

Just as the three of them were discussing how to pull Han Xiao to help with the Star Alliance, a remote projection suddenly appeared in the room. It was Han Xiao.

The three of them were shocked.

"Black Star? You… you're back. Why didn't you inform me…" Marbruce was halfway through his sentence when he suddenly realized something. He frowned and said with dissatisfaction," Hey! Did you hack into the Dynasty's database again? "

Han Xiao ignored Marbruce's dissatisfaction and looked at the three of them with a strange gaze.

"I'm here to share the information of the Sanctum. We can develop it together. If you're not happy, I'll leave."

The three of them were stunned.

"Are you serious? Are you really taking us to develop the Sanctum?"

Louis' tone was filled with doubt and disbelief. He had thought that Black Star was joking.

Han Xiao nodded but suddenly changed the topic.

"But before we work together, I have something to tell you… Don't be afraid of what I'm about to say…"

"Afraid?"

The Pope found it funny and did not think much of it.

"We've even experienced an enemy like the World Tree. What else can we be afraid of? Just tell us. We've seen all kinds of storms. We won't be scared."

Han Xiao raised his brows with a playful expression.

Chapter 1450: I gradually understand everything

"Alright, what I'm going to say next is the truth about the transition of the entire universe. It's more important than anything you've experienced in the past and present. I'll say this in advance. If you have any schedule later, clear it all."

Han Xiao saw the look of disapproval on their faces and shook his head.

"The truth of the universe?"

The three of them looked at each other. Seeing that Han Xiao did not seem to be joking, they could not help but be skeptical.

Han Xiao snapped his fingers and summoned a virtual screen that was playing the virtual image of the birth and death of the universe. He then explained,

"When the universe comes to an end, everything will return to nothingness. The phenomena like the heat death of the universe and the Big Crunch are the result of many scientists' guesses or foreseeing of the universe. All kinds of signs and experiments show that these are all very likely to be the correct doomsday models, but this is only under normal circumstances… The direction of our universe does not follow the most primitive laws of nature. Long ago, our universe was modified by a final civilization, and the fundamental laws of the Information Form changed. On the day of the end of our universe, what awaits us is not the heat death of the universe or the Big Crunch, but a phenomenon called the Great Reboot."

"The Great Reboot?"

The three of them were confused.

It was not that the scientific research community did not have similar speculations, but it was not the mainstream theory. Without conclusive sources, most of the evidence came from unknown items created by the information state disturbance. For example, the Virtual Mutiny Virus from back then was suspected to be from a civilization before the Great Reboot. However, it was not enough to be ironclad evidence, because it was not certain if it was an earlier civilization or a civilization from the unexplored universe.

Thus, Marbruce and the other two were not unfamiliar with this term. They were only confused as to why Han Xiao was so certain of the existence of the Great Reboot.

Han Xiao looked at the three of them and said slowly,

"The 'Great Reboot' I'm talking about is different from what you guys understand… The final civilization's modification of the underlying laws of the universe has caused the universe to deviate from the laws of the natural end. Therefore, the time of the end has been brought forward by a lot, and every Great Reboot is a brand new Iteration. New civilizations reproduce in the universe that has returned to zero. However, due to the shortening of development time, the strength of each of the iteration civilizations is infinitely lower than the Final Civilization that had initially established the Great Reboot."

"So, this is bad news?" Marbruce pondered. "If that's the case, all civilizations will develop from the beginning, and no one will be able to survive the end of the universe and reach the so-called… what did that popular phrase say, transcend worldliness?"

Han Xiao shook his head and said, "This is the main point I want to talk about. Although the Great Reboot causes the universe to return to zero, things from different Iterations will be passed down to the new Iteration through special means, and this medium is the Sanctum that all of you are longing for."

The three of them were stunned.

Han Xiao continued, "The initial goal of the final civilization to modify the universe was to continue their civilization through a reboot. They failed, but it was not a waste of effort. The Sanctum was their legacy. It was originally a reserve storage for life tinders, but a special Information Form Mutation appeared during the changes of the Iterations and became the Sanctum today. This is the only thing that is known to not disappear during the Great Reboot.

"The purpose of the Sanctum is to store the Information Form state of the development of every Iteration, and during each Great Reboot, a portion of Information Form will be randomly integrated into the new iteration of the universe. Therefore, when the universe is rebooted, it will not be completely zero. Instead, its underlying laws will constantly undergo changes in the Iterations. In this way, the achievements of each iteration will be passed down to the later iterations. For example, the current secondary dimension world is the inheritance of a past Iteration and not a natural phenomenon."

"So, you're saying that… the universe we're living in now is not the most primitive universe but a world that has been changed countless times? The Sanctum is equivalent to a… uh, processor?" Louis probed.

Han Xiao nodded. "More or less. Generations of civilizations treated the Sanctum as a way to get through the Great Reboot, so the Sanctum continued to develop all kinds of new functions. The Sanctum Revival is just one of them. The most important thing about the Sanctum is that it stored all the information of the Civilizations of the earlier Iterations, as well as their last words before the end of the world, all for future generations to refer to. This is a long relay that spanned countless Iterations, just for someone to break this cycle one day."

Hearing this, the three of them were shocked. Although Han Xiao's tone was very calm, when they thought of the scene of generations of civilizations working together toward the same goal, they could not help but be stunned by such a grand undertaking.

However, two seconds later, the three of them came to their senses, and their breathing suddenly became heavy.

At this moment, they suddenly realized that if what Black Star said was true, the information stored in the Sanctum would be an immeasurable amount of wealth.

As for Black Star, he could have held onto this wealth alone. If he did not say it, they would never have been able to get a share of it. However, he chose to say it instead of developing it himself. Was he that selfless?

It was precisely because they had thought this through that the three of them were even more shocked. For a moment, they fell silent, silently digesting the shock in their hearts.

After a while, the Pope said hesitantly, "You want to work with us to develop the Sanctum, is it because you want to get through the Great Reboot? Although what you just said is indeed quite shocking, let me be direct. The so-called Great Reboot should be very far away from us, right? Isn't it too early to worry about this…"

Hearing this, Han Xiao smiled faintly. "You think it's early?"

"Hmm…" Seeing this, the Pope could not help but widen his eyes in shock." Could it be that the end of our universe is coming, and the Great Reboot is here? "

The other two trembled in shock and disbelief.

"It wasn't easy for us to defeat the World Tree Civilization, and we enjoyed a rare moment of relaxation. I didn't expect…" Marbruce had mixed feelings.

However, Han Xiao shook his head and said, "You're mistaken. It's still too early for us to reach the end of this Iteration."

The three of them heaved a sigh of relief.

However, before they could completely relax, Han Xiao suddenly said something shocking, stunning them.

"But you've already been rebooted."

As soon as he finished speaking…

The Pope was stunned.

"What do you mean?"

"Four times." Han Xiao raised four fingers and said slowly, "Our universe has been rebooted four times… In the previous Iteration, you guys were the final civilizations. You guys used an Information Form Stripping Plan and successfully passed the Great Reboot, but you did not really enter the new universe of the next iteration. Instead, you guys became a sealed dark universe that cycled and restarted on its own… In other words, you guys have died a few times, but you don't know it yet!"

The three of them were dumbfounded.

During this period of time, Han Xiao had been trying to gain access to the First Sanctum. Every time he went in and out, the time he spent became shorter and shorter. When his access reached level fifteen, the flow of time finally converged. The time ratio of the main universe to the Sanctum was one to one, and the contents of the message board were finally unlocked.

At this point, Han Xiao finally understood everything. The messages from the bottom fourth to the last paragraph of the Sanctum were all left by the 'three Universal Civilizations'!

The Celestial Star Alliance was located in the fifth last paragraph, and it was the Iteration just before the three Universal Civilizations. The fourth last section was the new Iteration after the Great Reboot, and the three Universal Civilizations were the final civilizations developed by the new Iteration. During that period, there was no such thing as the World Tree. The three Universal Civilizations slowly multiplied, and they finally discovered the Sanctum and learned all the information about Iteration.

Because the previous Celestial Star Alliance's plan was very desirable, the three Universal Civilizations inherited it and improved it, forming the 'Information Form stripping plan'.

However, the three Universal Civilizations at that time knew very well that with their accumulation, they did not have the absolute confidence to survive the Great Reboot and did not want to risk it all. Therefore, the true goal of this plan was not to completely overcome the Great Reboot but to buy more time for themselves. They wanted to strip away the Information Form state of the entire universe and try to imitate the operation of the Celestial Star Alliance. They wanted to exist in the secondary dimensions and the dark side of the universe in the New Iteration era and continuously reboot.

However, the difference was that the three Universal Civilizations followed the mindset of the Celestial Star Alliance and made almost perfect improvements. Thus, they successfully peeled out the 'Information Form state' of the entire Iteration and formed a closed dark side universe in the next Iteration. It existed based on the Information Form state and was like a 'virtual' world, 'developing side by side' at a faster time flow. It was like a parallel line, difficult to intersect with the 'real' Iteration's main universe and difficult to interfere with each other.

After Han Xiao found out about the contents of the message board, he sorted out the time relationship. If the Celestial Star Alliance was the first iteration, then the three Universal Civilizations would be the final civilizations of the second iteration. They would activate the information form stripping plan and turn into the dark side universe of the third iteration, and the third iteration would be the true current iteration.

It was also at this point that Han Xiao realized that the Sanctum would not leave any information form empty shells for the current Iteration, and there was no such thing as a 'tombstone'. The three Universal Civilizations and the World Tree Civilization that he saw in the Sanctum were actually the second iteration remains. There was no content inside because they had been 'stripped' and became the dark side universe of the third Iteration.

However, the cycle of the dark side universe was not the same as the Celestial Star Alliance. Instead, it formed a 'small reboot' pattern. The three Universal Civilizations of the Second Iteration used the characteristics of the Sanctum to add new patterns every time the universe was rebooted, allowing the dark side universe to be included in the influence of the Sanctum.

What was different from the 'Great Reboot' was that every 'small reboot' in the dark universe did not return to zero but was formed based on a fixed Information Form state template, which meant that there would definitely be organizations like the three Universal Civilizations. Before the three Universal Civilizations came into contact with the Sanctum, their development trajectories were the same. Han Xiao called this situation 'dark side Iteration'.

Therefore, every time the dark side universe went through a small reboot, there would be an improved version of the dark side Iteration. It was just that there was a chance for 'Information Form Mutation' to occur. The three Universal Civilizations used this method to buy themselves more time, and they obtained more opportunities to test their luck.

However, this plan could not bring about eternity. After some calculations, there was an upper limit to the information form stripping plan. Their dark side universe would only exist in the third iteration at most. If they were to go through the Great Reboot and enter the fourth iteration, then their dark side universe would disappear… unless they could enter the real iteration main universe from the dark side universe and turn from 'virtual' to 'real'.

Therefore, after the three Universal Civilizations successfully entered the dark side universe, their goal was to break the seal of the dark side universe and return to the real main universe of the third Iteration.

The third last to last messages on the Sanctum's message board represented the three dark side Iterations of the dark side universe. Currently, Han Xiao was in the fourth dark side Iteration, and these four dark side Iterations had all happened during the third Iteration.

Since the Sanctum was not affected by the Iterations, the three Universal Civilizations used the message board of the Sanctum to record the experience of each trial and error. They made 'themselves' of the next dark side Iteration improve the path according to the previous experience, as well as create some key devices to improve the situation of the next dark side Iteration. This was the origin of the World Tree.

The three Universal Civilizations had added an Information Form Materialization device when they were in the second dark side Iteration (second last message), but in the third dark side Iteration, an information form mutation occurred. From a mechanical device, it turned into the World Tree with life force and went berserk… This was what Han Xiao experienced when he was a player in his previous life.

In the end, the three Universal Civilizations of the third dark side Iteration still opened the Sanctum and understood everything. Thus, they left behind the control terminal of the Information Form Materialization device. In the current fourth dark side Iteration, the Information Form mutation occurred and inherited the nature of restraint. But there was a change in its manifestation which became the World Tree's natural enemy, which was also the Pivotal Snake.

On the other hand, in the second dark side Iteration, the three Universal Civilizations had used the Information Form Materialization device that had yet to mutate and failed in the end. They had discovered that the reason was that there was a bridge that lacked the 'True State'. Han Xiao had also figured out the concept of the 'True State', which was actually the Information Form carrier that existed in the true universe.

In other words, the dark side universe had to form an Information Form connection with the true universe. Only by being able to interfere with each other would the Information Form Materialization device work. Therefore, the three Universal Civilizations of the second dark side Iteration launched a plan, trying to change the underlying laws of the next dark side Iteration, causing the two 'parallel lines' of the dark side universe and the true universe to deviate and finally intersect.

In the end, when the third dark side Iteration arrived, the underlying laws of the dark side universe changed, and they successfully projected themselves into 'reality'. They successfully obtained a part of the Information Form carrier of the true universe, which was the existence of 'players'. Through 'log in', these individuals who lived in the true universe turned their 'True State' into 'information form state' and were pulled into the dark side universe to form the Information Form interface. This was everything that Han Xiao and countless players had experienced in his previous life.

However, the World Tree went berserk in the third dark side Iteration. After the World Tree War in his previous life, the three Universal Civilizations obtained the Sanctum pathway from the Holy Accord Organization and learned everything. They inherited the heritage of countless civilizations, and their technology improved by leaps and bounds. At a level that the players could not come into contact with, the three Universal Civilizations came up with a new plan. They gathered the power of civilizations and built the 'control terminal' of the World Tree. At the same time, they lowered the cost of the World Tree going berserk in the fourth dark side Iteration.

Other than that, due to the players' version updates, the three Universal Civilizations of the third dark side Iteration felt that the 'True State' bridge was not stable enough, so they decided to spend a lot of resources strengthening the 'True State' connection with the next dark side Iteration.

Because the dark side universe and the true universe had already formed a preliminary Information Form interference, the three Universal Civilizations decided to build a stable interference bridge instead of intermittent bridge-like logins. The only targets they could choose were these individual Information Form records that had already been logged into the dark side universe, so they randomly selected a target to enter the dark side universe completely, forming a stable connection.

As long as this idea was correct, the dark side universe would be able to reverse-transform the 'Information Form state' to the 'True State' through this interference bridge, break free from the seal, and return to the true universe… In a more understandable way, it would be like installing a carrier bag for the so-called 'reality', which contained the entire dark side universe and the entire Galaxy World.

This was the truth that Han Xiao had learned from the Sanctum, and what happened after that was not recorded on the message board.

After knowing all of this, he had a rough guess about what happened after that. He suspected that the reason why he had 'transmigrated' was actually because he had been randomly selected as the 'stable interference bridge' that strengthened the Information Form entanglement between the dark side universe and the true universe.

His own Information Form state had been completely captured, and he had come to this dark universe from the 'reality'. Therefore, his 'real' self had disappeared, and he no longer had any information about himself. He had never seen his other self, who should be a 'player', all these years. Han Xiao suspected that this was the reason.

As for the dark side universe of the fourth dark side Iteration, it caused the time of the true universe to regress by ten years. Han Xiao did not know the reason, but he guessed that it was because the third dark side Iteration had more Information Form interference with the true universe when it was 'capturing' him, which affected the other party's time. However, he did not know if this was a reversal of time across the entire universe or only across a small area. However, from another point of view, this was also proof that the dark side universe used the 'True State' to create Information Form entanglements that could already cause a substantial change to the true universe.

Now, Han Xiao had roughly pieced together all the reasons from the Sanctum records and his own guesses. In his opinion, this series of guesses was more than seventy percent reliable.

Han Xiao hid part of his speculations and explained the secret.

After hearing all of this, only shock and disbelief could be seen on the faces of Marbruce, Louis, and the Pope. They looked at Han Xiao with their mouths slightly open, completely dumbfounded.

"This, this…"

The Pope was dumbfounded.

Although they were the rulers of the three Universal Civilizations and had seen countless storms, the information that Han Xiao had just given them had already exceeded their acceptance range.

After a long time, Marbruce turned to Louis and said with hesitation,

"Um… did you understand?"

"I didn't either…" Marbruce replied blankly.

Chapter 1451: Speculation and Conjecture

The three of them took a while to digest the information that Han Xiao had given them.

Louis hesitated.

"Black Star, are you trying to trick us…"

"Unfortunately, not this time." Han Xiao shrugged.

Marbruce had a strange expression on his face. "In other words, we are all people who died and reincarnated a few times. This is equivalent to being trapped in a sealed secondary dimension. Our final goal is to break through this secondary dimension and return to the main universe?"

"Hmm, although the difference is quite big, you can understand it that way." Han Xiao blinked.

"It means that everything our civilization has experienced from the beginning is a predestined development trajectory. It has already happened a few times, and it was 'personally' built by us?"

"Something like that." Han Xiao nodded.

"Let me recover…"

The Pope pressed his forehead and felt his blood pressure rising.

All of a sudden, the three of them felt as though the values that they had formed in their lives had been shattered. In the face of such a situation, they realized that all the political and military problems that they usually considered became insignificant.

"So, we're that powerful…"

Marbruce was still in shock.

Han Xiao ruthlessly interrupted his imagination. "It's not that you guys are strong, but the final three Universal Civilizations are. Compared to the 'you' of the past, you guys are like three little brothers. Don't flatter the three Universal Civilizations of now. Without me, you guys would still not have known anything."

"..."

The three of them felt a little hurt.

Although this is the truth, can't you let us indulge a little?

However, no matter what, the three of them still felt like they had been blessed by their ancestors after learning about these secrets.

"Black Star, you really gave us a scare…" Marbruce smiled bitterly." My mind is in a mess right now. I don't even know what to do. "

Han Xiao raised his brows and joked, "Didn't you say you've seen all kinds of storms? Have you seen this before?"

"Ahem, I think we should talk about how to break the seal of the dark side universe and return to the true universe…"

The Pope's face darkened, and he quickly changed the topic, not wanting to admit that he was too careless.

However, Han Xiao did not give a direct answer. Instead, he slowly said,

"I know you guys still have some doubts in your hearts, thinking that I made this up. When you guys enter the Sanctum and confirm that the information I'm talking about is correct, we'll talk about what to do next… By the way, let me remind you guys, the Sanctum requires authorization to access the Iteration messages. You guys will only know the basic information when you enter the Sanctum for the first time, which is information like Iteration and Great Reboot. As for information like dark side Iteration and continuous reboot, you guys won't be able to see it for the time being. I only learned about these things after completely unlocking the authorization."

"Oh, so it was like that…"

The three of them had not witnessed the functions of the Sanctum with their own eyes, so they could only listen to Han Xiao's explanation. However, they believed most of it, because there was no need for Black Star to lie to them about something that could be so easily verified.

However, Marbruce and the other two felt an itch in their hearts. This feeling was like watching a suspense movie. They had only seen the beginning, but Black Star knew all the details and did not tell them who the killer was. This made them very curious.

However, the three of them did have some concerns, and they did not dare completely believe what Han Xiao said. They would only be at ease if they entered the Sanctum to take a look.

"I will send you the method to enter the Sanctum in a while. Also, I will give you three more sets of Sanctum keys. You can enter by yourselves, lest you say that I did something."

Han Xiao said casually.

He was the only one who could quickly create the Sanctum Keys. Even the three Universal Civilizations, which had plenty of resources, needed time to collect materials. Therefore, without his help, the three Universal Civilizations could not enter the Sanctum frequently. This was also the reason why he had the confidence to control the Sanctum and did not mind letting the three Universal Civilizations enter the Sanctum.

"That is the best."

The three of them hurriedly nodded like obedient children.

"Alright, then you guys digest the truth of the universe and Iterations. I won't disturb you guys any longer. I'll send you the materials later."

Han Xiao nodded and hung up.

The remote projection disappeared, and the three of them looked at each other with different expressions.

"I didn't expect Black Star to bring such intelligence… If what he said is true, then our future plans will have to be reorganized."

"That's right. If the situation is true, then there's no point in us developing peacefully here. We have to break through fate and fulfill the wishes of our past lives, entering the so-called true universe."

"Let's not talk about this for now. Let's start from the beginning…"

The three of them gathered their heads together and started discussing.

...

Supers Holy Land, Leader's Office.

Han Xiao's eyes flashed, and he returned to his room. Complicated emotions appeared in his eyes.

He had pretended to be confident and calm in front of the three Universal Civilizations. In fact, when he found out about the truth from the Sanctum, he was also shocked, but it also solved many of his doubts.

In fact, Han Xiao still had many of his own secrets that he had not told the heads of the three Universal Civilizations just now. For example, the existence of the interface meant that there were three possibilities.

The first was that the interface was a special product formed when the true state of the true universe was transformed into the Information Form state of the dark side universe. It was like when a high-dimensional object descended into a low dimension, it had a special advantage. It was like how a piece of paper hid no secrets to humans, providing information that low-dimensional objects could not contain.

The second possibility was that it was the product of Information Form mutation.

The third guess was that the three Universal Civilizations of the second dark side Iteration had projected the 'information cluster' of the dark side universe into the true universe through 'login', and the interface was the necessary medium to complete this step. It could be considered a special 'retractor' or 'recorder'. Therefore, it might have been specially created by the three Universal Civilizations to ensure that the True State would remain in the dark side universe for a long time.

However, no matter which one it was, the interface was something unique to the dark side universe and could not enter the true universe. The evidence that made Han Xiao speculate this was that when he entered the Sanctum, the interface would disappear. Because the Sanctum did not only exist in the dark side universe, the interface lost its effect.

As for his 'special' interface, Han Xiao had a guess.

In his opinion, this was either because the three Universal Civilizations of the third dark side Iteration wanted to build a stable interference bridge and deliberately created life support for the 'Information Form Individual' who had completely entered the dark side universe, ensuring that he could live 'stably' in the dark side universe and reduce the chances of him dying due to various accidents, or it was the result of the Information Form mutation on the normal interface in the dark side Iteration.

According to the various performances of the interface, Han Xiao was more inclined toward the former. When the interface triggered a mission, more information would usually be revealed in the mission introduction. Because the development trajectory of the dark universe was almost fixed, the three Universal Civilizations of the third dark side Iteration could modify the interface into something similar to a 'Prophet'. Of course, this did not exclude the fact that their interface had the hidden principle of monitoring the entire dark universe.

In addition, when the players went online (the True States Interference), he would be able to enter the players' forums through the interface and spy on the communication between the 'True States'. During the version update period, the forums were also frozen for him. From this perspective, the special interface on him was indeed like an important medium and channel to communicate with the True States.

This reminded Han Xiao of the two Information Form threads he had seen on the interface when he used the Information Form Obliteration vision. One was connected to him, while the other extended infinitely. Now that he thought about it, the connection on this end probably represented the entire dark side universe. This seemed to support the idea.

On the other hand, Han Xiao also speculated about the theory behind the flow of time in the version update. In the mainstream scientific theories of the Galaxy, time was relative, not absolute. From this point of view, based on the content of the message board in the Sanctum, he felt that the time of the dark universe and the true universe did not have any connection, only the difference in relative speed.

The true universe was the foundation of the third Iteration. The dark side universe had to depend on it to exist, but the relative time flow of the dark side universe was faster and went through reboots again and again without affecting the other side. However, when the players came online and caused the dark side universe and the true universe to become entangled in Information Form, the flow of time between the two sides was locked. The time flow of the dark side universe and the true universe passed at a stable ratio, which was one to six… The reason behind this was that the true universe still occupied the dominant position, and the players whose 'foundation' existed in the true universe would not be affected.

When the True State of the players' temporary logins disappeared, the level of Information Form interference plummeted, and the flow of time in the dark side universe would be disconnected from the true universe… This conjecture showed that the version update would only take one or two days for the players while many years would have passed in the Galaxy World. Han Xiao felt that this was quite possible.

He even suspected that starting from the second dark side Iteration, the frequency of the Information Form mutation in the dark side universe was very likely the change brought about by the third dark side Iteration's introduction of the True States… If the true universe and Sanctum were seen as existences of a higher dimension, then the projected projection would produce distortions, and a 'surreal' phenomenon would occur, causing the third dark side Iteration's Information Form Materialization device to become the World Tree, and the fourth dark side Iteration's control terminal to become the Pivotal Snake.

"Other than this reason, perhaps the dark side universe is the same as the Celestial Star Alliance Dimension. Only an external Information Form carrier can greatly change its development trajectory, bringing new variables and accidents… Even if the dark side universe is not a rigid cycle, such variables might still be needed."

Han Xiao's expression changed.

Although many of these theories were speculations based on the truth revealed by the Sanctum messages, he felt that they were very likely.

"Even if this is a relay across Iterations, every civilization wants to be the last one. As long as there's a glimmer of hope, every civilization wants to continue surviving, and no one wants to go extinct. It's understandable for the three Universal Civilizations to do this, but…"

Han Xiao shook his head with mixed feelings.

If all his deductions were correct, then he would be the hope of the entire dark side universe…

But to him, this was a multiple-choice question.

Chapter 1452: Choice and Entry

Crack…

Han Xiao opened the cabinet and took out a box of unopened cigarettes from it. He tore open the packaging and took out a black cigarette wrapped in gold patterns. He swiped at it with his finger, and an electric spark lit it up. He held it in his mouth and slowly took a puff. Green smoke rose and covered his complicated expression, and his disappointed eyes could be seen through the smoke.

Ever since he entered the galaxy, Han Xiao had basically quit smoking. It had been almost a hundred years since he had last tasted a smoke, but today, he lit up a cigarette.

This was not an easy choice. If his hometown was the real universe of the current dynasty, then once the dark side universe returned, it would be like a dove taking over a magpie's nest, and countless powerful civilizations would sweep through the galaxy. Han Xiao did not know if there were any advanced civilizations in the real universe of the current dynasty because his hometown was only a surface-level civilization and could not explore the entire universe. However, his hometown was an information interface, so it would definitely be the first to face a change.

To his hometown, this was either a good thing or a bad thing. The only thing he was certain of was that his hometown would never develop freely again. It would definitely be interfered with by the advanced civilizations, just like the various small civilizations and surface civilizations in the galactic society.

However, the three Universal Civilizations, which had already gone through four dark side changes, were already half a step into the real universe. They were only one step away from the real universe and they had a chance to truly get through the Reboot. This was the ultimate dream passed down by the Final Civilizations after countless generations. Now that he had the ability to help them succeed… should he watch the efforts of the three Universal Civilizations go to waste? Or should he give them the final push?

Although Han Xiao was conflicted, he knew that he already had an answer in his heart. Revealing the Sanctum information to the three Universal Civilizations was to help him make up his mind not to turn back.

This was a great achievement that was supported by countless generations. It was also a great honor for him to be one of them. Furthermore, it was also related to the survival of the universe. The time he had spent in the galactic society had long exceeded the length of his life in the real universe. It was impossible for him to not have any feelings for the galactic society.

Furthermore, with Han Xiao's current experience, he felt that the possibility of his hometown becoming the current Final Civilization of this iteration was extremely low. Perhaps even becoming a Star System Civilization would be an extravagant hope.

In the middle of the 21st century, before he entered the dark side universe, the societal problems in his hometown were already very acute. It was like a train that had been overloaded for many years, with all kinds of failures coming one after another.

Due to the complex geopolitical situation, the entire civilization was wasting precious' birthplace resources', and the efficiency of resources was low. There were many problems that could only be solved before entering the interstellar era, and only then would the cost be minimized. Their hometown did not have an efficient collective will when their technology was low, and once such an opportunity was missed, it would be difficult to see it again. As the saying goes, a small boat is easy to turn around. The larger the body, the harder it is to turn back, and it would be difficult to make any changes. Any slight movement might trigger an internal crisis that could destroy the entire civilization.

Although his hometown might have a chance to turn around in the future, according to the trend before Han Xiao entered the dark side universe, the development of his hometown, if analyzed on the scale of civilization and the universe, was truly in a precarious situation. Therefore, after the birth of the virtual network in his previous life, it quickly became a haven for countless people to escape from reality.

According to this trend, the final outcome of his hometown might be natural death or being destroyed or captured by an unknown foreign civilization. In his eyes, most of the areas around his hometown did not have the qualifications to become the overlord of the universe… unless there were no competitors.

However, due to the existence of the Sanctum, this was clearly impossible.

Therefore, Han Xiao felt that since it would be difficult for his hometown to become the 'winner' of a single era, when the conversion of the dark universe was completed—while it might bring about risks—it would also bring along the successful plan to get through the Great Reboot. This would mean unlimited resources and techniques.

The current final Civilizations might not have matured yet, and the three Universal Civilizations would most likely replace it and rule it for a long time. This would be somewhat unfair to the current Iterated Civilizations, but in this regard, no civilization would not give in to be the leader of the universe. It was very difficult for the weak to choose their own fate… Of course, there was also the possibility of a powerful civilization existing in the real universe, but the civilization level of their hometown was too low for him to be aware of it.

In addition, Han Xiao felt that he had come to the Dark Side Universe because of the three Universal Civilizations. Perhaps he should return the favor.

"In the end, I still have my own selfish motives…"

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and suddenly shook his head.

He had never thought of himself as a selfless person. Apart from these concerns that involved the big picture, there were also reasons for him to choose to convert the Dark Side Universe.

He seemed to have used up all his luck to become the 'Stable Interference Bridge' that was randomly selected. If he did not do anything, the Dark Side Universe would only experience another round of reboot and might not have much of an impact on this place. However, in the next Dark Side, the Dark Side Universe would pull in a new True Form carrier and become a new 'Stable Interference Bridge' to replace him.

Due to the uniqueness of his identity, Han Xiao could not guarantee that he would become a member of the Dark Side Universe's development trajectory after the Dark Side underwent another iteration. Becoming a Transcendent might not mean that he could literally transcend an iteration. The 'Small Reboot' of the Dark Side Universe might still cause him to disappear… Rather than saying that his choice was to save the Dark Side Universe, it would be more accurate to say that it was to save himself.

Therefore, this might be his only chance. Han Xiao did not want to gamble.

"Phew… so this is an all-out invasion?"

With this in mind, Han Xiao calmed himself down and stopped smoking. He extinguished the cigarette roll that was only one-third burnt in the ashtray without hesitation.

A few days later, in a certain military-restricted area in the Central Galaxy.

Three small spaceships hovered outside the space fortress, ready to go.

In the military command tower on the side, the remote projection of the three Universal Civilizations' Ruler stood in front of the window, staring at the three spaceships outside with a nervous and expectant expression. The operators in the room were adjusting the parameters in front of the instruments.

This time, Han Xiao's remote projection appeared in the room, attracting the attention of three people.

"How's the preparation going?"

"We have already filled up the Sanctum key in the synthesis device according to the method you provided," Marbruce replied immediately.

Han Xiao nodded. "What about the candidates to enter the Sanctum?"

Louis said with a deep voice, "We have all chosen a spaceship full of elites, and their loyalty is reliable. Our side will be led by Oulou, and the Crimson Dynasty will be led by Clotti."

Han Xiao looked at the Pope and said, "What about you? Are you going to let Wuornos take the lead?"

"I originally planned to let Wuornos enter the Sanctum, but he happened to have left some time ago, so I found another direct descendant." The Pope shook his head.

"…Is that so? What a twist of events."

Han Xiao's expression was complicated.

Due to the fact that he needed to accumulate the authority of the Sanctum, he did not know if the Arcane Church would allow Wuornos to become the Sanctum Explorer even after he returned…

Great, he had missed out on another huge benefit. He always felt that Wuornos seemed to miss out on everything good. This guy was really unlucky.

Seeing that Han Xiao did not speak, Louis said, "If there's no problem, shall we begin?"

"Go ahead, I'll watch from here." Han Xiao nodded.

Marbruce nodded and gave the order.

Very soon, a few rays of light shot out from the military fortress and gathered in midair, slowly turning into three Sanctums. The Sanctums Key that Han Xiao had provided each led to different Sanctums, and they were all opened at the same time.

Han Xiao had seen this scene many times and did not have much of a reaction. However, the heads of the three Universal Civilizations stared with their eyes wide open, staring at the changes in the scenery outside the window. It was as though they wanted to memorize all the details of the Sanctum passageway.

The next moment, the three spaceships started moving and entered different passages of the Sanctum. The Sanctum's light then spun and contracted before disappearing from everyone's sight.

Only at this moment did the three Universal Civilizations' leaders relax. They heaved a sigh of relief and were filled with anticipation and anxiety. They were afraid that something would happen during their trip to the Sanctum, or they might not bring back the information they wanted.

"This is their first time entering the Sanctum. Their authority is very low, and the time flow is very different. It will take them a very long time to return."

Han Xiao explained.

Marbruce nodded absent-mindedly. Suddenly, he thought of something and turned to look at Han Xiao.

"Since it will take a long time for them to return, let's not just blindly wait for them. We might as well use the time to solve some important problems."

Han Xiao raised his brows. "What do you want?"

"Initially, we wanted to wait until the galactic society recovered more than half of its strength before launching a military operation against the Star Alliance. However, the intelligence you brought disrupted our strategic plans, so I think it's better to solve this hidden danger as soon as possible… However, we alone cannot proceed with the highest efficiency, so…"

"So, you want my help?" Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and continued.

"That's what I meant." Marbruce nodded quickly.

Han Xiao turned to look at the other two. "You guys have the same idea?"

"I hope Your Excellency Black Star can help."

Louis and the Pope nodded as well.

Ever since they knew the truth about the Universe Iterations, they had become more relaxed. They were all in the same boat now, so helping the other party meant helping themselves, and they were no longer as reserved as before. They were just short of hugging Han Xiao's thigh and calling him daddy.

"…You guys are really impolite. Let me do some research then."

Looking at the three of them, Han Xiao's mouth twitched.

Originally, he did not want to interfere in this matter. However, given the current situation, if he did not settle the Star Alliance as soon as possible, there would be more variables in the plan of converting the dark universe. It was indeed not good.

Han Xiao thought about it and said slowly,

"If I can solve this problem with less bloodshed, that would be the best. I hope that my interference will allow them to accept reality faster…"

Chapter 1453: What? The World Tree Called?!

"What? Black Star and the three Universal Civilizations have privately agreed to open the Sanctum?!"

The surprised voice of the leader of the Star Arc sounded in the conference room of the Super Star Cluster Alliance.

A civilization leader nodded with a solemn expression. "I received some news. Black Star seems to have really shared the Sanctum information with the three Universal Civilizations."

"Is the news accurate?" The Star Arc Leader's expression turned solemn.

"Very reliable."

Hearing this, the expressions of all the Super Star Cluster leaders changed.

The three Universal Civilizations did not cover up Black Star's actions of sharing the Sanctum. This was not a secret that no one could not find out, but they did not disclose it to the outside world either. After knowing about their current situation, they did not have such thoughts for the time being. If not, they would have advertised it in the past to increase their reputation.

The composition of the three Sanctum keys that Han Xiao had given them, as well as the method of entering the Sanctum, were the three Universal Civilizations' top-secret information. Outsiders would not be able to find out about it, so the Super Star Cluster Alliance only knew about the appearance of the two sides cooperating to open the Sanctum. They did not know the exact reason and details.

"This is really strange. Now, the three Universal Civilizations, the Supers Holy Land, and we are already in a tripartite situation. The Sanctum is the core strength of the Supers Holy Land. Isn't Black Star helping the enemy? What does he mean by this?"

The leader was confused.

"Indeed, I don't understand either. Why does Black Star need to share the Sanctuary with the three Universal Civilizations?" Another civilization leader was puzzled. "In the past, when Beyond Grade As still existed as organizations, they did not share the Sanctum's information even when facing the suppression of the three Universal Civilizations. Now, the Supers Holy Land is already a huge force, comparable to the three Universal Civilizations. Why did they give out the Sanctum's information instead? Could it be that some chip has fallen into the hands of the three Universal Civilizations?"

"I feel that it's impossible for Black Star to be threatened by the three Universal Civilizations. There must be other reasons. Black Star might have other plans… We can't even rule out the possibility of them forming deep strategic cooperation."

"The World Tree has already been dealt with, what other strategic cooperation can they have? Could it be that they are fighting that third-party infiltrator? But is there a need for that? Both the three Universal Civilizations and Black Star can deal with the Star Alliance alone."

At this moment, one of the leaders hesitated for a moment and said carefully,

"…Have you ever thought that they might be working together against us?"

The room fell silent.

After a long time, the leader of the Star Arc swallowed his saliva and said, "Um… I don't think that's possible. We're lubricants between them. They probably won't gang up on us…"

"I don't think so…" Someone was worriedly singing the opposite tune." Could it be that our attitude of waiting for a good price was too blatant and angered both sides? "

Hearing that, everyone panicked.

After the structure of the war was established, they would circle around the three Universal Civilizations and the Supers Holy Land, jumping around to maintain balance.

According to their initial analysis, the three Universal Civilizations needed to form an alliance with them to suppress the Supers Holy Land. Therefore, they would definitely 'change their ways' and use a lot of benefits to rope them in. This was also the case in the early stages. Finally, they were no longer suppressed and had the space to develop freely. Using a different method, they achieved what they initially wanted to achieve through migration.

Logically speaking, if not for the rise of the Supers Holy Land, the Super Star Cluster would not have been able to do as they wished. Black Star had contributed to this, but because of the balance, they could not stay as close as they wanted to the Supers Holy Land. Otherwise, the three Universal Civilizations would definitely explode. Thus, they could only temporarily put aside the alliance agreement with Black Star and turn it into superficial cooperation.

The Supers Holy Land did not say anything about this. The Super Star Cluster Alliance had even specially called Black Star to apologize, and the other party did not seem to mind. Thus, the Super Star Cluster alliance had always been at ease and felt that this route was not a problem. They hoped to maintain a good cooperative relationship with both sides… But now that Black Star and the three Universal Civilizations had played such a card, they immediately felt uncertain.

It felt as if there were two enemies who were not on good terms with each other, and he had maintained a good relationship with both of them. Like a sticker for the three of them, he let everyone play together. However, one day, the two enemies suddenly made up for no reason. They put their arms around each other's shoulders and did not bring him along to play. Instead, he became the third person, isolated. This was very uncomfortable.

"I think we need to analyze it, but we can't rule out the possibility that such a factor is involved. We need to consider our attitude towards the Supers Holy Land and the three Universal Civilizations. We can't be too cold," the leader of the Star Arc said with a heavy tone.

The higher-ups of the Super Star Cluster felt their hearts turn weak the more they thought about it. They were too suspicious and scared themselves.

In the unexplored universe, Star Alliance capital.

"Ever since the World Tree fully invaded, the three Universal Civilizations have been in an increasingly difficult situation. In the past two years, they have lost almost six percent of their territory. I thought that they would be able to hold on for a few decades, but it seems like I've overestimated them. The three Universal Civilizations will not be able to withstand the attack of the World Tree at all. At this rate, the three Universal Civilizations will definitely be defeated in five to six years, the longest in thirteen to fourteen years!"

In the meeting room, the leader of the Star Alliance and the leaders of the various civilizations had smiles on their faces. The room was filled with happiness.

For more than a year since the World Tree invaded the interstellar society, they had been living a very happy life. Even their footsteps were light. Every time they read the "battle report" sent by the spies, they would look forward to the next episode because they were always full of surprises.

The more miserable the galactic society was, the happier they would be!

The leader of the Star Alliance knocked on the table and said with a smile, "Over the past year, the three Universal Civilizations were almost completely defeated by the World Tree. Black Star was heavily injured by the ambush and had exceeded the limits of his Indestructible Body. He had no choice but to fall into a deep sleep and slowly recuperate. Thus, the Sanctum Revival was temporarily terminated. The intel says that he is now the spiritual pillar of the galactic society to resist the external enemies. Once Black Star falls, the morale of the Galactic Alliance Army will collapse, and they will be forced to retreat on the battlefield… Therefore, it is obvious that without Black Star, the galactic allied forces are just a motley crew."

"Hehe, not bad, not bad." The leader of the Lore Civilization, Savignes, chuckled. "Furthermore, the reports from the first two episodes said that the mother planets of the three Universal Civilizations were attacked frequently and had no choice but to let many of the upper echelons take refuge. During the voyage, the Crimson Dynasty's spaceship was ambushed on a large scale, and the current leader, Marbruce, was cut in half at the waist, dying without a complete corpse. The previous Dynasty Ruler, Urranrell, was captured by the members of the World Tree, and it was said that the pillar of the nation, Clotti, went alone to save her. In the end, he was captured, but his will was firm. Thus, the World Tree gathered the members and violated Urranrell repeatedly in front of him, destroying Clotti's will before the World Tree devoured him and turned him into a slave…"

"Speaking of which, the peak Beyond Grade As of the galactic society either died or were injured. Manison's true body was exposed, and he was turned into a slave by the World Tree. All of his assets were used to support the enemy. Kasuyi's mind was shattered, and he became a fool. Wuornos was forced to participate in the battle, and the Church's National Treasure was almost shattered…"

These battle reports were all fabricated by Han Xiao's order to the lurkers who had already jumped out of hiding. He even added quite a number of personal gossips into them, which made it quite "exciting". As for the people involved in the battle report, they did not know that Han Xiao was making things up about them.

The members of the Star Alliance talked about the good news in the previous war reports with great interest. They wanted to see the suffering of the people of the galactic society and laugh.

After chatting for a while, the leader of the Star Alliance calmed down and knocked on the table.

"Although the defeat of the three Universal Civilizations is set in stone, and we have finally gotten rid of a huge threat, the World Tree is a new threat. When the war ends, we still need to pay attention to the World Tree."

"That's right. The failure of the three Universal Civilizations has proven how terrifying they are. Even if we reach the height of the three Universal Civilizations, we still won't be their match."

"Yeah, but time stands with us. As long as we keep developing, sooner or later—"

The leader of the Star Alliance was about to look forward to the future to cheer everyone on when the meeting room was suddenly pushed open.

Bang!

A secretary rushed in anxiously with an anxious look on his face. His eyes were filled with fear.

"Leaders, something bad has happened. We found traces of the World Tree army. The World Tree is attacking!"

"What?!"

Crash—

The expressions of all the Star Alliance's upper echelons changed drastically as they stood up!

Chapter 1454: Give Them a Taste of Their Own Medicine

Within the Star Alliance, the Margus Star System.

A long and narrow spatial rift cut through the starry sky like a knife cutting open the belly of the universe, splattering out endless green tides.

Countless World Tree battleships flew out from the wormhole and formed an army. They turned into dense streams of light and dispersed in all directions, attacking the planets on the star map.

The World Tree fleet was traveling at an extremely fast speed. Before long, a prosperous planet was in sight. The defense troops of this planet had already taken off and were distributed in outer space, ready to fight against the invasion.

Buzz!

At this moment, there was a flash of light in the distance. A huge wave of starships covered in starlight approached rapidly. The outer armor of the starships was engraved with the Star Alliance's insignia. This was the military's rapid support unit. They were stationed at the nearby military fortress and were in charge of the daily security in the area.

In the main starship of the Star Alliance's rapid support troops, the middle-aged commander with a strong temperament gripped the edge of the table tightly with both hands. He gritted his teeth and looked at the enemy troops outside the window, countless times more numerous than his own. His heart was in agony as he let out a hoarse roar:

"Unit 17 and 18, fall down. Immediately organize the people to board the ship and escape. The rest… attack! Stall for time!"

As soon as the order was given, the rapid support troops immediately charged towards the incoming World Tree.

Facing an unrivaled opponent, the Star Alliance's fleet still chose to counterattack. This scene was very tragic. It was like an isolated and helpless troop enduring the endless encirclement of countless enemies.

However, the difference in strength would not be reduced because of this. Their fearlessness could not stop the spreading of the green tide. The world-destroying green tide did not stop and easily drowned the armed fleet.

The Star Alliance fleet's counterattack only caused a small ripple before disappearing into the endless green tide.

Roots tore through the sky and pierced into the flourishing planet like straws, devouring the matter and energy inside and turning them into their own nourishment.

In the flagship of the World Tree fleet, the Heart Tree King looked down at the planet with a glimmer in his eyes. Vast psychic energy had already covered the entire planet, hypnotizing all living beings to give up on escaping and voluntarily enter the roots to become a member of the World Tree.

The Heart Tree King shook his head as he watched the last few Star Alliance battleships explode into pieces under the concentrated fire of the World Tree fleet.

"It's just a futile struggle…"

He turned to look at the countless soldiers in the cabin and saw a feverish look on each of their faces. War was their specialty.

Sensing the Heart Tree King's gaze, everyone raised their arms and shouted.

"For the mother tree! For Father God!"

After Black Star subdued the World Tree, he became the 'Father God' in the hearts of all the members of the World Tree. His will was above the Mother Tree's.

The Heart Tree King muttered to himself before retracting his gaze and looking at the starry sky. His gaze seemed to be able to penetrate the endless distance and lock onto the mother planet of the Star Alliance.

...

In the conference room in the Star Alliance's capital.

Unlike the joyous atmosphere a few days ago, the room was filled with gloom, fear, despair, anxiety, and other negative emotions.

In the past few days, news of the World Tree's invasion broke out in various parts of their territory. It was as if the entire Star Alliance was in danger overnight and countless planets had fallen.

The upper echelons of the Star Alliance were no longer as high-spirited as they were a few days ago. At this moment, they looked haggard and their clothes were in a mess. They had not slept or rested for the past few days as they argued intensely.

"Isn't the World Tree Civilization still fighting with the three Universal Civilizations? Why did they invade us?"

The Star Alliance Leader frowned and looked exhausted. His eyes were bloodshot and his voice was extremely hoarse.

Savignes trembled slightly and said with a shaking voice, "Could it be that the World Tree Civilization feels that they have already crippled the three civilizations and wants to fight on two fronts? What should we do?"

The upper echelons of the Star Alliance frowned.

They thought that the three Universal Civilizations were still fighting the World Tree to the death, but because they had discovered their location, they had deployed a portion of their forces to fight with them. This feeling was like they were enjoying the sufferings of others, but the sufferings suddenly appeared on their own head.

"What else can we do? Since the World Tree is here, we can only resist!" Someone slammed the table to hide the fear in his heart.

Just as he said that, someone immediately objected and said loudly,

"What fight! Even the three Universal Civilizations were no match for the World Tree, they were crippled in a few years. We can't defend our own territories at all. We should quickly migrate the refugees, preserve our tinders, and abandon our territories!"

"How can we do that? At least we still have the strength to fight! The World Tree is wreaking havoc in my territory. As long as everyone sends out reinforcements, we will definitely be able to defeat the World Tree!" someone else said in a low voice.

"Bullsh*t! We don't even have enough troops, how can we help you?!" Another person shouted.

This argument instantly ignited the fuse. Everyone's emotions had been like a spring that had been pushed to the limit these past few days. With this, all the accumulated dissatisfaction in their hearts erupted. They directly split into two groups. One group was advocating war while the other was in favor of escaping. The argument was extremely intense.

If not for the fact that most of them were projections, everyone would have rolled up their sleeves and started fighting.

The Star Alliance was formed by the alliance of more than forty civilizations. They were not united in the first place and each had their own standpoints for benefits. Usually, they could be gathered together, but when faced with the pressure of a powerful foreign invasion, internal conflicts immediately erupted.

Some of the upper echelons of the civilizations who had been against causing trouble couldn't restrain themselves anymore and started complaining loudly.

"Everyone, calm down! Calm down… We still have other paths. We can't resist the World Tree on our own, but since the three Universal Civilizations are in the same situation as us, perhaps we can take the initiative to communicate with them and join forces against the enemy… As for our previous plans, we can put them aside for now. The most important thing is to defeat the World Tree together. They will definitely know the severity of the matter. We will settle the score with the three Universal Civilizations later in the future. We have to protect ourselves first before we can talk about the future…"

The Star Alliance Leader raised his suggestion loudly and tried his best to ease the atmosphere. However, it was useless. Everyone was speechless at his suggestion and turned a deaf ear to it. They continued arguing and the situation was getting out of control.

In the past, many members of the Star Alliance would not have been so disrespectful to him. However, now that their own civilizations were on the brink of death, no one cared about him anymore.

Everyone had a big fight. Many people were furious. They stopped talking and directly went offline. They did not want to listen to the unified dispatch of the Star Alliance anymore. They decided to fly off on their own when disaster struck.

Not long after, there was no one left in the meeting room. The Star Alliance Leader sat alone in his seat, his heart filled with bitterness.

...

After the quarrel, the leaders of a few civilizations gave out orders without any hesitation. They did not listen to the Star Alliance's orders at all and packed up their resources and population. They started to escape hurriedly, preparing to escape from the Star Alliance's territory and enter the unexplored universe.

Initially, although most civilizations were angry and panicked, they had not decided to abandon their homes. However, when they saw someone running away decisively, they immediately became anxious. Since the others had already run away, if they did not keep up, wouldn't they be staying behind to help others cover their retreat? How could this do!

The chain reaction happened very quickly. One after another, the members of the Star Alliance didn't dare to delay any longer. They also started to migrate and escape, no longer caring about the Star Alliance's agreement.

When these member countries refused to listen to the orders, the Star Alliance's mechanism was quickly paralyzed. The huge Star Alliance seemed to have broken up overnight, and the fleets of various civilizations began to escape and part ways.

In the past, many members would not easily go against the unified order of the Star Alliance, or else they would be isolated by others. But now, they could not care so much. When the World Tree attacked, the Star Alliance immediately had a disagreement of opinion. This joint Universal Civilization was destined to fall apart. No one planned to wait for death in a group. They only wanted others to stall the enemy so they could escape.

This was Han Xiao's intention. The weakness of the Star Alliance's structure was too obvious, which was that they had too many interests and did not have the strength of a dominant civilization. They could barely coalesce, and their opinions could not be completely unified.

Usually, the members of the Star Alliance had their reservations, but once they were in a life and death crisis, it would definitely be difficult for them to unite. There was an 80% chance that they would split up. As long as this collective will was disassembled, the Star Alliance's small giant would be dismembered. Its resistance would drop by several levels, and it would lose most of its fighting spirit.

Back then, the Star Alliance had secretly leaked the information, wanting to cause internal conflict in the galactic society. Han Xiao's action was also to give them a taste of their own medicine, using a different method to cause internal conflict.

...

The port on the mother planet of the Lore Civilization was already packed with people. Anti-gravity transport vehicles loaded the supplies onto the fleet one by one. Countless frightened citizens lined up to board the ships under the orders of armed soldiers. No matter how anxious they were, they could only suppress their emotions and listen to the orders obediently.

Not long ago, there was a group of people who wanted to rebel, but they were suppressed cruelly, killed on the spot. Their blood had not even dried yet. That was why no one dared to act recklessly right now.

Not long after, the first fleet was finally filled up. Without waiting for the subsequent spaceships, they took to the sky and fled into the depths of space.

Savignes was already in the main ship. As the leader of the civilization, he did not dare stay on the mother planet any longer. The fleets of refugees had split into several batches. In order to escort him, more than half of the armed forces were moving together with the first fleet with the least population load.

"We've finally set off…"

Savignes let out a small sigh of relief.

He still remembered that in the "battle report", the two Dynasty Rulers were tortured to death by the World Tree. It could be seen that the World Tree Civilization liked to carry out the tactic of killing the leader very much. He was worried that he would follow in their footsteps and be "trampled to death". Therefore, he only wanted to run away quickly and did not dare to stay on the mother planet as a target… As far as he knew, the other heads of civilizations had the same idea and had all fled from the mother planet.

As the spaceship slowly accelerated, Savignes was no longer so worried. He muttered to himself,

"It should be safe for now…"

However, before he could finish his sentence, the spaceship's radar suddenly exploded with an ear-piercing hum. It pointed straight at the front of the spaceship, and an energy reaction appeared out of nowhere, blocking the way.

The next moment, a Mechanical Deity suddenly expanded in size, surpassing the size of the entire fleet stacked on each other. It covered the sun and the stars, and a huge hand suddenly came down.

Hong Long Long~

Psionic energy burst out like ripples, and the entire fleet began to explode like firecrackers. In the blink of an eye, the armed escort fleet was almost completely annihilated. They could not even make a splash and turned into a large patch of fireworks in the starry sky. It was very beautiful.

"This is Black Star ‽"

Savignes turned pale with fright and hastily shouted,

"Run, run…"

However, before he could finish speaking, many of the spaceship operators were already sweating profusely.

"This won't do. The fleet's intelligence matrix is completely locked. We can't control it at all. The spaceship is already paralyzed!"

"No…"

Savignes' eyes widened in horror as his pupils reflected the enlarged palm of the Supreme Heavenly Venerate. The mechanical lines on the palm became clearer.

Crack!

Han Xiao directly grabbed the flagship and sucked it into his body, capturing Savignes and the upper echelons of the ship.

Immediately after, he suddenly raised his hand and punched. Energy burst out like a gamma-ray burst, spreading in a large area and instantly vaporizing a large group of warships that were about to counterattack.

"The first."

Han Xiao turned around and disappeared as though he had never been there.

His goal was to capture the leaders of all the civilizations in the Star Alliance and display the advantage of individual strength.

With his current combat strength, the success rate of the targeting the leader tactic was almost 100% against a civilization like the Star Alliance. No one could stop him.

"His Excellency Savignes has been captured by the enemy!"

Because Han Xiao's execution efficiency was too great, the remaining defense troops on the mother planet did not have the time to rush over to support Savignes when he was captured.

The guards on the ground base stared blankly at the place where Han Xiao had disappeared. Listening to the busy tone in the command channel, they fell into a state of chaos.

Chapter 1455: Crushing Dry Weeds and Smashing Rotten Wood

The Star Alliance also had individual strengths, but compared to the three Universal Civilizations, they had too few top-tier combatants and were too weak. With Han Xiao's abilities, he could do whatever he wanted here.

In addition, the entire virtual network of the Star Alliance was under the surveillance of Han Xiao, a Legendary Mechanic. The whereabouts of the upper echelons of the Star Alliance could not be hidden at all. Han Xiao was like an eagle pouncing on a chicken, constantly teleporting and flashing, accurately intercepting the fleets of the upper echelons of the Star Alliance. Not once did he fail. Even the Star Alliance Leader was captured by him.

Within a few days, the leaders of the forty-six civilizations and the upper echelons of the Star Alliance were all captured by Han Xiao.

One civilization after another lost its command from the upper echelons. Some civilizations had a good system and continued to maintain the implementation of the migration plan through the base chain of command. Some civilizations were quite decisive, and there were some who took the position of the upper echelons, but most of them fell into different degrees of chaos.

The intelligence of the World Tree and the three Universal Civilizations was a secret of the upper echelons of the Star Alliance. The citizens and the officers did not know anything about it. They did not know what the World Tree fleet represented, nor did they have the strong fear of the World Tree Civilization like the upper echelons had developed over the years of war reports. Therefore, after the upper echelons of the various civilizations disappeared, many civilizations launched an intense counterattack.

However, due to the collective vacancy of the upper echelons, the internal secrets were leaked out under the influence of a certain force, and it quickly spread throughout the Star Alliance base. Most people understood the source of the disaster and knew how terrifying the World Tree Civilization was, as well as how the World Tree Civilization was currently at war with the three Universal Civilizations.

As for the actions of the upper echelons of the Star Alliance, trying to reap benefits but inviting trouble instead, they were not announced under Han Xiao's control.

Because the World Tree's mechanism was too terrifying, the morale of many civilizations was immediately reduced by half.

What completely destroyed the will of the Star Alliance civilizations was the invasion of another armed force. This time, it was the three Universal Civilizations army that was supposed to fight the World Tree in the news! They had also become the attackers!

The morale of the Star Alliance completely collapsed. Facing the pincer attack of two Universal Civilizations, they no longer had the courage to resist and could only flee in panic.

The entire Star Alliance's battle situation slid into the abyss at lightning speed. All the resistance forces were paralyzed and wiped out by the three Universal Civilizations and the World Tree. Countless spaceships escaped from the Star Alliance's territory, and it was a complete mess. Only a month had passed since the World Tree Civilization and the three Universal Civilizations invaded the Star Alliance.

In reality, if the Star Alliance could unite all their forces, they would at least be at the Universe Grade, and would not be so weak. They could still work together to resist for a period of time. However, the situation was too sudden, and there were too many internal conflicts, so they could not form an effective counterattack… The current situation of the Star Alliance was like the three Universal Civilizations that were attacked by the World Tree in his previous life, and the situation was even worse. They were caught completely off guard.

If the Star Alliance was given some time, they might be able to recover from the chaos after suffering heavy losses and form various scattered civil resistance forces. However, they had no chance now.

All the upper echelons of the Star Alliance civilization that were captured by Han Xiao were not executed, nor were they immediately devoured and transformed by the World Tree. Instead, they were locked in the same cage without any physical torture.

There were only virtual screens floating in the cage, showing the tragic situation of their various civilizations under the attack of the World Tree all day long. All the upper echelons of the Star Alliance could not rest peacefully and were suffering from psychological torture.

Every day, as they watched the World Tree fleet destroy the Star Alliance, they were furious, terrified, and desperate.

After the scene of the three Universal Civilizations attacking the Star Alliance was shown on the screen, all the upper echelons of the Star Alliance were stunned.

They had originally thought that the World Tree was fighting on two fronts, but they did not expect the three Universal Civilizations to attack them too. In an instant, their previous guesses were overturned, and everyone was horrified.

"Why would the three Universal Civilizations invade our territory together with the World Tree Civilization? Aren't they still fighting ‽"

The Star Alliance Leader said with a hoarse voice, unable to hide his shock and confusion.

"Could it be that they've stopped the war and reconciled? No, how is that possible? One should not have stopped until the other died. Isn't the World Tree unable to coexist with any civilization ‽" someone murmured in disbelief.

Savignes' eyes were bloodshot and his voice hoarse, "There's only one possibility. The three Universal Civilizations have been devoured by the World Tree and turned into slaves of the World Tree. They have lost their freedom… In other words, their civilization has been destroyed! Hahaha… wuu wuu…"

As he said that, a twisted expression appeared on his face. It was as if he was laughing and crying at the same time. There was an indescribable sense of viciousness and joy.

Among all the Star Alliance civilizations that were attacked, the Lore Civilization was the most miserable. They were targeted by the World Tree and the three Universal Civilizations. Savignes watched the tragic scenes of his race every day, and his mental state was on the verge of collapse. In his eyes… although he was about to die, at least the three Universal Civilizations were gone. His revenge had succeeded, and he had already dragged his enemies along with him to die, destroying the prosperous world of the three Universal Civilizations.

Hearing this, everyone nodded silently. They all agreed that the three Universal Civilizations had become the World Tree Civilization's vassal.

However, unlike Savignes, the other upper echelons of the Star Alliance did not feel any joy, only fear.

Originally, one World Tree Civilization was enough to destroy the Star Alliance. Now, they had even 'absorbed' the forces of the three Universal Civilizations. It was equivalent to two Universal Civilizations attacking from both sides.

No matter how they thought about it, they felt that there was no chance that the Star Alliance would survive. They had already lost all hope in their hearts. Their expressions were numb, and they were like walking corpses.

Swoosh!

At this time, the cell door opened, and everyone turned around to look. A figure walked in against the light from the corridor outside, revealing an expressionless face. It was Han Xiao.

"Everyone, how have you been?"

Han Xiao said emotionlessly.

"Black Star!"

Everyone subconsciously shrank back with fear on their faces.

Savignes was the only one who did not retreat. Instead, he took a few steps forward with a ferocious smile on his face. He stretched out his hands as though he wanted to grab Han Xiao's shoulders.

Pa!

Before he could even take a few steps, an invisible force sent him flying, and he slammed into the prison wall.

However, Savignes did not seem to feel any pain at all. Instead, he started laughing like a maniac.

"Hahaha—Black Star! Your three Universal Civilizations have also suffered a crushing defeat and become the slaves of the World Tree. We will also become a member of the World Tree. We are equals with you, and we all have the same ending. Don't think that anyone has won! Haha… cough… haha…"

The upper echelons of the Star Alliance looked at the crazy Savignes and remained silent. There was only disappointment on their faces, and they even looked at Han Xiao with sympathy.

Although they were destined to become a member of the World Tree and would not die, they would lose their sense of self. In their eyes, it was no different from death.

Seeing this, Han Xiao knew what they were thinking. He shook his head and laughed.

"Do you think the three Universal Civilizations have become the slaves of the World Tree? A reasonable deduction, an interesting conjecture… Unfortunately, it's a completely wrong conclusion."

Without waiting for the others to react, he raised his palm, and a small World Tree phantom appeared in his palm. It spun around and exuded an astonishing high-level pressure, causing everyone present to feel weak all over. They could not even stand, and collapsed onto the ground one after another.

"Our war has ended, but you guys guessed wrongly. The World Tree was captured by me and has now become my Universal Treasure. In other words… I'm the master of the World Tree Civilization."

As soon as he said that, Savignes' crazy, hoarse laughter stopped, like a screaming chicken that had its throat pinched.

He stared at Han Xiao with his eyes wide open.

"Impossible! I don't believe it! The intelligence said that the World Tree Civilization had the upper hand and almost destroyed your side…"

"Oh? You're talking about the intelligence sent back by the spies you left in the desolate universe belt?"

Han Xiao interrupted him and said with a teasing tone,

"I got someone to make up those battle reports. Isn't that great?"

As soon as he said that, it was as if he had pressed the mute button. Savignes' anger froze on his face, and the others' eyes widened.

The room fell silent.

Han Xiao blinked and slowly said, "Your spies have long been discovered by us and transformed into the servants of the World Tree. We have been sending fake intelligence to you all, making you think that we are still in the midst of war. In fact, we had already dealt with the World Tree more than a year ago. What you all saw was just an illusion we made up."

At this moment, everyone's expression was extremely interesting.

Thinking about how they had been surprised every time they saw the 'battle report' in the past year, everyone felt as if they had eaten a piece of incense.

It turned out that they had been laughing at the fake intelligence that others had fabricated. They had been complacent, proud, and had been toyed with!

At this moment, everyone wished they could tear off their faces and throw them somewhere they could no longer see.

At the same time, an even deeper sense of despair rose in everyone's hearts. Knowing that this was a mixed attack, they had no hope at all. Their faces were extremely gloomy, knowing that the Star Alliance was finished.

Seeing this, Han Xiao shook his head.

In fact, he felt that the Star Alliance was quite unlucky. Even if these people did not take advantage of the situation to give trouble to the three Universal Civilizations, when he defeated the World Tree, he would still use the Information Form Warning Network to cover all the Star Fields in his territory. This way, the Star Alliance would still have nowhere to hide and would be exposed.

At that time, the Star Alliance would still receive the attention and vigilance of the three Universal Civilizations, and their outcome would probably not be any better. Therefore, the moment the Star Alliance sent their spies to gather information about the galactic society, their outcome was almost certain.

The Star Alliance Leader clenched his fists and gritted his teeth. "What are you going to do to us if you don't want to devour us ‽"

Han Xiao glanced at them and said, "I need everyone's cooperation. As you can see, we have the ability to destroy all the civilizations in the Star Alliance, but I will give your race a chance. Stop resisting, choose to submit, and become our subsidiary… Only then will we give you the right to continue surviving."

"You could have swallowed us all, why would you do this!" The Star Alliance Leader was furious.

"I want to." Han Xiao raised his brows, paused, looked at everyone, and continued, "Think about it first. You only have one chance…"

This time, Savignes suddenly roared and interrupted him.

"We will never give up our freedom to become the World Tree's vassal! You will never be able to enslave us…"

However, before he could finish speaking, Han Xiao flicked his finger, and mechanical particles flew out, forming a sealed mechanical device that covered the lower half of Savignes' face, blocking all of his roars.

Han Xiao retracted his gaze and said with a calm expression, "It seems like he has already made his choice. Before the destruction of the Lore Civilization, he will not be executed. He will stand here and watch the outcome of his choice… Everyone, it's your turn. Because I was interrupted just now, I will repeat myself. The three Universal Civilizations won't even need to put in the effort to destroy you all. If you reject me, you all won't even have the chance to reproduce under the jurisdiction of the World Tree. Destruction or continuation, think carefully before you speak."

Everyone's expression was uncertain, and they fell into a dilemma.

They knew that this was a warning, but it was still very effective. They really wanted to say that they would never become slaves out of spite, but looking at the tragic state of their race on the virtual screen, they only felt the heavy burden on their shoulders become heavier, so heavy that they could not even speak.

At this time, mechanical particles flowed out from under Han Xiao's robe and turned into a fixed cabin, locking Savignes up.

"There's no need to hurry. You have plenty of time. Before our fleet destroys your civilization, you can hesitate as much as you want. After all, you're not the ones who are dying."

Han Xiao then turned around and left.

The cell door closed behind him, cutting off the sound of Savignes struggling.

Han Xiao did not stop, and the officers of the three Universal Civilizations were already waiting at the door. Seeing this, they quickly followed.

"Your Excellency Black Star, thank you." Teny nodded.

"It's nothing. I'll leave the rest to you."

Han Xiao waved his hands.

He had already helped them to this extent, and the Star Alliance had already lost the ability to resist. The three Universal Civilizations would be more than enough to take care of the rest of the work. With the World Tree Civilization cooperating, he did not need to do anything anymore.

The three Universal Civilizations still had the ability to handle such a simple concluding job.

I didn't expect things to go so smoothly… A civilization that has stepped into the threshold of the Universe Grade was easily destroyed in such a short period of time. My force has already expanded to this level.

Han Xiao sighed in his heart before walking away.

Chapter 1456: Logging Out and Returning

After settling the upper echelons of the Star Alliance, Han Xiao had nothing to do and could focus on his own work. The three Universal Civilizations and the World Tree Civilization were both in charge of cleaning up the Star Alliance.

Because the resistance of the Star Alliance had collapsed, it was a piece of cake for the three Universal Civilizations to clean up the migrating troops within the Star Alliance.

Originally, the rare war mission was a large-scale event that the players were passionate about, but this time, the three Universal Civilizations did not issue a large-scale gathering order. Only a few players were summoned to deal with the Star Alliance, and most of the players were focused on their own Pro League.

After a long period of preparation, the qualifiers had already begun, and it was already at its climax. Therefore, most of the players were not interested in the Star Alliance war at the moment. They only wanted to hurt each other and participate in the upcoming Pro League.

As Han Xiao had been farming the Sanctum authority for the truth of the universe and Iterations, he did not pay much attention to the players' Pro League. He took some time to check it out, and he realized that the biggest special feature of this Pro League was a significant increase in the level of combat. The mainstream competitive level had gone from Grade B to Calamity Grade, and the destructive power had increased tremendously.

It was now Version 5.5. Compared to Version 4.0, the level cap had increased from level 150 to level 200. The series of missions in the World Tree War had made the players extremely rich. Although they had watched CGs during the final battle, the results of the battle had brought them a shocking profit.

In the fourth Pro League, the mainstream players were basically Grade Bs. Although they were considered the backbone of the universe, they were still considered weak in the eyes of the top combatants. However, in the fifth Pro League, the gap between the players had grown even wider. Now, the main players of the Pro League had to be at the Calamity Grade.

In the Supers Holy Land, on an uninhabited planet. Qualifiers round, Arena 24.

The battleships of the guilds floated in the air and watched the battle on the ground. They saw two 'yellow dragons' that were covered in dust colliding with each other, creating shockwaves from time to time, creating spiderweb-like cracks on the ground.

Two players in heavy armor were moving rapidly on the surface of the planet, fighting each other continuously. They were like walking natural disasters, but their IDs were unfamiliar. They were not professional players from any guild but ordinary players.

These were just two unknown players, but their destructive power was already very outstanding. The players in the sky could not take their eyes off them.

As the players stepped into the Calamity Grade batch by batch, their strength increased collectively, and many of them experienced a qualitative change. In order to ensure the viewership ratings and prevent some professional players from the large guilds from really failing in the qualifiers, many large guilds obtained direct access cards to the official league, so they did not need to take risks in the qualifiers. Although this decreased the excitement of the qualifiers, because there were many dark horses, the players were still very excited.

'The overall destructive power of the players is getting stronger…'

Outside the atmosphere, Han Xiao's virtual projection looked down at the planet and took in the scene of the players fighting.

He was in stealth mode, and the other players could not see his projection. They were still looking down at the competition, not looking up at the sky.

"Let the players grow a few more versions, and the level cap will be unlocked more and more. They will definitely become the new source of chaos."

Han Xiao pondered.

Now that the galactic society had formed a new stable structure, it would be peaceful for a long time. It was good for the galactic residents but bad for the players.

After experiencing several versions of events, the players had already eaten big fish and meat, and they had seen big scenes. If they were asked to go back and do the daily side missions, it would definitely be unbearable. If there were no new disasters or big events, the players who were unwilling to remain out of the limelight would definitely become 'big events'. As their strength increased, they would definitely become more restless, and they would not be satisfied with a leisurely life, which would lead to chaos.

All kinds of thoughts flashed through Han Xiao's mind. He took a deep look at the players' spaceships, turned around, and disappeared.

On the other side, in the cabins of the players' spaceships, countless people were staring at the feedback of the competition on the ground on the satellite screen.

The officers of the guilds and clubs were also paying attention to the situation of the qualifiers, noting down the dark horses and discussing softly.

"This year's competition is really amazing. There are too many strong players."

"I don't think it's good. I've already seen more than thirty top-notch non-professional players. If our team's players are really defeated by the normal players, we'll lose a lot of face."

"I really hope that the next version is released as soon as possible. The guild's plans can also be implemented then."

Many guild officers were secretly excited.

As the level cap was unlocked further, the Calamity Grade players of the various guilds experienced a huge increase in size, and the operational capability of the guild organizations also increased.

Currently, many guilds had a large number of Calamity Grade players on their hands, and their strength was enough to dominate a region in the galactic society. In order to maintain the gap between their own pro players and ordinary players, many professional guilds privately created detailed plans for the guild's operations for the next version, deciding to expand in the universe in the next version.

Although they were watching the Pro League, the thoughts of many guild officers had already drifted away. They could not wait to go all out in the next version.

...

Han Xiao did not have the time to pay attention to the pro league of the players. To him, this was just a distraction. He buried his head in the machinery factory and almost left all his chores behind. He checked over and over again the feasibility of the World Tree's Information Form Materialization function breaking through the dark side universe.

As the days flew by, the three Universal Civilizations' invasion of Star Alliance also gradually came to an end. They had long received the battle reports that Han Xiao had fabricated from the upper echelons of the Star Alliance, and they were speechless at Han Xiao's bad taste. This guy was f*cking irregular.

However, the leaders of the three Universal Civilizations would not disturb Han Xiao, who was studying how to break the seal on the dark side universe, over such a small matter. They could only pretend that nothing had happened and silently order their people to destroy this 'dark history'.

In the blink of an eye, more than a year had passed. The three Universal Civilizations had more or less completed dismantling and clearing the Star Alliance, digesting most of the spoils of war, and destroyed this enemy that was lurking behind them.

The fifth Pro League also came to an end during this period. This time, Dynasty Club finally returned to first place and won the championship of the fifth Pro League. Second Prince inherited King Admiral's position and led the team to win the championship, instantly raising his historical status by a level. He was praised by the club as the 'cornerstone of the next dynasty'.

Dynasty was the only team that had won the championship twice in the past five Pro Leagues. Their popularity, which had originally fallen slightly, soared like a rocket.

The former Dynasty champion captain King Admiral, who was the team's coach, publicly congratulated Second Prince, expressing his relief. Bun-Hit-Dog called it 'King's Baton Pass', which was accepted by the players and spread on the forums.

This time, the first and second runner-ups were America's Devil team and Russia's White Vodka team. Although the Chinese team was not as dominant as before and could not occupy two places in the top three, their performance was still not bad. They had achieved outstanding results in the individual and group competitions.

As the Pro League came to an end, Version 5.5 also came to an end.

In the guild bases of the players on the various planets of the Supers Holy Land, groups of players were gathered, waiting to go offline. They chatted casually, and it was as noisy as a market.

"It's finally going to be updated again. I wonder how many years it will be this time."

"It should be the main version update now. We should be able to unlock at least 20 levels!"

"I wonder what will happen in the next version. Since even the World Tree has been dealt with, I don't think anything will be able to shake the current situation of the galactic society."

"Didn't you see the Galaxy Times' deduction? There's a high chance that internal conflicts will intensify, and Black Star might turn black and become a new boss, fighting against the three Universal Civilizations."

"Yo, does this mean that we can finally start a massacre? I'm going to turn the world upside down!"

"It would feel so refreshing. I've been unhappy with those three old b*stards for a long time. When the time comes, I'll chop them up to vent my anger."

"You guys are so disappointing! Compared to this, shouldn't we be more concerned about whether we can repair the BUG that we can't get naked in the next version?"

"Yes, yes, yes! If I can't run around naked in the next version, I'll definitely complain!"

Hearing the players around her yelling, Maple Moon had a look of disgust on her face. She felt that these people were hopeless.

As they chatted, time slowly passed. When they went offline, a large white light flashed, and batches of players disappeared one after another. The hall became empty.

At the same time, in the private research room of the Supers Holy Land, Han Xiao, who was studying, paused and looked up.

"Hmm, has the version update started again?"

Han Xiao stopped what he was doing and opened the interface to take a look. The forums were closed once again. This meant that the time flow between the dark side universe and the true universe was disconnected once again, turning into two independent systems. He was the only stable information interference bridge left.

During this period of time, he had repeatedly studied the feasibility of the conversion plan, and he was now more than seventy percent confident. Although he had made some technical contributions, most of it was thanks to the tests and improvements of the previous dark side Iterations.

Han Xiao shook his head and closed the interface. Just as he was about to enter the research again, Phillip suddenly appeared.

"Master, hum, Her Excellency Ames is in your office. She wants to see you, hum."

"Oh, I got it. I'll be right there."

Han Xiao rubbed the space between his brows. He had no choice but to put down his research and head to his office.

The moment he entered, he saw Ames sitting in his seat with her back facing the door.

Hearing the noise, Ames turned her chair around, and her long legs extended out from under her black dress. She sat down and looked at Han Xiao with a smile that was not a smile. "Busy man, it's not easy to see you."

"I've been very busy recently. You know that." Han Xiao walked around the table and came to the back of the chair. He placed his hands on both sides of Ames' forehead and gently massaged it.

Ames closed her eyes comfortably, but her mouth did not stop. She chuckled and said, "That's right, there's no time when you're not busy. If I didn't come to find you occasionally, I would have suspected that you had forgotten about me."

"What are you saying? You're just spouting nonsense. You deserve to be punished." Han Xiao curled his lips, and a faint electric current appeared on his finger, causing Ames' eyelashes to tremble.

Ames avoided Han Xiao's finger and slapped his hand away. She then stood up and said seriously,

"I don't understand. The World Tree has been dealt with, and the three Universal Civilizations have given in. We don't have any safety concerns now, so why are you still so busy? Where did you get the pressure ‽"

"…This is a secret that I can't tell you yet. In any case, it's very tricky." Han Xiao shook his head. It would be useless to tell the Beyond Grade As about the secrets of the Iterations, so he did not tell anyone other than the heads of the three Universal Civilizations.

"Do you still remember what I said back then? Ambition is never-ending. When are you willing to stop? Do you really want to replace the three Universal Civilizations?" Ames frowned. "What is it that you have to hide so closely? Can't you just say it out loud and let everyone bear the consequences?"

"You can't help…"

Han Xiao hesitated for a moment before touching Ames' cheek.

"This should be the last time. I will keep us all alive."

Hearing this, Ames' eyes changed. Although she did not know what Han Xiao was hiding, she could hear the seriousness in Han Xiao's tone. A situation which even a Transcendent found difficult to deal with, had to be some kind of problem that she could not imagine.

Just as Ames was about to ask, the communicator in the room suddenly beeped.

It was a message from Marbruce. There was only one content…

The Sanctum exploration team was finally back!

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

"I have something to do, so I'll leave first. I'll accompany you next time."

Han Xiao quickly changed into King.

Ames opened her mouth, wanting to say something, but the next moment, Han Xiao activated teleportation and disappeared from the room.

Looking at the empty room, Ames clenched and unclenched her fists. She repeated this a few times before taking a deep breath and suppressing the complicated emotions in her heart.

The subordinate that once needed her protection was now an existence that she could only look up to. She was increasingly feeling that it was harder for her to keep up with Han Xiao.

Although Ames had a cold personality and rarely bothered herself with such matters, she would still feel a sense of loss after so many years. Even though Han Xiao's attitude toward her remained the same, Ames knew that she could no longer share Han Xiao's worries.

Chapter 1457: Plan

In a certain military-restricted area in the Central Galaxy, the location of the Sanctum channel that had once been summoned had already been tightly sealed. There were densely packed space armed fortresses and large fleet troops scattered all around, and the security was tight.

Suddenly, a beam of light lit up in the darkness and slowly expanded, turning into three Sanctum channels that led to the white world. They floated quietly in space like three miniature white holes.

In the dazzling light door, three black shadows gradually grew larger and larger. They were the spaceships that the three Universal Civilizations had sent to explore the Sanctum.

A group of soldiers immediately flew out from the military base and led the three spaceships back to the fortress. The members of the ship walked out under the support of their comrades. Most of them looked dazed, as though they were out of their mind. Their eyes were dull and their reactions slow.

Only Clotti, Oulou, and the Beyond Grade A from the Arcane Church seemed to be in a better state. However, their faces were still filled with shock, and their legs were trembling.

Right at this moment, a faint light flashed, and the remote projection of the three Universal Civilizations' Rulers appeared. They immediately surrounded the group with a nervous expression.

"How's the situation? Did you guys get the information from the Sanctum?"

Clotti's eyes were focused, and he was stunned for a few seconds before he seemed to come back to his senses. He nodded with a serious expression.

"The scene in the Sanctum is exactly the same as what Black Star said. We have already seen the records on the Sanctum's message board. The truth about the Alterations of the Universe is indeed on it. In addition, we also obtained some information about the Alterations of the past from the Sanctum. Although it's not much, it's still a piece of evidence."

Hearing this, the heads of the three Universal Civilizations took a deep breath. Although they knew that Han Xiao was not lying, they were still shocked.

At this moment, Louis suddenly lowered his voice and said, "Has the Sanctum Revival experiment succeeded?"

"It's true." Clotti raised his palm and showed the Sanctum Revival mark on the back of his hand. It was exactly the same as in the records.

The three of them finally relaxed and nodded silently.

In order to prove the authenticity of the Sanctum and prevent themselves from being tricked by Black Star again, the three Universal Civilizations took out a few mediums of their late direct descendants and gave them to Clotti and the others to test if the Sanctum Revival was feasible. If it failed, it would mean that the Sanctum that they had entered was full of tricks. It could be that Black Star had deliberately built this alternate dimension to trick them. If they succeeded, they would be able to prove that it was the real Sanctum.

Back then, when he asked Black Star to help revive the direct Beyond Grade As, the three Universal Civilizations' Ruler had said that he had taken out all the mediums of the late direct descendants, but he had actually hidden a small portion of the late direct descendants, claiming that he did not have these mediums, so as to guard against Black Star and prevent any accidents. Even when Black Star proved that the Sanctum Revival was reliable, the three Universal Civilizations did not reveal this. They planned to use it as test material when they researched the Sanctum in the future, and it was now useful.

Ta ta ta…

At this time, the sound of footsteps could be heard from afar. Han Xiao, who had teleported over, walked over in large strides. Before anyone could say anything, he grabbed Clotti's hand and raised it in front of his eyes.

"What are you doing?" Clotti was shocked. He subconsciously wanted to break free, but he realized that he could not move Han Xiao's fingers at all.

The heads of the three Universal Civilizations thought that Han Xiao was concerned about the Sanctum Revival Mark, and their hearts tightened. They were worried that Black Star would hold a grudge against them for trying the Sanctum Revival in private.

However, they were wrong. Now that things had come to this, Han Xiao would not pay attention to these details. He revealed his Sanctum authority mark, and Clotti's palm immediately produced feedback, showing his own Sanctum authority mark as well.

One of the symbols was complicated and exquisite, while the other was simple and plain. This was the difference between a max-level authority and a level-one authority.

Seeing this, Han Xiao then let go of Clotti and said,

"How is it? How does it feel to enter and exit the Sanctum? Does it feel like you were hallucinating?"

Clotti rubbed his painful wrist and hesitated for a moment before saying, "Indeed, I feel like I'm sleepwalking. Although I can still control my body, my senses seem to be separated by a layer. It's not like I can move freely under normal circumstances. It's more like I'm controlling my body through a third-person perspective. My brain and body are no longer one…"

"This was your first time in there, so it's normal for you to feel this way… although I've never experienced the feeling of having a low authority." Han Xiao patted his shoulder. "Your authority is too low, and you spent a lot of time. We've been waiting for you in the main universe for a long time."

Clotti and the others looked at the time and were shocked. It had been a year or two since they left. They had only stayed in the Sanctum for a few hours.

"Just get used to it. When your authority gets higher, the flow of time in the Sanctum will slowly converge with the main universe."

Han Xiao casually explained before turning to look at the heads of the three Universal Civilizations.

"How is it? Did you guys get the information you wanted? Do you believe me now?"

Marbruce nodded. "We've confirmed the truth about the Universe Iterations. It's exactly as you said."

At this time, the Pope said, "It's just that our authority is too low, so we can't see all the information on the Sanctum's message board. Therefore, we still can't investigate the secrets of the Final Three Universal Civilizations and the Dark Side Universe that you mentioned…"

Hearing this, Han Xiao opened his eyes wide and found it funny.

"Why? Don't tell me you want me to help you access the Sanctum until you unlock all the messages on the boards?"

"If you don't mind, we would be honored…"

"Get lost."

"Ahem, we can understand why you're not willing…"

The three of them looked embarrassed.

"It's true that I can help you complete the great deeds that you have done for many generations, but don't push your luck." Han Xiao crossed his arms and said with a frown, "I have already done enough for the galactic society. I have already given you enough sincerity, but you guys are still skeptical of me. It was like this when we dealt with the World Tree, and it is still the same now. To be honest, if you guys still doubt me, we can just dissolve this partnership."

"Don't, don't, don't. We just need to think about it because of the big picture. We don't suspect you… Let's go to the office and have a chat."

The three of them quickly surrounded Han Xiao and explained, leading him to the private conference room.

After closing the door and confirming that there were no outsiders, Marbruce coughed and said,

"Black Star, we believe in the intelligence of the Dark Side Universe. Now that we've verified that the Sanctum's intelligence is not fake, let's talk about the topic we didn't finish last time. How do you plan to break the seal of the Dark Side Universe and let us return to the real universe?"

"Two ways." Han Xiao raised two fingers.

"What are they?" The three of them perked up and listened carefully.

Han Xiao paused to gather these thoughts before explaining slowly.

"The first is to follow the route of the three Universal Civilizations in the first two dark sides and use the Information Form Materialization device normally. Although the World Tree has mutated and changed its nature, it still has the core function of being an Information Form Materialization device. I've already dug it out."

"What about the second one?"

"Secondly, I still have to use the Information Form Materialization device, but it has to be combined with my Virtual Creation ability."

The three of them looked at each other in confusion.

Marbruce said with a puzzled tone, "Aren't both of them using Information Form Materialization devices? What's the difference?"

"The difference is in my position. In the first plan, the success rate depends entirely on whether the information interference bridge has met the prerequisite requirement for conversion, which means that this predetermined route may still fail. As for the second plan, I can use my own abilities. The principle is… well, let's not talk about the principle. Anyway, none of you can understand it. In any case, I feel that it can increase the success rate of conversion… The only concern is that the two previous dark side iterations have never tried my new method before, so there might be some uncertain factors."

Han Xiao shook his head.

The first plan was to use him as a tool, a 'medium' to activate the Information Form Materialization device. In the second plan, he was the executor of the device… The difference between the two was the leader.

After fusing with the World Tree, Han Xiao studied it carefully and finally allowed his [Virtual Creation] skill to transform. After removing the 'Pseudo' part, the effect of the skill had changed drastically. It had the same function as the core ability found in the Information Form Materialization device and could resonate with each other.

The three of them hesitated and discussed softly. Han Xiao did not rush them.

After a few minutes, Marbruce looked up and asked, "What is the estimated success rate of these two plans?"

Han Xiao shrugged. "The first plan has a fifty percent success rate, and the second plan has a seventy percent success rate, but the risk is unknown."

Louis pondered and said, "Why don't we try the first plan? If it doesn't work, we can try the second one."

"Hmm, it can be done, but the stable interference bridge might be damaged in the case of a failure. At that time, even if you want to regret it, you won't have the chance to do so. Therefore, I personally suggest that it's best to do it in one go." Han Xiao shrugged.

"…We need to think about it."

"Alright, you have plenty of time, but the preparations for the two proposals are more or less the same. During this time, mobilize the galactic society and get ready."

"Okay."

The three of them nodded and disconnected from the remote projection. They could not wait to go back and discuss it.

Han Xiao was the only one left in the conference room. He looked at where the three of them disappeared and curled his lips.

In fact, he had hidden a third plan, which was to use the World Tree to swallow the entire universe and "compress" it in his body, forming a complete and independent "information assembly". This way, it would reduce the difficulty of the actualization of information. In his opinion, the success rate of this plan could exceed eighty percent.

However, even if he used his chest muscles to think, he knew that the three Universal Civilizations would definitely not agree to this plan. They might even start to doubt his motives for helping.

In addition, this process was truly too long. Who knew how long it would take for the World Tree to devour the entire dark side universe? Just the journey alone would take countless years, and he did not really want to utilize this plan.

Therefore, Han Xiao decided not to say anything and kept it to himself.

"I hope the three Universal Civilizations choose the second plan… Hmm, but even if they don't choose the second plan, I'll still do it."

Han Xiao clicked his tongue.

Letting the three Universal Civilizations choose was mainly to give them a feeling of 'participation'… When the galactic society was ready to officially begin the transformation, it would still be up to him.

Chapter 1458: Information Form Anchor (1)

Han Xiao teleported back to the office in the Supers Holy Land's main planet. The meeting with the three Universal Civilizations went much faster than expected, but Ames did not wait. She had already left, and the room was empty.

"Where did she go?"

"Her Excellency Ames has gone to look for Aurora. Should I inform her to come over?"

"There's no need. I'll look for her later."

Han Xiao casually expressed his concern and did not ask further. His expression was not as relaxed as when he was talking to the three Universal Civilizations' rulers, but rather, he had a lot on his mind.

He told the leaders of the three Universal Civilizations that he was worried that the stable interference bridge would be damaged during the conversion. This was not a lie, but a real concern.

After this period of testing, he realized that as a medium for conversion, when he officially activated the Information Form Materialization device, he would suffer a large amount of information impact and temporarily form a connection with the universe consciousness. During the process of reverse conversion to the True State, the interface, as a specialty of the dark side universe, would gradually lose its effect, so the Character Summon Cards could not be used continuously during the conversion process.

If he wanted to maintain his consciousness and maintain the effect of [Virtual Creation—True], he would need to strengthen his Information Form base and add some 'Information Form Anchors' to prevent himself from being unable to hold on and cause the information interference channel to break.

He did not disclose these details, and no one else could help him. It would only add to his troubles.

"The so-called Information Form Anchor should be my understanding of myself, my connection with the World Tree, and my past memories…"

Han Xiao pondered.

This was a rather mysterious perception. If one did not reach the Transcendent Grade, they would not be able to have such an intuition—tracing back to the past and commemorating the past might be the way to deepen the Information Form Anchor.

"The three Universal Civilizations are about to start preparing. I have to start preparing too…"

Han Xiao then changed into another King and disappeared from the room.

Shattered Star Ring, Planet Aquamarine.

The planet that had been abandoned for more than ten years was rebuilt after the people of Planet Aquamarine relocated. The old buildings covered by nature were demolished and rebuilt. The entire planet looked completely new.

There was only one place that had not been renovated. The large ruins were already covered in wild green vegetation, and the large number of building wreckage stuck in the ground had already rusted. These were the ruins of the Germinal Organization. It laid quietly on the wasteland, as silent as ever. Only the traces left behind by time seemed to be telling the past.

Three people were strolling around the ruins, stopping from time to time to observe.

"…Back then, your godfather and I fought side by side and destroyed the Germinal Organization. He infiltrated this place alone and stole countless key secrets. He even saved Hila and Aurora, who were still young at that time. He fought for thousands of miles before giving the information to us. In the end, the war was decided in one fell swoop, and the Six Nations no longer had anything to worry about. The Germinal Organization was destroyed with a nuclear explosion. It was also on that day that Planet Aquamarine was reborn."

Bennett caressed the remains of a huge metal plate. He wiped off the rust on it with his palm, revealing a blurry Germinal Organization insignia. A complicated look appeared in his eyes, as though he was reminiscing about the war years ago.

Nero, who was standing behind him, took a few steps forward and placed his hand on the metal wreckage as well. "I've seen these things in my textbooks, but every time I come to the Germinal Organization ruins, I always feel as though I'm there, as though I've experienced a battle that changed the fate of this planet."

Bennett turned to look at him, shook his head, and laughed. He then took back his hand and sighed. "Thinking about it carefully, Black Star's appearance when he was young is like a completely different person compared to the current him. Sigh, when one is old, one loves to reminisce about the past."

"You're not old yet," Mia, who was holding a baby, said with a smile.

Bennett laughed out loud and walked to Mia. He bent down and looked at the baby in Mia's arms. At this moment, he was staring at him with his eyes wide open. He chuckled and extended his short arms.

"Yo, my good grandson, let grandpa carry you."

Bennett's face was filled with kindness, and his arm, which could easily crush steel, carefully took over his grandson. He held his grandson in his arms and shook him gently.

Nero also came over with a face full of envy.

Although he was the child's father, the moment he hugged his son, the child would cry nonstop. Instead, his son would only be able to sleep peacefully in his grandfather Bennett's arms.

After the war ended, Nero and Mia had a baby, which made Bennett feel very happy.

Considering that Nero had become the acting Army Commander and that Planet Aquamarine was on the right track, Bennett decided to give up his position as the leader of the Aquamarine Federation after much consideration. Originally, many of the upper echelons did not agree and wished for Bennett to be re-elected. However, he had already made up his mind and was determined to give up his position. He was no longer in charge of any duties and had retired to enjoy the happiness of a family.

Bennett played with the baby for a while before asking Nero, "Have you tested his Super-Gene?"

"I did. The report said that his Super-Gene is extremely active and rare. He might be an extremely talented Esper in the future." Nero was overjoyed.

"Is that so? That's not too bad." Bennett nodded and stroked the baby's sparse hair.

The three of them played with the baby and walked away slowly.

Suddenly, the space around the area fluctuated slightly, and Han Xiao's figure walked out. He stood still and watched as the three left.

"How beautiful…"

Han Xiao muttered to himself and turned to look at the Germinal Organization ruins.

His path was already very far, but when he looked back, his past on this planet seemed to be right before his eyes, just yesterday.

Old memories flooded in like a tidal wave, and in a daze, images flashed past his eyes. He had transmigrated to the Germinal Organization base, spent half a year in darkness, escaped with great difficulty, drove an off-road vehicle under the moonlight, left Stardragon and transformed into Black Phantom, walked alone in the Wasteland, infiltrated the Germinal Organization to steal intelligence, and was chased for thousands of miles. The headquarters of the Germinal Organization had been reduced to ashes in the dazzling nuclear explosion…

Similarly, human figures flashed in his eyes. The young Hila who was determined to enter the Abyss but was eventually dragged back by him, the young Aurora who was still optimistic about being saved by him despite being tortured, Bennett who worked hard to end the battle, the Germinal Organization leader who did not regret even after reaching the end of the road…

The tragedy of the Mutation Disaster that followed also appeared before his eyes. The chaotic world, the crazy crowd, the endless beast tide, the spaceships that fell from the sky, the blazing cannons… everything came from DarkStar.

"Two full versions of disasters. This place is really full of trouble and misfortune…"

Han Xiao closed his eyes. The storyline of Version 1.0 and Version 2.0 flashed through his mind.

After a long time, he opened his eyes. He felt that his mind was calm, and there seemed to be some subtle changes in his body.

Somehow, the foundation of his Information Form seemed to have become thicker. It seemed like he had already set the first Information Form Anchor and connected it to Planet Aquamarine.

"Planet Aquamarine…"

Han Xiao slowly rose into the air. He looked down at the ruins of the Germinal Organization, then at the bustling city at the end of the horizon. He turned around and disappeared.

Chapter 1459: Information Form Anchor (2)

The dark and deep universe seemed to be decorated with a curtain of diamonds. A silvery-white planet was rotating quietly. The surface of the planet was made of metal, and there were mechanical towers with sharp edges. They were connected to each other in the air, forming matrix-like patterns. The neat layout had an exquisite mechanical aesthetic.

This was the new main planet of Han Xiao's machinery civilization. It was located in the Supers Holy Land and was completely created by the Mechanical Lives. The size of the planet was extremely large, and it was integrated with the matter of several planets. The former Planet Apostle was also broken down and integrated into this planet.

Originally, Psionic Prime and the other Mechanical Oracles wanted to name this new main planet 'Black Star Planet' as a sign of respect for the Lord God Black Star, but they were firmly rejected by Han Xiao. In the end, Psionic Prime and the other Oracles changed their minds and named this planet 'Holy Planet'.

On the bustling alloy path, mechanical lives of all shapes and sizes were bustling about. Some mechanical life's feet clashed with the ground as they walked, and some mechanical life's tires rubbed against the ground as they drove. Some mechanical life's engine tanks were constantly rumbling, and some mechanical life's exhaust pipes would spurt out gas from time to time, forming a strange tune with a strong mechanical feeling.

Han Xiao walked among the mechanical army. His entire body was covered in camouflage, and he looked like an ordinary mechanical life form. All the nearby mechanical lives could not detect his presence.

"This place is becoming more and more prosperous…"

Han Xiao was glad.

After taking in the World Tree, he no longer needed the machinery civilization to produce mechanical soldiers all day. Thus, he stopped the basic command of troop production and allowed the machinery civilization to develop on its own. This was the first time he had carefully observed the changes of the machinery civilization after the war.

Han Xiao's walking speed was slow, as though he was taking a stroll. His eyes kept looking left and right, sizing up the machines on the street.

Although the Mechanical Lives were produced in batches, and many of them had the same model, there were almost no identical Mechanical Lives on the streets. Even if they were Mechanical Lives of the same model, they added all kinds of personalized structures to themselves through self-modification. Some liked guns, some liked sharp blades, some liked heavy equipment, and some liked to run around naked… From the perspective of a normal life, it would be like the difference in clothes, hairstyle, makeup, and accessories.

In the shops along the street, Han Xiao also saw all kinds of products. Most of them were modification shops and parts malls. There were all kinds of mechanical parts and even different colored paints. The customer flow was huge, and there were mechanical lives coming in and out every second, 'trying on clothes'.

Other than that, he also saw the specialty snack shop. The chef robot inside was cooking oil, lubricant maintenance gel, energy blocks, and other items. It placed them in a large pot to stir and cook, making all kinds of strange foods. Han Xiao took one and tried it. It tasted so bad that it almost broke his defenses.

However, the other Mechanical Lives that came to purchase left in satisfaction and enjoyed their meal. In their eyes, it was a rare delicacy. There were also a few pairs of couple-like Mechanical Lives feeding each other.

Han Xiao also saw the sensory stimulation shop. To mechanical lives, it was like an entertainment venue. Inside, it was connected to all kinds of senses and emotions, directly stimulating the artificial intelligence core. At the cost of a large sum, the mechanical lives could even directly upgrade their own emotion module through the shop's main system.

In a small alley at the side, Han Xiao saw a few small robots surrounding the alloy wall and doodling. Seeing that someone was coming, they quickly dispersed and flew away on electromagnetic wheels, like a bunch of rebellious street kids. The doodling on the wall was extremely wild, filled with a large amount of twisted bright colors. One could vaguely see that it was a portrait of the Supreme Heavenly Venerate.

In the originally cold and strict mechanical group, there was a strong personalization. A free culture was popular, and Han Xiao could see worldly customs from a group of mechanical bodies.

'The life of a Mechanical Life is quite similar…'

Han Xiao smiled.

All along, he had mainly treated the machinery civilization as a weapon factory and did not pay much attention to the changes in the life of the machinery civilization. It was only when he allowed the machinery civilization to reproduce freely that he finally saw the cultural trend.

As the Creator, he could guide the culture of the machinery civilization, but he did not do so. Instead, he allowed it to take shape naturally.

Only now did he feel that the machinery civilization was a little 'civilized'.

As he walked, Han Xiao realized that he had arrived at a huge mechanical square. There were two statues standing in the middle of the square, both of which were him. One was his normal self, and the other was his body in the Supreme Heavenly Venerate mechanical body.

The mechanical lives in the square were endless, and no one paid any attention to the statues. At most, they would stop and look at them for a second before walking away to continue their own lives. Their respect for Han Xiao was no longer as rigid as before but rather placed in their 'hearts'.

Han Xiao came to the foot of the statue and looked up. Suddenly, he saw a tall mechanical life carrying a small mechanical body that looked similar.

He turned around and saw that it seemed to be a harmonious father and son pair. The father let the child ride on his neck and kept teasing him.

Han Xiao silently watched this scene. Images of the machinery civilization following him for the past few decades appeared in his mind. Countless mechanical lives were sent to the battlefield under his orders and used as cannon fodder. Countless unique sparks of consciousness were born in the AI chip circuit, disappearing into the cold universe together with the broken body.

Although he treated the Mechanical Lives as tools, due to the restrictions of the basic logic, they did not have any complaints. They buried their hobbies and interests and fought for him with their lives, still respecting him as the Creator.

"I don't need you guys to fight for me anymore. Enjoy your new life…"

Han Xiao shook his head. He would not cancel the base logic of the Mechanical Civilization's reverence for him, but he did not plan to order the Mechanical Civilization to fight either. He had already mastered the World Tree and [Virtual Creation—True], so he no longer needed these mechanical lives to work for him.

He took one last look at his statues, and memories flowed in his mind. He felt another Information Form Anchor being set up, and only then did he turn around and disappear into the bustling crowd.

In the new headquarters of the Black Star Army in Supers Holy Land.

Han Xiao strolled around the base and hid himself. No one noticed his presence.

The huge base was very lively. Countless members of the Black Star Army were working there. People came and went, and from time to time, there would be people talking and laughing as they walked past Han Xiao.

He strolled around slowly and arrived at the area where the upper echelons were working. He saw Herlous, who was working on the desk, Sylvia, who was still trying to break through to Beyond Grade A, Aroshia, who was staring at the starry sky outside the window, Lagi, who was slacking, and Reynold, who had been maintaining the logistics department for decades…

Looking at the current state of the Black Star Army, Han Xiao was a little dazed. The difficult memories from when he first started his force surfaced in his mind.

He remembered that he had just entered the galaxy back then, and he was still a 'country bumpkin' who had come from a surface civilization. He was completely broke, and the only thing he could rely on was the cannon in his hand.

These old comrades had followed him to build the army's current foundation and grew to where it was today with a third-rate mercenary group.

Everything seemed to have happened yesterday, and his memories were still fresh. The scenes of Herlous, Aroshia, Sylvia, and the others becoming mercenaries with him appeared in his mind. At that time, everyone was very young and fought with their lives on the line. Now, almost a hundred years had passed, and everyone had become important figures in the galaxy. They no longer needed to do things by themselves, and they had already achieved success. They now had a different life.

Thinking back, Han Xiao could not help but sigh at the passing of time. Everyone, including himself, had more or less changed. Perhaps they all missed their old selves even more… At the start, they were always the freshest, and in the future, they would always look at each other with disgust. As their careers progressed, their viewpoints changed, giving them the feeling of 'if time could stop at the moment when we first started'.

However, even though he was emotional, he still preferred the spiraling trend of things, allowing the path ahead to continue expanding and welcoming all kinds of changes.

Memories of the rise and expansion of the Black Star Army flashed through Han Xiao's mind. Suddenly, he felt another Information Form Anchor being generated. He nodded and disappeared.

At the same time, Herlous, Sylvia, Lagi, and the others, who were doing their own things, suddenly had a thought. For some reason, Han Xiao's figure suddenly appeared in their minds, and they could not get rid of it. They subconsciously thought of the dusty memories when they first fought with Han Xiao, and they stopped what they were doing and remained silent.

"What's wrong with me… Why do I suddenly miss Black Star so much?"

Chapter 1460: Information Form Anchor (3)

Holy Accord's headquarters.

Han Xiao teleported over. Under everyone's surprised gazes, he passed through the complicated corridor and arrived at the confinement room of Destiny's Child.

Destiny's Child, who was soaking in the solution, woke up. He leaned closer and placed his hand on the inner wall of the container. Han Xiao smiled and placed his palm on the container.

This time, an experimenter walked over and asked curiously, "Your Excellency Black Star, what are your orders this time?"

"Release Destiny's Child." Han Xiao pursed his mouth.

The experimenter was stunned and said with uncertainty, "Are you kidding? If we let it go, it will be very difficult to catch it again…"

"Let it go." Han Xiao shook his head.

"Er… although you're also the leader of the Holy Accord, it's best if His Excellency Beiger gives the order personally…"

"It's alright. I've already told him."

Han Xiao showed Beiger's message and patted the researcher's shoulder.

"…I understand."

The experimenter did not understand, but he still did as he was told. He terminated the operation of the information stabilization device and put away the storage container, removing all restrictions on Destiny's Child.

Destiny's Child was finally exposed to the outside world, but he did not immediately enter the high-dimensional information form to escape. Instead, he floated beside Han Xiao and looked around curiously, as though surprised that he was released.

"You've helped me quite a bit. I believe that freedom is a pretty good reward." Han Xiao smiled and raised his hand to show the Destiny's Child mark on the back of his hand. "Also, we've already formed a connection. I just hope that you can help me one last time…"

With a slight exchange of consciousness, Destiny's Child understood what Han Xiao meant. He nodded lightly, and his body slowly turned into a high-dimensional information form, disappearing without a trace.

"Will this really not be a problem? If we don't control Destiny's Child, and allow him to trigger the information state disturbances again, many more children will be born…" the experimenter could not help but say.

"It's alright, that's what I'm hoping."

Han Xiao waved his hands.

He had formed a connection with Destiny's Child, and their consciousness could communicate at any time. He hoped to use the information connection between Destiny's Child and many of his children to form a large net, forming a new information anchor point.

In addition, he suspected that Destiny's Child was not simple. Ever since he entered the dark side universe, he seemed to have been indirectly entangled with Destiny's Child… He had a feeling that Destiny's Child might not be a pure Primal Esper Ability Entity.

"If I'm not wrong, Destiny's Child has a special ability mechanism. He might have some kind of special connection with the Dark Side Universal Consciousness. He might even be one of the unconscious incarnations of the Dark Side Universal Consciousness."

Han Xiao thought to himself. He put on the King and disappeared.

...

One day later, in the conference room of the upper echelons of the Supers Holy Land.

There were more than ten Beyond Grade As in the room, and Aurora sat in the main seat, maintaining her sisterly posture. Her long hair was tied up, and her slightly round and exquisite face tried to maintain a serious expression.

"…I have already reviewed the recent reports. I discovered that the results of your work did not meet the expectations of the previous quarter. Although the Supers Holy Land has a stable position now, we are a force that has been established for just a few years. It is not the time to be lazy. I hope that everyone can take their jobs seriously…"

Aurora kept a straight face and criticized the people present.

This meeting had already been going on for some time. She had initiated this small-scale meeting to encourage some of the upper echelons so that they would not slack off.

Black Star had not been in charge recently, and Aurora had been acting as the leader for a long time. Now, she had also built up some prestige. The dozen or so people present gave her face and silently received the criticisms.

After talking for a while, Aurora finally stopped and said in a gentler tone, "Alright, that's all for today. I hope everyone can go back and supervise their respective departments and relay my message. Meeting dismissed."

Everyone nodded and left the room.

Only then did Aurora relax her body, no longer maintaining her smart and capable attitude. She grumbled at Han Xiao for not doing anything and left through another door.

After everyone left, Han Xiao's virtual figure appeared in the room. He looked in the direction where Aurora had left and smiled with relief.

Although Aurora liked to act young in front of him, they were actually around the same age. Han Xiao was quite happy to see Aurora acting dignified and serious. Now, she had more or less the aura of a leader, and she no longer needed someone else to protect her.

"She's no longer the little girl who needs protection…"

Han Xiao shook his head and smiled before walking around.

A weak song suddenly sounded, and Han Xiao followed the sound to the rooftop.

Feidin was holding onto Chen Xing, and the two of them were on a date. They were sticking to each other as though superglued together.

The Soul Swapper had separated their souls a long time ago, but the experience of existing as one had allowed the two of them to know each other's personalities even if they were separated. They only needed one look to guess what the other was thinking. There was no wall of hearts that could not be understood by the two, only the tacit understanding of soul mates.

Han Xiao still remembered the reason Feidin and Chen Xing had coexisted as one. It was as if they had met by fate, and in the end, it became a puzzle that fit into their lives.

All these years, his life had been smooth sailing, and it was also because of Feidin's good luck. His military medals, a small part of them was due to Feidin.

"Tsk, a winner in life…"

Han Xiao looked at them from afar and left the rooftop quietly.

He could not help but think of Hila. Speaking of which, he and Hila had met each other by fate as well. On the first day he came to the dark side of the universe, he had already formed a bond with Hila. Back then, they were still enemies. He did not expect that they would support each other and travel together to this day.

With a thought, Han Xiao arrived at Hila's residence. She had built the house beside the advanced cultivation room. Even though it was peaceful now, she did not slack off.

Hila had just finished her first round of training, so she left the training room. She returned to her room and a strange skeleton beast resembling a dog and a cat pounced on her.

Hila's usually indifferent face revealed a doting smile. She bent down and picked up the little skeleton beast, stroking its smooth and white bones. The little beast stretched comfortably in her arms.

Han Xiao tilted his head, surprised. This was the first time he had seen Hila raise a pet.

Although this pet looked a little scary in his eyes, in the eyes of Hila, who controlled the power of death, this little skeleton beast was probably quite cute. As the saying went, beauty lay in the eyes of the beholder.

Seeing Hila slowly play with her pet, Han Xiao felt a little strange.

"Raising a pet doesn't seem like something she would do…"

In his eyes, Hila's personality had always been strong and cold. She pursued greater strength and would not waste her energy on unnecessary things, making people stay away from her. Now that she had a hobby… well, having a hobby made her more of a normal person.

"This is good. She finally found some interest in life…"

Han Xiao turned around and left.

He strolled around the Supers Holy Land and observed the lives of the various Beyond Grade As. He saw many Beyond Grade As who no longer needed to fight with others and focused on their careers. It was as if most of them had found the peace and quiet that they had not felt in a long time.

Very soon, Han Xiao arrived at the business department and saw it bustling. In the office, a group of executives was queuing up to receive Sorokin's instructions.

He took a closer look and saw that Sorokin's body was emitting a faint light, and he was in the revival state. His face was full of energy, and he was in high spirits as he arranged the business plans in an orderly manner.

Under Sorokin's leadership, the economic development of the Supers Holy Land had been booming. Sorokin felt as though he had met a second spring in his career, and he had finally found a stage to showcase his strength.

Not long after, Han Xiao walked past all the departments and finally arrived at the square. There were statues of all the Beyond Grade As there.

His gaze swept across everyone's statues, and the experiences he had with the Beyond Grade As over the past few decades surfaced in his mind. Under the hard work of himself and a few pinnacle Beyond Grade As, the Beyond Grade As had gone from a pile of loose sand to a tightly-knit collective of benefits. The creation of the Supers Holy Land gave everyone a place of refuge, bearing witness to the fruits of their decades of hard work.

Although there was some animosity between them, in the end, these hundreds of statues represented the Beyond Grade As who had fought alongside him for decades. They could be considered comrades who had fought together.

"We can be considered partners…"

Han Xiao closed his eyes and vaguely felt a new information anchor being generated. He then turned around and left.

At the same time, all the Beyond Grade As in the Supers Holy Land suddenly felt something and looked up in the direction where Han Xiao had disappeared.

...

Half a day later, Han Xiao, as an uninvited guest, arrived in the Mechanical Race territory.

The Mechanical Race was no stranger to a big shot like Han Xiao, and they welcomed him.

A young Mechanic came out to receive them and brought Han Xiao to the guest room.

"Your Excellency Black Star, may I ask why you're here?"

As soon as he sat down, the young Mechanic asked curiously.

"I want to meet Manison and catch up with him."

Han Xiao smiled.

Among the many Beyond Grade A comrades, Manison was the most special one.

The two of them had been 'in love' for decades, and Han Xiao had even 'inherited' many of Manison's abilities. Therefore, Manison had a special position in Han Xiao's heart. He felt that Manison might be able to bring him a new Information Form Anchor, so he came to visit.

However, this young Mechanic shook his head and rejected his request.

"I'm sorry, Your Excellency Black Star. His Excellency Mechanic Emperor is going to conduct a long period of closed-door research. No visitor is to be allowed."

"Me too?"

"My teacher has already instructed me, especially you…" the young Mechanic replied carefully.

"Heh, this guy really doesn't hide it at all. I thought our relationship had eased up a lot."

Han Xiao then sized up the young man before him and asked,

"You're Manison's student? What's your name?"

"Allow me to formally introduce myself. I am a new student that my teacher accepted two years ago. My name is Marigo Morgan, and I am temporarily in charge of the Mechanical Race's affairs for him. Greetings, Your Excellency Black Star." This person nodded politely.

"He actually accepted a new student and didn't even inform me." Han Xiao was amazed.

Seeing that Manison was not willing to reminisce, Han Xiao did not hesitate and expressed his intention to leave.

Arriving at the Moon Platform, Han Xiao was about to board the ship and leave when he suddenly realized that a new Information Form Anchor had been created.

He looked back at the depths of the Mechanical Race territory and smiled mysteriously. He then closed the hatch, activated the spaceship, and escaped into space.

At the same time, deep within the Mechanical Race's territory.

Manison, who was in seclusion studying the technology, raised his head and looked in the direction that Han Xiao left through the wall. He did not say much and lowered his head to continue his research.

"Humph, annoying fellow…

Chapter 1461: Information Form Anchor (4)

Ancient Star Desert, a certain dead planet.

Green moonlight hung in the sky, and the cracked black earth was in perpetual silence. Not a single blade of grass could be seen, and there was not even a hint of green. Occasionally, broken buildings could be seen stuck in the ground, and the parts that emerged were filled with mottled traces of wind erosion. The exquisite carvings were already blurry, and there were also shattered statues of people lying on the ground. Some only had half a head, while others only had half a body.

This area seemed to be the ruins of some abandoned city buried by time.

A small spaceship was hovering one meter above the ground, emitting a light blue field that covered dozens of kilometers, providing remote energy and life support functions. The silver-gold spaceship had a narrow front and wide back, forming a triangular shape. Its exterior armor was also engraved with the insignias of the Supers Holy Land, Black Star Army, and Floating Dragon Island. This was a special high-end spaceship that had yet to be mass-produced by the army's logistics department. It was equipped with all kinds of cutting-edge technology and could break through the speed limit of level five warp speed to reach level 17.7. It was quite expensive.

At this moment, under the spaceship's life support field, about five hundred meters underground, two figures were slowly trekking through a maze-like ruin.

"These are the ruins of the capital of the Fifth Dynasty, and also the last remains of the people of Tersrand. Their civilization perished at the end of the exploration era, and the scavengers later dug out some ancient objects, which allowed the ruins of this civilization to see the light of day again. Speaking of which, they were unlucky. Who would have thought that their mother planet was once the resting place of a group of giant galactic beasts countless years ago? The awakening of the ancient beasts brought about a disaster to their civilization…"

Harrison stroked the blurry engravings on the wall of the underground palace as he spoke. Jenny hugged the child and listened with interest.

Jenny had already given birth to a child. After recuperating on Floating Dragon for a few months, Harrison's desire for adventure grew, and Jenny could not stay idle either. The two of them set off immediately. Using their connections, they took a cutting-edge spaceship from the army logistics department for free and explored everywhere.

Because they were carrying a child, it was not suitable for them to go to places that were too dangerous. Thus, Harrison decided to take Jenny to tour archaeological sites. For this reason, he specially joined the Spacetime Research Council and read the records of a large number of lost civilizations. He was determined to be a 'good tour guide'.

The three of them were currently wearing the new generation interstellar exploration mechanical suits produced by the army. It could withstand all kinds of extreme environments, and the baby's mechanical suit was specially made, and even had a series of functions such as mental stability, sleeping, and automatic diaper changing…

Harrison stopped in front of a row of broken statues, pointed at them, and smiled.

"This is the underground palace that the last King of Tersrand built for the past kings when he was young. In the eyes of ordinary people, he built it to honor the previous kings, but in fact, according to the records in some books, he built this underground palace to cover up a natural tunnel that goes deep underground. There was a young Ancient Beast inside, and he wanted to tame it secretly. He wanted to use this external force to break the grip that the Prince Regent had on his authority… It sounds boring, right? It's also a boring political struggle in the palace, but you definitely won't be able to guess what happened."

"He accidentally awakened more ancient beasts and destroyed the civilization?" Jenny was curious.

"Haha, you guessed wrong. He awakened this ancient beast, but he fell in love with it. Due to the special genes of the ancient beast, the closer the last Tersrand King got to the ancient beast, the more his bloodline mutated. In the end, he transformed into a new ancient beast at the court assembly and personally led the ancient beast to destroy the capital…"

"Is this love that transcends species? Or is this a mental hint from the ancient beast?"

Jenny's eyes widened. Although interspecies dating was very common, it was still quite impactful to hear of it.

Harrison shook his head. "I'm not sure. Only the person involved knows."

"What happened then?"

"After that, the slumbering ancient beasts woke up one after another and escaped into the starry sky. The last Tersrand King was nowhere to be found. Some said that he disappeared into the starry sky with the ancient beasts. Some said that he stayed with his partner in the ruins of his mother planet and wandered in this dead land forever…"

"Sounds a little romantic," Jenny said.

"Haha, we might even be able to find their corpses here. This is the purpose of our exploration."

Harrison laughed.

The two of them chatted casually as they went deeper into the underground palace. Most of the time, Harrison was the one talking, while Jenny was the one listening. Not long after, they finally arrived at the end of the underground palace. There was a tunnel blocked by rocks.

Harrison casually shattered the rocks with a punch, revealing a broken staircase that descended diagonally. He walked in with Jenny, and after walking for a long time, they finally arrived at the end. It was a cave-like space. Two beast skeletons were hugging each other as if they were lying dead in each other's arms.

"Could this be the last Tersrand King and his partner?" Jenny was curious.

"I think so… Looks like they decided to stay here to accompany each other and sleep together forever."

Harrison's eyes sparkled. He recorded a series of videos, picked up a few bones, and stored them. He planned to bring them back for research.

However, right at this moment, the ground suddenly shook. The two of them felt the cave shaking, and the tremors gradually grew larger. Soon, the ground began to shake.

Boom!

The sound of the earth veins moving could be heard. It was getting louder and louder, like the earth was roaring.

"Is it collapsing?"

Harrison's heart skipped a beat, and he immediately flew back with Jenny.

However, halfway through, the entire underground palace collapsed.

Hong Long Long~

Countless rocks fell, filling up all the gaps.

Looking down from above, the ground had instantly collapsed, turning into a huge crater.

However, right at this moment, a force field with a faint green glow suddenly descended from the sky, tearing the surface of the planet apart.

Under the guidance of the force field, a round ball of soil broke out from the ground and flew for a distance before finally landing beside the spaceship.

The ball shook, and the dirt and rocks on it fell off, revealing a round blue shield. The armors of Harrison and the other two could sense the impact of the outside world, so they automatically opened their shields. This small scene could not cause any damage to them, and the three of them were completely unharmed.

This time, Ames, who was wearing a black dress, landed from the sky and floated in front of the three of them. With a helpless expression, she said with dissatisfaction,

"How could you be so careless? I saw that you were buried alive the moment I arrived. Since you're carrying a child, don't go to such a dangerous place."

"Ahem, an accident, an accident."

Harrison was embarrassed. Although they would not be injured in the collapse, it would still take some time for them to climb out. He did not expect Ames to see them, which made him very embarrassed.

Jenny, on the other hand, did not have much of a reaction. She had been out with Harrison for more than a year, and they had been buried alive seven or eight times. Anyway, she would not get hurt, and she was used to it.

With extraordinary strength, her definition of danger was definitely different from ordinary people. Jenny was not afraid of taking a small risk with her child, so she asked curiously, "Sis, how did you find us?"

Phillip suddenly appeared and sat on Ames' shoulder, giving her a thumbs up.

"Of course it's because of me, hum… I can locate all the spaceships produced by the army, hum…"

"Alright, I almost forgot that Black Star gave you the authority to mobilize the army's artificial intelligence… Then why are you looking for us personally? Can't we talk through the communicator? Why are you disturbing our time together?"

Jenny curled her lips.

Ames turned to look at the sleeping child in Jenny's arms, a gentle smile on her face. "I missed my nephew. Can't I come and take a look? Quick, let me play with the child."

"Don't even think about it! Don't you know how heavy your hand is? Every time I give him to you, you don't know how to cherish him at all. You don't care if it's not your child, right?"

Jenny immediately objected and turned around to protect the child in her arms.

However, Ames did not listen to her. Ignoring her objections, she controlled her force field and took the child from her arms. Then, she opened the mechanical suit and used her fingers to rub the child's chubby face, waking the child up.

"Hey! Be gentler!" Jenny grabbed Ames' arm and yelled at Harrison, "What are you still doing there? Come and help!"

Harrison smiled bitterly.

The sisters were having a fight, so he did not dare to meddle.

"What do you know? I'm using my energy to clear his body and build a good foundation for him."

Ames ignored Jenny and continued to rub the baby's face. Although she controlled her strength, she did not have any parenting knowledge, so she still made the baby cry.

Jenny could not win against Ames' strength, so she had no choice but to coax the child.

"Don't you dislike children? Why are you always pestering me?"

"Just because I didn't like them before doesn't mean I still don't like them."

Ames did not even turn around and continued to tease the child, finally making him laugh.

Jenny said unhappily, "If you like them, you can have them yourself. Why are you always playing with my child?"

"What's the point of spending so much effort? Don't you have one here?" Ames blinked.

Jenny's mouth twitched. Sometimes, she really could not stand Ames' straightforward style.

She was speechless for a while before asking curiously,

"Speaking of which, have you thought about whether or not you want to have a child with Black Star? He mentioned it more than once, but you never responded to him."

"…I haven't thought about it yet. Let's think about it again." Ames was a little hesitant.

"My good sister, how long have you been thinking about this?" Jenny was speechless. "Although you guys have a long lifespan, there still has to be a result from all the thinking about, right? Only Black Star spoils you. If it were someone else, they might have even created a race at this age."

Hearing this, Ames glanced at her and clicked her tongue in wonder. "Weren't you always unhappy about me accepting Black Star? Why are you now urging me to reproduce with him?"

Jenny pursed her lips and did not speak.

In the past, she was indeed unhappy that Han Xiao was together with Ames, but now that she had a child, she wished that Han Xiao could make Ames unable to get out of bed every day so that she could have a happy life. This way, she and her child would not be harassed by Ames.

Buzz!

Space rippled slightly, and Han Xiao stepped out from the void.

"Hmm? Why are you here too?" Ames looked over and was surprised.

"You borrowed Phillip's authority. Of course, I received the news." Han Xiao shrugged.

"Then what are you doing here?" Ames narrowed her eyes and said with a strange tone. She still remembered what happened the last time and still had some emotions in her heart.

"My business is done for the time being. I came to accompany you." Han Xiao smiled.

"Do you think I need you to accompany me now?" Ames raised Jenny's child and snorted.

Han Xiao looked down at the child and saw Jenny giving him a look. He immediately walked forward, grabbed the child's clothes, and placed him in Jenny's hands. He smiled and said, "Since you like children so much, let's have one too."

"You are on that again?" Ames looked around. "Didn't I reject you?"

Han Xiao hugged Ames' waist as though there was no one else around. He smiled and said, "No matter how many times you reject, I will ask you again and again until you agree."

"Hmph, shameless… I thought a bigshot like you wouldn't have any obsession with your descendants. I didn't expect you to still be so vulgar."

Ames did not break free from Han Xiao's embrace. She only placed her hands on Han Xiao's chest and leaned back slightly, not letting him get close.

Han Xiao pondered for a few seconds before speaking from the bottom of his heart, "The world is filled with ups and downs. No matter who we are, we need something to anchor our existence, be it ideals, beliefs, or feelings… I have already made a choice. Let everything enter a new era, turning us into unique existences. There will no longer be a cycle, so I don't know what will happen in the future. I just hope that I have another place in this world that I will never forget."

"Oh, how rare. You actually know how to coax me… Don't you remember me well enough?"

"Isn't it better to go deeper?"

"…Are you teasing me?"

"What else? What do you think my hand is doing?"

The two of them had been intimate with each other countless times, so they were not shy at all. As they exchanged glances, their words became more and more explicit.

Seeing that the situation was not looking good, Harrison and Jenny quietly boarded the spaceship. They quickly started the engine, and the thrusters shot out flames as they quickly took off.

Very soon, the spaceship left outer space, and the planet became further and further away.

However, before Harrison could catch his breath, the planet behind him suddenly shook violently, and the surface of the planet shattered. A huge crater that could be seen from outer space exploded, and the shockwave swept out, sending countless sand and stones flying. It was as if the planet had suffered an unbearable impact.

Immediately after, the planet seemed to have suffered an invisible blow. The surface of the planet caved in, and the entire crust shattered like an eggshell. All the matter caved in at the center, and the surface became riddled with holes.

"These two adulterers really think we don't exist…"

Jenny was both angry and excited, as though she wanted to see the world burn. Her face was red, and she cheered them on in her heart.

The next moment, a blinding light burst forth, and the planet exploded!

Boom!

An intense wave of energy spread out and caught up to the tail of the spaceship. It even activated the protective shield and sent the spaceship flying.

After a while, the spaceship stabilized.

Harrison wiped off his cold sweat and looked back at the scene of the planet's explosion. He swallowed his saliva with a complicated expression.

"Luckily, we ran fast enough… It's a pity that these ruins…"

Chapter 1462: Information Form Anchor (5)

A few days later, on a residential planet in the Ancient Star Desert.

"Gasp, this woman…"

Han Xiao walked on the bustling streets and passed through the crowd. He activated the invisibility function and was not discovered by the passersby. He rubbed his waist from time to time and mumbled softly.

It was not easy for him to appease Ames and leave an Information Form Anchor. He was finally able to leave the crime scene and go to the other metropolitan planets. He planned to take a stroll and find a new Information Form Anchor.

"I already have quite a few Information Form Anchors on me. I can feel that my Information Form base has become much stronger, but I feel like I'm still lacking something…"

Han Xiao looked around as he pondered.

After walking for a while, he suddenly stopped and looked ahead.

Not far in front was a Wayne Cards store. There was a huge crowd at the entrance, and there was a long queue. On the side was a poster of himself, on which were written the names of various stores and offers. Today was the day of the release of the Black Star series.

In front of the shop, a shop assistant was shouting.

"This set of 'Black Star' series has a total of twenty-four cards, including the Black Star cards from different time periods. There are also thirteen new cards, all equipped with holographic effects. The appearance, attack, defense, and activation of special effects all have different holographic images. The collection value is extremely high, and this is a new product that Wayne Card's fanatics absolutely cannot miss. There are only eight thousand sets in our store, and each person can only buy two at most. It's a limited sale…"

In front of the shop, a long line of people was rubbing their fists and palms. Their faces were full of anticipation, like a group of lively leeks waiting to be harvested.

"This is a single-player set for me?"

Han Xiao blinked and did not know whether to laugh or cry.

Although Wayne Cards included most of the famous people in the galaxy, there was only a handful of them who had a whole set for themselves, which showed how shocking his popularity was in the galactic society. Speaking of which, shouldn't his portrait usage fees be increased this year?

Right at this moment, Han Xiao suddenly felt a jolt in his intuition. He sensed a new Information Form Anchor, and his expression changed slightly.

Wait, could Wayne Cards also be an Information Form Anchor…

He quickly narrowed his eyes and sensed for a while before heaving a sigh of relief.

The next moment, he opened his Virtual Vision and instantly covered the entire planet. The lives of the galactic residents jumped into his eyes.

Han Xiao saw that some people had posted his posters at home, some had bought his figurines, some were watching movies and series based on him… All the galactic residents who were related to him were marked and lit up in his vision.

"This Information Form Anchor is from the galactic society itself…"

Han Xiao pondered.

He had brought countless changes to the galactic society which deviated from the trajectory of his previous life. These were all signs that he had been there. The changes he brought to this world were all Information Form Anchors.

After experiencing all kinds of storms, the galactic society finally had the long-lost peace. Behind every galactic citizen's peaceful and happy life was his image. The respect and memories of everyone in the galactic society were the biggest Information Form Anchor.

As the galactic residents lit up one after another in his Virtual Vision, Han Xiao felt that this Information Form Anchor was getting stronger and stronger along with his Information Form base.

Han Xiao understood.

Perhaps this was the most important Information Form Anchor, to personally witness the changes he had brought to this world, to see the new life he had brought to countless people… to walk through the mortal world, to see all living things, to anchor himself to the entire world.

"Come to think of it, is this the scene of Immortal Cultivation or Cthulhu…"

Han Xiao laughed to himself before retracting his smile. He stood still and fully activated his Virtual Ability.

The next moment, countless Virtual Souls split up and spread out along the quantum network, taking in the lives of countless people.

The citizens of the planets were lit up one after another, and the Virtual Vision seemed to see a bright galaxy. The Information Form Anchor seemed to have absorbed endless nutrients and was continuously growing.

...

Central Galaxy, three Universal Civilizations' conference room.

The remote projections of Marbruce and the other two sat behind the table, whispering to each other from time to time, their eyes fixed on the door.

"Strange, why isn't Black Star here yet?"

"I've already sent him a message, but he hasn't replied. I wonder if he received any news from today's meeting?"

"He must have received it. He probably just can't be bothered to reply. Recently, he's been busy preparing for the Information Form conversion…"

"Speaking of which, what does he need to prepare? I saw that the intelligence department recently reported that Black Star has been visiting various civilizations and constantly releasing and receiving data on the quantum network. I wonder what use this has for our plan?"

"I don't understand, but he's the user of the Information Form Materialization device. He definitely knows what he's doing…"

The three of them discussed softly.

During this period, they had also been preparing for the conversion and had completed a series of preparations.

Although Han Xiao was in control of the Information Form Materialization device, it was not something that could be activated immediately. According to the messages in the Sanctum, there were many more supporting facilities required to transform the entire dark side universe. What the three Universal Civilizations were doing was creating a large number of supporting facilities for the Information Form Materialization device and installing them in different areas. The blueprints were provided by Han Xiao, and they were all supplementary devices used to enhance the transformation of the Information Form state.

The three Universal Civilizations had spent a lot of manpower and resources to install these parts, and the hardware had already been settled. Now, they only had the problem of overall planning, which could only be carried out after the official implementation of the conversion was finalized. Many of these were trivial matters, but the three Universal Civilizations handled them well, so Han Xiao gave them all these miscellaneous tasks.

While the three of them were chatting, the door suddenly opened, and the secretary led Han Xiao in. He then left and closed the door, leaving the room for a few big shots.

"Black Star, you're late. We thought you wouldn't be coming today." Marbruce heaved a sigh of relief.

"I was preparing for the conversion and was delayed."

Han Xiao casually explained.

The three of them wanted to say something, but suddenly, their expressions became strange.

Although Han Xiao's appearance did not change, for some reason, they felt that the feeling Han Xiao gave them was completely different from the last time they met.

Black Star's aura gave them an indescribable feeling, as though they were staring at a black hole.

"You seem a little different…" Marbruce said hesitantly, suspecting that it was his imagination.

"I've deepened my connection with the dark side universe. This is normal."

Han Xiao waved his hands casually.

During this period of time, he had visited most of the civilizations in the galactic society and integrated all beings into his heart, perfecting the last Information Form Anchor. At this point, his Information Form base had become extremely solid, making him give off the presence of everything returning to one.

Han Xiao did not elaborate further. He paused for a moment before asking,

"I'm almost done preparing. What about you guys?"

"We're more inclined to spend some time to verify all the information in the Sanctum… but in principle, we're all willing to cooperate with your actions to carry out the conversion plan. We're just short of time."

"Alright, the transformation won't happen overnight. It might take a few years, or it might take dozens or even hundreds of years. Therefore, the earlier we start, the better."

"Yes, we're having a meeting with you now to discuss the exact date."

The three of them nodded.

"Alright, let's have a chat."

After Han Xiao finished speaking, he exhaled lightly.

I've finally come this far…

Chapter 1463: Final Relay, Destination Point (End)

The meeting between the two parties did not last long. In the end, the date was set to be after nine years. Without the entire galactic society knowing, the fate of the dark universe they were in was decided.

Countless galactic residents were still immersed in a peaceful and happy life. In places that they could not see, the three Universal Civilizations and Han Xiao were silently preparing for the transformation of the dark side universe into the true universe. The days were approaching the official implementation of the plan.

In the long-lost era of peace, the days flew by. The sun rose and the moon set, and time flowed like water, never to return. Nine years passed quietly as the various large organizations rested. The affairs of the galactic society had changed, and a new generation of young people had grown up, but nothing seemed to have changed. The three Universal Civilizations, the Supers Holy Land, and the Super Star Cluster Alliance still occupied one side of the explored universe.

Today was the appointed date, and also the starting point for the fate of the Dark Side Universe.

In the Central Galaxy, the military forbidden zone that the three Universal Civilizations had specially built for this day.

Countless Information Form reaction strengthening devices formed a dense and neat formation in the galaxy. They were distributed layer by layer and formed a spherical shape. Han Xiao was at the center of all the support device formations, floating alone in space.

Far away, the fleets of the three Universal Civilizations were surrounded by layers of guards to prevent any accidents from disturbing Han Xiao's transformation.

In the main ship, the remote projections of the three Rulers looked at Han Xiao outside the porthole with a solemn expression.

"Your Excellency Black Star, we are all prepared. Please…"

Marbruce paused, took a deep breath, and spoke in the communication channel.

"… begin."

"…Okay."

Han Xiao replied with a calm expression. A complicated look was seen in his eyes.

Although he had rehearsed for this day more than once in the past nine years, he could not help but feel emotional when it actually happened.

The plan for the conversion of the dark universe was still a top secret of the upper echelons. The three Universal Civilizations hoped to quietly solve this ultimate problem that involved the truth of the universe when countless galactic residents were asleep. It would be best if the dark universe could be merged with the real universe without anyone noticing. Therefore, Han Xiao only told Ames and a few other trustworthy people about this information. The others continued to live their normal lives up to this day.

Han Xiao sank his consciousness into his body, and his chest slowly lit up. It was as if he had turned into a white spatial tunnel, where space folded and contracted.

Very soon, in dazzling white light, the World Tree that was rooted in his inner space appeared in the outside world, emitting a green light that was full of vitality.

Han Xiao lowered his head and looked at the miniature World Tree. His mind was already connected, and he could activate the Information Form solidification function at any time. However, at this moment, he stopped, and his eyes turned dreamy.

Information Form Anchors flashed in his mind one after another, and his eyes seemed to be filled with a rippling illusion. It was as if he was using the perspective of a third party to relive his hundreds of years of strange and magnificent life.

The final scene was fixed on countless familiar figures. There were old acquaintances, deceased enemies, present friends…

"I hope that everything that happened here will be able to anchor my existence. Don't let me forget… I've been here before."

The next moment, Han Xiao no longer hesitated and activated the Information Form solidification function of the World Tree.

Buzz!

Han Xiao's figure was instantly drowned by the light akin to the Big Bang of the universe. It was as if endless light was spraying out, filling everyone's vision.

At this moment, everyone in the galactic society felt something and subconsciously thought of Black Star.

...

Floating Dragon Island, top floor of the palace.

Ames stood on the balcony with her hands behind her back, looking up at the bright galaxy. Her long hair and black dress fluttered in the wind like black flames.

"Mom, I just thought of Dad…"

A childish voice sounded behind her, and a little girl in a dress ran out of the room. She tripped and almost fell along the way.

This little girl was about seven or eight years old. She looked like she was carved from jade, and her face was a little chubby. Her eyes were as black as gems, and she looked lively. She looked very cute and festive. She was the only offspring that Ames and Han Xiao had.

Ames turned around with a doting expression. She hugged her daughter and rubbed her nose. "I miss Daddy too."

The little girl hugged Ames' arm and stayed comfortably in her embrace. She blinked her big eyes and said with a little grievance,

"Daddy hasn't come to see me for a long time. Where did he go?"

"He's doing a huge job outside right now."

Ames smiled.

"When will Daddy be back?" The little girl's eyes widened with curiosity.

"I don't know either…"

Ames shook her head. She hugged her daughter with one hand and pointed at the deep starry sky with the other.

"However, no matter where he is, he will definitely watch over you. When you grow up, he will return."

...

The real universe, the Solar System, behind Neptune.

A small exploration space station covered in black and blue paint floated quietly in outer space, disguised as a meteorite. It looked inconspicuous.

At this moment, in the observation room of the space station, a few intelligent creatures wearing heavy spacesuits were adjusting their equipment. Their bodies were shaped like humans, but they had hard skin covered in spikes. They were short, about 1.3 meters on average.

Most of these instruments were remote observation devices. Above the instruments was a dense screen, showing scenes of cities on Earth.

At this time, one of the spiked humanoids in the room turned on the video recorder, cleared his throat, and spoke in his unique language.

"The 27,081st Planetary Year, Information Record. The observed target's behavior is the same as before. There are no abnormalities. We have yet to be discovered. Over."

"Another boring day!"

A thin, spiked humanoid beside him interrupted and stretched lazily in his seat. The hard shell and bones in his body made crackling sounds.

The person recording the video seemed to be the captain. Without turning his head, he replied seriously,

"The best news is that there are no abnormalities. Our job is to ensure that there is no technological boom on the observation target before the main force arrives, in the event that they develop a galactic weapon that can threaten us."

"Yes, yes, yes. I'm just complaining. I really hope that the next shift will come soon. I'd rather freeze and sleep than stare at this weak surface civilization every day… Sigh, I really want to go home."

The thin humanoid who had spoken earlier sounded helpless.

This group of intelligent creatures did not belong to this region. They were distant visitors from another Star System, from the Kabang Civilization.

In order to find any extraterrestrial civilizations, the Kabang Civilization sent out exploration squads to the galaxy. They took the exploration spaceships with the stealth function constantly activated and drifted in the universe for a long period of time. All the crew members were put in cryostasis. When the traces of civilization were discovered, the artificial intelligence system of the spaceships would automatically wake up the dormant crew members.

This group of Kabangs was one of the galactic explorers. Many years ago, when they came to the Solar System, the spaceship discovered the detector that the Earth Civilization had sent out into outer space, thus awakening the team. This team locked onto the Earth Civilization through the detection equipment of the spaceship, then chose a remote location, expanded their spaceship into a small space station, completed their disguise, and hid there.

This Kabang exploration team held the principle of not interfering, not communicating, and not exposing themselves. They quietly waited in the Solar System and used the galactic observation equipment provided by the spaceship to monitor Earth for a long time without being discovered.

"Stop complaining and pay more attention to your mission." The captain of the Kabang Explorer turned off the video recorder, paused, and said, "The main force is only five hundred and eighty Planetary Years away from us. We won't need to monitor them for too long and will be free."

"That's true. I really want to end the mission as soon as possible. I really can't stand eating these nutrition ointments every day. I really want to go back and eat something good…" The skinny Kabang member said with longing.

This team of explorers had long sent the news of the existence of Earth civilization back to their mother planet. The large fleet of the Kabang Civilization had already set off from their hometown, but they had not developed to the level of the stargate technology. The large fleet had been traveling in the universe near the speed of light for a very long time, and they were not far from them now.

The many explorers present had been hiding in the Solar System for many years and were only outposts. Although their technology was far ahead, they still did not dare to rashly come into contact with the Earth Civilization. Their mission was to monitor the Earth Civilization all day long and guide the subsequent main force… Only when their main forces arrived would they have sufficient confidence. Whether it was invading the colonies or destroying them, it would be a piece of cake. They would then think about how to deal with this surface civilization.

The Kabang Explorer captain was about to say something, but at that moment, the space station's surveillance radar suddenly sounded with an urgent notification.

Beep! Beep! Beep!

Everyone was stunned. They quickly moved closer to the screen and were shocked. They saw that the readings on the screen were all messed up.

"What's going on?"

This group of Kabang explorers quickly adjusted the instrument, but there were no problems with it. The various parameters of the outside world were showing more and more abnormalities, especially the curvature of space.

At the same time, with the Earth civilization as the center, a large number of spatial folds appeared, spreading outward at an astonishing speed.

"What is this? There are no similar events in the database!"

Everyone's eyes widened in shock.

At this time, an invisible energy wave suddenly erupted and spread toward the universe. It instantly swept across the various planets and the space station they were in. The energy reading instantly exceeded the power limit of the radar and caused it to burn.

Everyone was shocked and quickly touched their bodies, but they did not suffer any damage from this energy.

"This level of energy surge is unprecedented. What happened…"

Just as the group of them was feeling extremely surprised, the spatial folds had already spread to the vicinity of the space station. Through the porthole, they discovered that all the space within their sights was in ripples, like that of blanket folds.

From their point of view, it was as if the entire universe had turned into a quagmire. The torrent formed by starlight and dark matter was constantly spinning.

Amidst the layers of wrinkles, they seemed to see a strange illusion. Countless civilizations and planets that they had never seen before were floating and vanishing.

Suddenly, they had a sort of premonition.

This universe seemed to be changing.

...

"Attention, everyone! The new version will be released in five minutes. Everyone, work overtime today and log in immediately. I'm going to check on you, do you hear me?"

Zhu Xiaohua ordered loudly. Seeing that the dozens of employees in the workshop all responded, he nodded with satisfaction, turned around, walked into his private office, closed the door, and looked at the new Galaxy game cabin in the middle of the room. He rubbed his hands excitedly.

Ever since the Black Star Army video series made with the ID 'Bun-Hit-Dog' became popular, Zhu Xiaohua's career was on track. He rented a floor to use as a studio and expanded his business, making a brand.

Currently, Galaxy's popularity had reached its peak in history, and he was paying more attention to this main business. Galaxy had entered the version update two days ago, and today was the day the update would be completed. Version 6.0 would be officially released, so he took it very seriously and was prepared to log in as soon as possible.

The thought of the new version unlocking a higher level made Zhu Xiaohua's heart itch.

Although the storyline of "Galaxy" seemed to be heading toward peace, and it would be very difficult to find any more explosive points, he believed that the players would be the main characters of the stage after "Galaxy". Now that they had been unlocked to the Calamity Grade, as their level continued to increase, the players who wished for the world to be in chaos would definitely not be able to hold themselves back. They would definitely cause chaos in the game, which would lead to countless conflicts and interesting exciting stories. This way, there would definitely be no lack of materials to make videos…

Zhu Xiaohua already had an idea, and he planned to adjust the focus of the video. He would no longer focus on the Black Star Army but on the various experiences of the players and NPC organizations, making it into various series and interview records.

Just thinking about the endless supply of materials and the possibility of a huge sale made him extremely excited.

"I'm going to be rich again!"

Zhu Xiaohua was in an excited mood as he skillfully lay down in the game cabin. The hatch closed, and the countdown timer for the update was displayed on the screen. He stared with his eyes wide open at the time passing by in seconds. He could not help but shake his legs as he felt that time was passing too slowly.

"There are only a few seconds left… Five, four, three, two, one! Alright!"

At the last second, the countdown on the built-in screen turned into a login interface, and it finally became version 6.0.

Zhu Xiaohua was overjoyed and could not wait to start the game cabin. He quickly closed his eyes and prepared to enter the game.

However, after waiting for more than a minute with his eyes closed, he did not enter the Galaxy like before. Zhu Xiaohua could not help but open his eyes.

"Strange, why can't I log in? Is the game cabin malfunctioning? It can't be, this was changed two days ago…"

Zhu Xiaohua opened the game cabin in confusion and climbed out again. He squatted down to see if there was a problem with the lid of the game cabin.

However, at this moment, there was a knock on the door. A few employees walked in with helpless expressions.

"Boss, there's a problem. None of us can log in."

"Hmm? So I'm not the only one. Looks like it's not about the game cabin. Have you seen the official website?"

"I did. It seems like no one can log in."

Hearing this, Zhu Xiaohua was stunned for a moment. He walked to the computer, opened the "Galaxy" official website, and entered the forums. He realized that there were a lot of players posting, but none of them could log in.

"It seems like there's a bug in the new version. Maybe the photon processor itself is malfunctioning… But that's strange too. No one can log in. The officials will probably send a notice to explain such a huge matter. Why is there no response?"

Zhu Xiaohua browsed through the post, puzzled.

"Why don't you ask?" an employee suggested.

"Hmm, okay. I'll ask the officials."

Zhu Xiaohua nodded.

He had been invited to attend a few Pro League seasons as a guest, so he had an internal channel to contact the officials and ask about the situation.

Zhu Xiaohua picked up his phone from the table and opened his social media app. He found an official he knew and was about to send a message to ask.

However, at this moment, there was a commotion outside the office.

"What's going on outside? Why is it so noisy?"

Zhu Xiaohua frowned, paused his message, and walked out of the office. He saw all the employees gathered by the window, looking up as though they were looking at something.

"What are you guys looking at? Go back to your posts… Hmm?"

Zhu Xiaohua was a little dissatisfied. He walked over with large strides and also leaned close to the window. He subconsciously looked outside and suddenly paused.

On the road outside the window, all the pedestrians stopped and looked up at the sky. All the balconies and windows of the surrounding buildings had people sticking their heads out, looking up at the sky, their faces filled with shock.

Seeing this strange scene, Zhu Xiaohua's heart tightened. He slowly looked up at the sky.

The evening had just passed, and night had just fallen. A bright galaxy had already appeared in the sky, and more stars were shining in the night sky. The stars were like waterfalls, hanging upside down in the Milky Way, swaying and spinning. The sky seemed to have become a whirlpool, completely distorted as if someone was stirring the sky.

"This, this is…"

Zhu Xiaohua stared blankly at this scene, completely unaware that his mouth was wide open.

Just as everyone was dumbfounded, a spatial ripple suddenly appeared in the sky, and galactic fleets appeared out of thin air, attracting everyone's attention.

Zhu Xiaohua also looked over, but his eyes suddenly widened. He stared blankly at the identical emblems on the exterior armor of these battleships… This emblem was too familiar, he recognized it at a glance.

Before the crowd could react, an even more familiar figure suddenly appeared in the air. It was as if he had woken up from a deep sleep, as he opened his eyes blearily.

The expression of this figure slowly turned from a blank look to pleasant surprise before finally turning into nostalgia.

"My hometown, I'm back…"

Although he was far away, for some reason, his voice seemed to ignore the distance and sounded in everyone's hearts.

At this moment, Zhu Xiaohua, like all the employees around him, felt like he had fallen into an icehouse. Their faces were filled with confusion, and their minds blank.

At this moment, the figure in the sky seemed to have sensed the presence of someone familiar. He looked down and looked at Zhu Xiaohua from afar.

Zhu Xiaohua seemed to have woken up from a dream. He took a few steps back in disbelief, tripped over a table, and fell to the ground.

His eyes almost popped out of their sockets, and his face was filled with disbelief. His mouth trembled, and his voice involuntarily rose.

"Black Black Black Black… Black Star?!"

...

On this day, the world experienced a huge change.

Countless phantoms that should have disappeared long ago reappeared.

Some called it an 'Invasion of the Realms', while others called it a 'Turning Point of Fate'.

Some felt that this was a case of a dove occupying a magpie's nest, while others felt that this was a case of a tree spreading its branches.

Some believed that this was the beginning of the end, while others believed that this was the continuation of life.

But no matter what they thought, everything that happened on this day was remembered by countless people, and a new era was born.

—— END ——

Translators' Thoughts:

Hi guys, Chuchutrain here. I took over as the translator midway in the novel, ~Ch 400.

It feels pretty surreal that this book is now completed, considering that the author was still writing it even when I took over. I hope you enjoyed this journey with our thick-skinned (figuratively and literally) MC, the Great Mechanic Han, and hope that my translations were bearable for you guys (if they aren't, just pretend that they are :P)

I'll be moving onto a new book called Necromancer: Divine Level Summoning, so do give it some love as well! Thanks for being a part of TLM and may you always be blessed with great books to binge on :)